<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE Items SYSTEM "items.dtd">
<Items>
  <Item ItemID="1045769659">
    <Name>SPRINGERLE COOKIE BOARD ** NO RESERVE**</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Other Kitchenware</Category>
    <Currently>$14.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$14.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="torrisattic" Rating="223">
          <Location>Happy Holidays</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:23:53</Time>
        <Amount>$14.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Sunny South</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:23:53</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:23:53</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="do-south" Rating="21"/>
    <Description>Wood Springerle cookie borad depicting a FISH, flowers &amp; birds. It will imprint 8 designs in all. It is app. 3" x 8" in size. Nice patina...no cracks. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Contact must be made within 3 days of close of auction. Item must be paid for within 10 days by PayPal or Money Order for next day shipping. Personal checks must clear bank prior to shipping. International buyers must pay by PayPal or Postal Money Orders for US dollars. Buyer to pay shipping/handling and insurance if desired. Satisfaction is guaranteed if notified within 3 days of receipt of item.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045770692">
    <Name>Lanam Co. Lid to fit Longaberger Envelope NEW</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$13.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$13.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="dpaustintx" Rating="100">
          <Location>SEE MY OTHER AUCTIONS</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:25:30</Time>
        <Amount>$13.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Ohio - The Buckeye State!</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:25:30</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:25:30</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dog415@msn.com" Rating="178"/>
    <Description>You are bidding on an oak lid made by the Lanam Company to fit the Longaberger Envelope Basket. This lid has never been used or displayed, stored in my smoke free home. It features laser engraving and hand painting and is just what you need to complete your basket. Buyer to pay actual shipping. I will accept money order, paypal or personal check but will hold until check clears. Over the next few days, I will be selling several baskets and lids from my personal collection. Most have never been used or displayed. Be sure to check my other auctions. Feel free to email me with questions. Thanks for lookig!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045771355">
    <Name>Nabisco OREO Cookie Stacked Cookies Jar NR!!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Cookie Jars</Category>
    <Category>Modern (1970-Now)</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Great State of, Kentucky</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:26:02</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:26:02</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="kywildman" Rating="128"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#FFFFFF; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #ffffff; } Nabisco OREO Cookie Stacked Cookies Jar NR!!! Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Here is a wonderful Nabisco OREO Cookie Jar. Stands about 12 inches tall and features a stack of very large OREO Cookies with a comical Oreo Cookie with a face as the handle at the top. Part of the Nabisco Classics collection. Has two very small nicks in the back otherwise no cracks or crazing. If you have any questions, please email me before you bid as all sales are final and I want you to be happy with your purchase! Happy bidding! Buyer to pay actual shipping unless otherwise noted in auction description. Payments to be recieved within 10 days of close of auction. We happily take Paypal, Visa, MasterCard, Money Orders Cashier's Checks and Personal Checks, from US buyers only. Internationala Buyers payments accepted via USD Money Order or Cash Only there will be a 10 day delay in shipping your item after receiving payment by personal check. This allows enough time for the check to clear the bank. There will be a $25.00 charge for any check returned unpaid. Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Visa/Master Card, Discover, Money Order, Personal Check. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773325">
    <Name>OVERSTREET COMIC BOOK PRICE GUIDE #8 (1978)!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Other Modern Age</Category>
    <Currently>$11.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$11.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="grandmap2823" Rating="1084">
          <Location>Paypal Preferred</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:29:40</Time>
        <Amount>$11.95</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Prescott, Arizona</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:29:40</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:29:40</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="cparadise" Rating="6506"/>
    <Description>This is The Official Overstreet Comic Book Price Guide #8 (condition VF/nm; softcover), published by Overstreet Publications, 1978!!! Contents include: Grading, Storage, How to Start Collecting, Collecting Back Issues, Buying and Selling, Conventions, History of Fandom, Fanzines, Collecting Strips, Collecting Original Art, price lists, and more!! WE SHIP WORLDWIDE!!! Write to ask for shipping rates outside the USA! (**WINNERS OF MULTIPLE AUCTIONS CAN COMBINE TO SAVE ON SHIPPING**) After you bid on this item, we want to see you bidding on other items from us. However, we realize that with all the auctions we run, it is hard to look through them and find what you might want. To help you out, we have come up with 4 different ways, not generally offered by eBay, to search our auctions . 1) Click here to search our other auctions alphabetically starting from A to Z (numbers come 1st) then the As, Bs, Cs, Ds, Es, etc.! 2) Click here to search our other auctions alphabetically starting from Z to A. In this order Zs, Ys, Xs, Ws, Vs, Us, etc.! 3) Click here to search our other auctions by lowest current price to highest current price, $3.95, $4.95, $5.95, etc.! 4) Click here to search our other auctions by items closing the soonest (this is less organized but you can get last minute deals easier here)! Good Luck Bidding!! Shipping Terms: High bidder pays either $2.50 Book Rate shipping (10-21 days for delivery) or $4.00 Priority shipping (3-5 days for delivery) To cover the cost of our packing materials and employee's wages who pack the orders, all orders are subject to an 80_ handling fee. Insurance is an extra $1.10(per $50 of value) and is required on auctions closing above $25. If you choose no insurance and your package is lost or damaged, no refund is possible. We have been in business for 10 years so bid with confidence. Payment may be made with Pay-Pal (at our address of wantlist@cableone.net), with Money Order, Check, or directly with VISA, MASTERCARD, or DISCOVER. To pay by credit card directly please call us at (928)717-1030 and leave your name, item #, credit card #, expiration date, address, and telephone #. Please speak slow and clear as you have about 2 minutes to record this information. To pay by check or money order please send payment to: Randy Tusha P.O. Box 4224 Prescott, AZ 86302-4224 Payment must be received within 10 days of close of auction. Positive feedback will only be left for those paying promptly, and only after you have received your order and are satisfied. Negative feedback will be left for anyone who doesn't pay! ***SPECIAL NOTE*** WE ARE CLOSED ON WEEKENDS! We contact all winners on Mon-Wed following the auctions. Randy &amp; Michelle Tusha Hours: Monday - Friday 10:00 A.M to 6:00 P.M. Mountain Time (928)717-1030 Besides our normal 300-400 auctions per week: Click here to see our HIGHER DOLLAR items, listed on EBAY! Click here to e-mail us with questions about this or any other item we are listing on eBay!!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773349">
    <Name>Great 3color DIRIGO acl soda bottle BOAT lake</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bottles: Modern (1900-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Sodas</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$48.64</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>DEACON JONE'S LOCKER</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:30:55</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:30:55</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dknjonz" Rating="385"/>
    <Description>Fantastic "near-mint/mint" condition- no chips, cracks, or case wear; super-glossy, three color painted label and smooth, scratch-free glass. Twelve ounce size, from Dirigo Bottling Co., Portland, Maine. 1942. A real beauty! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773721">
    <Name>ELVIS PRESLEY BLACK AND WHITE.NR</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Art, Animation &amp; Photo Images</Category>
    <Category>Photographic Images</Category>
    <Category>Contemporary (1940-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Celebrity</Category>
    <Category>Other</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>MISSOURI</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:30:59</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:30:59</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="angel65767" Rating="63"/>
    <Description>IT IS A BLACK AND WHITE PICTURE OF ELVIS PRESLEY,IT IS NOT A CUT OUT EITHER.I,VE HAD IT FOR A LONG WHILE.IT IS ABOUT A 13 BY 10 PICTURE WITH FRAME.BUYER PAYS SHIPING AND HANDLING ALSO INSURANCE.THANK YOU FOR STOPING BY.GOOD LUCK ON BIDDING.NR</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045776745">
    <Name>Vintage Mirro Cookie-Pastry Press W/Recipes</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bakeware</Category>
    <Currently>$26.00</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$113.32</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$8.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>6</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kathyh05" Rating="1050">
          <Location>Calif</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 11:15:38</Time>
        <Amount>$11.82</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jaci888" Rating="1262">
          <Location>OR</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 05:55:38</Time>
        <Amount>$14.66</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="worldsawayimport@aol.com" Rating="2220">
          <Location>Beautiful Lake Tahoe, CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 00:35:38</Time>
        <Amount>$17.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="blagnothing666" Rating="214">
          <Location>Kingston PA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 19:15:38</Time>
        <Amount>$20.33</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="rose-noire" Rating="341">
          <Location>Northern California</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 13:55:38</Time>
        <Amount>$23.16</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="judyandjef@aol.com" Rating="1126">
          <Location>Fl.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 08:35:38</Time>
        <Amount>$26.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Northville, MI 48167</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:35:38</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:35:38</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="meldarr" Rating="3402"/>
    <Description>Vintage Mirro Cookie-Pastry Press W/Recipes This is a vintage Mirro brand cookie-pastry press in the original box with recipes. You are getting the aluminum press, 12 cookie plates and 3 pastry tips, and an instruction/recipe book. This is in very good condition -- looks like it was never used. All the pieces fit down into a styrofoam base and there is a box bottom only -- I think a lid of some type is missing, but the base fits over the styrofoam. If you are planning to make holiday Spritz cookies -- this is just what you need! NO RESERVE! Buyer agrees by bidding to pay $5.20 for shipping in the U.S. Most likely, the shipping quote is priority mail through the USPS, but I also use first class, or media mail if appropriate. Insurance is optional at $1.10 for the first $50. coverage. If you opt to not have insurance it is understood that you are shipping at your own risk. If I have not given a quote above it is because this weighs more than 5 lbs. wrapped and the costs vary depending on where you live -- You can get an exact quote by going to the postal website at www.usps.gov -- my zip code is 48167. I cannot ship UPS. International rates will be higher -- write me for a quote before you bid if you are concerned about the cost. Bid on more than one item to save shipping costs!! ALL THE FINE PRINT: Personal checks, money orders, PayPal, Billpoint or Bidpay are accepted. I make every effort to ship as soon as possible with any type of payment. Since I list a wide variety of collectibles, I can't be an expert on everything. I do try to be as accurate as possible in my item descriptions, but I may inadvertently leave out some information because I'm not that familiar with a particular piece. If you have any questions, please feel free to e-mail me. Thank you for looking!! Michigan residents must pay 6% sales tax or provide me with your tax ID#. Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="iid=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Free counters provided by Honesty.com This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $6.30 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (6.000% if shipped to MI) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions If the shipping amount is listed as $1.10 only, that is just the insurance. It is because this weighs more than 5 lbs. wrapped. I will need to calculate the shipping cost based on your address. Returns allowed if item not as listed.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045780900">
    <Name>FATHOM 0 GREEN PRISM VAR SIGNED LIM 250 RARE</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Other Modern Age</Category>
    <Currently>$22.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$22.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>AUBURN CA.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:43:45</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:43:45</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="scout0001" Rating="1127"/>
    <Description>THIS IS THE GREEN PRISIM VARIANT SIGNED BY TURNER AND LIMITED TO 250 COPIES. VERY LIMITED AND VERY RARE. NM CONDITION. BUYER TO PAY $3.50 PRIORITY.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045781414">
    <Name>Longaberger Double Chocolate Cocoa Tin</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$4.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$30.83</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$4.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Lehigh Valley, PA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:45:07</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:45:07</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bonaire3" Rating="157"/>
    <Description>This Double Chocolate Cocoa Tin is brand new from the Homestead. It contains 2.5 oz of Double Chocolate Cocoa. This item was produced exclusively for the Longaberger Company by McSteven's, Inc. It is labeled collectable mini tin #369. Priority shipping &amp; handling is $3.50. I accpet PayPay, Billpoint, and money orders. Personal checks will be accepted from eBayers with a positive feedback rating of 40+. Payment must be received within 10 days of auction close or auction considered void. See my other auctions and save on shipping. Please e-mail with questions prior to bidding. Thank you.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045781936">
    <Name>Longaberger/Mary's Moo Moos HOMESTEAD SIGN!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$30.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$29.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kidsgalorenmoreaw" Rating="172">
          <Location>Lake Wales, Fl.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 02:21:58</Time>
        <Amount>$30.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="badangel49" Rating="1">
          <Location>La Plata, MD</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 11:57:58</Time>
        <Amount>$30.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Dayton, Ohio</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:45:58</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:45:58</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="terih" Rating="4171"/>
    <Description>Hello! This is a great new Longaberger/Enesco Mary's Moo Moos exclusive item! This is a resin piece with a Mary's Moo Moo standing next to the 'Welcome To The Longaberger Homestead' sign. She is holding the classic Apple basket filled with daisies. This is a very detailed item! Just check out the picture. The back of the sign also shows the back of the cow, sign, and more daisies! Bottom states'"From our hearts to you a little moo and daisies too" The Longaberger Company Exclusive'. This is brand new and includes its original box with registration card. Measures 5 1/2" x 3 1/4". Buyer pays $4.50 shipping. Insurance is additional. Credit cards by Paypal, MO, and personal checks accepted. Please click on my "me" page for all the specifics and fine print. Also check out all of my other auctions. I combine items to save you on shipping. E-mail response expected within 3 days, payment within 14 days. Thanks for looking! Teri Click HERE to see my other auctions! I combine items to save you shipping! Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="iid=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045782248">
    <Name>57pc ROGERS PRECIOUS MIRROR FLATWARE W/BOX</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Tableware</Category>
    <Category>Flatware</Category>
    <Currently>$69.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$69.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>merlin</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:46:05</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:46:05</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="$303" Rating="534"/>
    <Description>57pc ROGERS PRECIOUS MIRROR FLATWARE W/BOX THIS IS A VERY NICE SET OF ROGERS FLATWARE. ITS PRECIOUS MIRROR PATTERN AND THE PIECES ARE : 8-8 1/2 INCH KNIFES , 8-7 INCH SOUP SPOONS , 16-6 INCH TEA SPOONS , 8-7 1/2 INCH FORKS , 8-6 3/4 INCH FORKS , 1-8 3/4 INCH SERVING FORK , 1-6 INCH LADLE , 2-8 1/4 INCH SERVING SPOONS , 1-9 1/2 INCH PIE SERVER , 1-9 INCH VEGETABLE SERVER , 1-7 3/4 INCH TOMATO SERVER , 1-6 INCH SUGAR SPOON , AND 1-6 3/4 INCH BUTTER KNIFE. THE SET IS IN VERY NICE CONDITION WITH NO TABLE WARE AND LITTLE TARNISH. THE CHEST IS MADE WITH DOVE TAIL CONSTRUCTION AND IN GREAT CONDITION. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045785902">
    <Name>Longaberger Serving Solutions 8x8 Bskt &amp; Prot</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Dinnerware, Serving</Category>
    <Currently>$40.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$40.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="craftskitty" Rating="33">
          <Location>Grand Rapids,Mi</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:54:10</Time>
        <Amount>$40.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Exeter, CA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:54:10</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:54:10</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bethmicari" Rating="28"/>
    <Description>Just in time for the holidays. You are bidding on a BRAND NEW Longaberger SERVING SOLUTIONS 8 X 8 BASKET, DIVIDED PROTECTOR AND REGULAR PROTECTOR . This is brand new, never been used. Please see my other auctions for other Longaberger Items. Thanks for shopping and have a nice Holiday Season. Buyer to pay 5.95 shipping.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045788253">
    <Name>Home Interior Rooster SconcesPr. / MIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>HOMCO</Category>
    <Currently>$18.95</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$36.59</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$18.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>York, Pa.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:59:11</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:59:11</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bbw55" Rating="595"/>
    <Description>Two Home Interior Hostess Only "Morning Rooster Sconces" in black metal. Measures 4-1/4" x 5-1/4" x 13". Both are mint in the box. I have votive cups available for separate purchase if needed. Shipping in the U.S. priority mail will be $3.95, plus $1.10 optional ins. I accept money orders, cashiers checks, bidpay and paypal. Personal checks accepted with a 14 banking business hold to clear. Payment is to be received within 10 days of auction close. Visit my other auctions for more Home Interior and I will combine on shipping when possible. New items added weekly.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045788549">
    <Name>DEPARTMENT 56 SNOWBABIE MAKE IT SHINE NEW</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snowbabies</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$61.32</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Eighty Four</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:59:48</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:59:48</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="louber" Rating="1417"/>
    <Description>DEPARTMENT 56 SNOWBABIE MAKE IT SHINE NEW THIS IS A BRANDE NEW DEPARTMENT 56 SNOWBABIE NAMED "MAKE IT SHINE". IT IS MINT IN THE ORIGINAL PACKAGING. THIS IS AN EXCLUSIVE SNOWBABIE AND CAN'T BE BOUGHT IN ANY STORE. THIS BEAUTIFUL SNOWBABIE HAS ANGEL WINGS ON ITS BACK. SHE IS PLACING A SWAROVSKI CRYSTAL STAR ATOP THE CHRISTMAS TREE, WHILE HER PENGUIN FRIEND WATCHES WITH EXCITEMENT. IT MEASURES 3 3/4" H x 3"W AND IS MADE OF BISQUE PORCELAIN, WITH HAND PAINTED FACIAL FEATURES AND HAND APPLIED BISQUE CRYSTALS. PAYMENTS CAN BE MADE BY MONEY ORDERS, CHECKS AND BIDPAY ONLY. WINNING BIDDER WILL PAY $3.95 SHIPPING. INSURANCE IS EXTRA. THANKS FOR LOOKING AND HAPPY HOLIDAYS. click on image to enlarge Please visit our other auctions! Powered by The Auction Solution Copyright 2001 Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions PAYMENTS MUST BE RECEIVED WITHIN 10 DAYS AFTER THE AUCTION HAS ENDED.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045788675">
    <Name>DICKENS VILLAGE RETIRED WOOL SHOP W/BOX</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Dickens Village</Category>
    <Currently>$75.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$75.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Grand Haven, Michigan</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:00:00</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:00:00</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dickens_donnie" Rating="0"/>
    <Description>Dept 56 Dickens Village Series "WOOL SHOP" (no. 5924-2) issued in 1987 and retired in 1990. There are ivy sided turret rounds out one front corner of the shop. Wood framing around the 3 front windows. The shop is part of the Cobbelstone Shops series. It is in excellent condition along with the original box and sleeve. Buyer will pay actual shipping (and insurance if requested by the buyer-we recommend it since we can not be responsible for the item once it leaves our hands) to be determined at the time of sale. Payment is appreciated in 7 days, auction will be voided if payment is not received within 2 weeks. Money order and cashiers checks will ship the next day. Personal checks are OK but will delay shipping by 7 business days. We have additional hard to find pieces, please let us know if you are looking for a specific one. HAPPY HOLIDAYS! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Checks and money orders should be sent to Donald Wolffis; 413 Sandpiper; Grand Haven, MI 49417..items will be sent after personal checks clear..money orders will be sent the next day.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045788878">
    <Name>SNOWBABIES - I'M AN ARTIST - SET OF 3 - MIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snowbabies</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>New Jersey</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:59:56</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:59:56</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="chardi" Rating="242"/>
    <Description>Snowbabies _I_m an Artist Part of the Department 56 Snowbabies, number 69069. This piece was introduced in 2000. Set of Three. Item is in mint condition in original sleeve and only removed for inspection. Buyer to pay a fixed shipping/handing and insurance fee of $6.00. Payments should be received within ten days of auction_s close. Item shipped immediately with cashier_s check, Paypal, or money order. Personal checks must clear before item is shipped. Feel free to contact me with any questions. Please view my other auctions. Thank You!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045789448">
    <Name>God Of War XENA Season 6 9 CARD SET **NEW**</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Trading Cards</Category>
    <Category>Science Fiction</Category>
    <Category>Other Sci-Fi</Category>
    <Currently>$3.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$3.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>FARGO, ND.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:00:27</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-18-01 17:00:27</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lantrn1" Rating="6352"/>
    <Description>THIS MINT CARD SET HAS 9 CARDS. YOU ARE BIDDING ON THE SET ONLY. THIS HAS JUST COME OUT FROM RITTENHOUSE. PLEASE SEE MY OTHER AUCTIONS FOR AUTOGRAPHS, COSTUME CARDS AND OTHER INSERTS. SHIPPING IS $1.50. MULTIPLE WINNERS CAN COMBINE FOR CHEAPER SHIPPING COSTS. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045789543">
    <Name>Aphrodite XENA Season 6 COSTUME CARD #R3</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Trading Cards</Category>
    <Category>Science Fiction</Category>
    <Category>Other Sci-Fi</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="*2ndhand*" Rating="216">
          <Location>Adirondacks</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 05:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$9.95</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>FARGO, ND.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:00:31</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-18-01 17:00:31</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lantrn1" Rating="6352"/>
    <Description>THIS MINT COSTUME CARD COMES ONE TO A BOX. YOU ARE BIDDING ON THIS CARD ONLY. THIS SET HAS JUST COME OUT FROM RITTENHOUSE. PLEASE SEE MY OTHER AUCTIONS FOR AUTOGRAPHS, COSTUME CARDS AND OTHER INSERTS. SHIPPING IS $1.00. MULTIPLE WINNERS CAN COMBINE FOR CHEAPER SHIPPING COSTS. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045790496">
    <Name>Dept 56 Snow Village Lionel Electric Shop NIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$27.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$27.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kdeitrick" Rating="178">
          <Location>SUNSHINE STATE</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 11:02:16</Time>
        <Amount>$27.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>U.S.A.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:02:16</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:02:16</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="tbenterprises" Rating="10"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#ffffff; } a.textLink { color:#93A836;} HR { color: #ffffff; } Dept 56 Snow Village Lionel Electric Shop NIB Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version This is a wonderful retired piece by Department 56 from the Snow Village Collection titled "Lionel Electric Train Shop". This item is brand new, never been displayed, comes in the original box, and from a smoke-free home! Winning bidder to pay $7.70 USPS Priority Shipping. Insurance is extra and highly recommended (see below). MAKE SURE YOU CHECK OUT MY OTHER ITEMS BY CLICKING ON THE STOREFRONT LINK AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS PAGE. I will COMBINE SHIPPING CHARGES with multiple purchases, but to make sure I am aware of your multiple purchases..please e-mail me following the auction close in order to get a quote on shipping RIGHT AWAY!!! Payment must be received within 10 days of auction close or item will be relisted and negative feedback may be posted - depending on circumstances. I accept PayPal, Money Orders, personal checks, and Cashier's Checks! PayPal and Money orders ship within 3 business days of payment receipt. Personal checks will require clearance (usually 7 days) before shipping. Shipping DOES NOT INCLUDE INSURANCE. Due to the increase in postal rates insurance will be an additional cost. Priority rates for insurance are $1.10 for up to $50.00 and $2.00 for $50.01 up to $100.00. Buyer assumes liability for lost or damaged items not insured. Please include item description and ebay item number if possible on all correspondence. PLEASE USE THE LINK ON THE WINNING BID NOTIFICATION E-MAIL I SEND TO COMPLETE THE TRANSACTION! Not doing so may delay processing your item. All bids are expected to be honored! Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Money Order, Personal Check. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045790825">
    <Name>Dept 56 Heritage East Willet Pottery NIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$22.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$22.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>U.S.A.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:02:34</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:02:34</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="tbenterprises" Rating="10"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#ffffff; } a.textLink { color:#93A836;} HR { color: #ffffff; } Dept 56 Heritage East Willet Pottery NIB Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version This is a wonderful retired piece by Department 56 from the Heritage Village Collection titled "East Willet Pottery". This item is brand new, never been displayed, comes in the original box, and from a smoke-free home! Winning bidder to pay $7.70 USPS Priority Shipping. Insurance is extra and highly recommended (see below). MAKE SURE YOU CHECK OUT MY OTHER ITEMS BY CLICKING ON THE STOREFRONT LINK AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS PAGE. I will COMBINE SHIPPING CHARGES with multiple purchases, but to make sure I am aware of your multiple purchases..please e-mail me following the auction close in order to get a quote on shipping RIGHT AWAY!!! Payment must be received within 10 days of auction close or item will be relisted and negative feedback may be posted - depending on circumstances. I accept PayPal, Money Orders, personal checks, and Cashier's Checks! PayPal and Money orders ship within 3 business days of payment receipt. Personal checks will require clearance (usually 7 days) before shipping. Shipping DOES NOT INCLUDE INSURANCE. Due to the increase in postal rates insurance will be an additional cost. Priority rates for insurance are $1.10 for up to $50.00 and $2.00 for $50.01 up to $100.00. Buyer assumes liability for lost or damaged items not insured. Please include item description and ebay item number if possible on all correspondence. PLEASE USE THE LINK ON THE WINNING BID NOTIFICATION E-MAIL I SEND TO COMPLETE THE TRANSACTION! Not doing so may delay processing your item. All bids are expected to be honored! Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Money Order, Personal Check. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045792355">
    <Name>Hallmark 1996 FELIZ NAVIDAD Orn MIMB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$7.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$7.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Pittsburgh - Home of Steelers !</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:04:59</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:04:59</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="libbylibbylibby" Rating="1673"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://home.adelphia.net/~libbys/snow.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Hallmark 1996 FELIZ NAVIDAD Orn MIMB Hallmark 1996 FELIZ NAVIDAD Sculpted by linda Sickman This Hallmark Ornament is Mint in mint box, never displayed, and comes from a totally smoke free home. Bid with confidence that you are purchasing from a top seller of Hallmark items. Buyer to pay $4.50 for USPS Priority shipping &amp; handling for ornaments and most other Hallmark items except Kiddie Cars , Insurance is additional based on final value. Shipping Charges are for one item, typically we can ship up to three Hallmark Ornaments based on the total weight at the single item cost. Heavier items when combined will cost a little more. Please see my other Auctions to combine and save $ on shipping costs. Our shipping costs are all based on Priority mail shipping. We do not use shipping costs as a way to make money only to cover the costs of packaging materials and Postage. We do not ship standard mail in the US at reduced rates so please don't ask. Even though our packaging top notch and we have very very few problems or lost mail We assume no liability for items shipped without insurance so if you have any reservations about item damage please ask for insurance. This pricing is for US addresses only. International bidders should contact me before auction ends for a shipping estimate, based on your needs. Payment is expected within 7 days of close of auction. Methods of payment accepted are PayPal, BillPoint Yahoo Paydirect, postal money orders or cashier's checks for immediate shipping upon receipt. Personal checks are also welcome but may delay shipping up to 10 days while check is clearing bank. Returned Checks are subject to a $15.00 handling fee. Please email me if you have any questions or would like additional images.Thank you for Bidding Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="item=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Please check out the other auctions we currently have running on eBay to combine and save on shipping charges. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $4.50 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.10 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions We want you to be as satisfied with your Hallmark items as we are in them. We sell only 1st quality items unless otherwise it stated in Auction .Returns on items that are clearly not as described.. No returns without prior notification and approval.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045793153">
    <Name>Good Friends Are For Always 524131 Ornament</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$7.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$7.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Springfield, MO</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:06:34</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:06:34</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="no.1teacher" Rating="37"/>
    <Description>This 1992 figurine ornament has a treble clef mark. It comes with its original box and papers. It is in mint condition. This charming girl is holding her bunny. The girl has pastel purple hat, coat, and pants. The hat has a pink pom pom on the top of it with a rough edge look around the brim. She has blond hair. The bunny has a pink bow between its ears and is in a pink dress. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $4.00 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.10 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions Payment Accepted: Money Order, Cashiers Checks, Billpoint, Paypal. Winning bidder will pay $4.00 for shipping for the 1st piece and $1.00 additional for every extra piece won in the United States. Insurance is an additional $1.10 and is choice of buyer. Without insurance, I do not guarantee the figurine. No returns.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045795074">
    <Name>LUCY AND ME LUCY RIGG BEAR PEACE ON EARTH</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Lucy &amp; Me</Category>
    <Currently>$11.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$8.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>5</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="cutsiepups" Rating="484">
          <Location>CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 14:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$9.10</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="abraceme" Rating="216">
          <Location>East Coast</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 11:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$9.70</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ex0rcist2000" Rating="190">
          <Location>CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 08:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$10.30</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="consider.it" Rating="509">
          <Location>Anacortes, Wa.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 05:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$10.90</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ianmuir681@aol.com" Rating="97">
          <Location>Caithness, Scotland</Location>
          <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 02:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$11.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>CH-CH-CHICAGO</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:10:31</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:10:31</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="kag54" Rating="781"/>
    <Description>LUCY AND ME PEACE ON EARTH ENESCO 1992 by Lucy Rigg &amp; Co. Lucy &amp; Me is gone. It is no longer in production. This is a cute piece is a bear dressed as the world, holding a banner that reads" Peace On Earth". Also has a small dove on his head.. Approximately 3 1/4 " in height. You can see by the picture this piece has great coloring. The bottom of the piece has the Lucy and Me markings. Good Luck Bidding. This bear needs a good home! A great addition to the Lucy and Me or bear collector. See my other auctions for Lucy And Me and Lucy Riggs items. BUYER TO PAY $3.50 IN SHIPPING AND DELIVERY, COST ADJUSTED FOR INSURANCE OR SHIPPING OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES. MONEY ORDER OR CASHIERS CHECK ARE PREFERRED METHOD OF PAYMENT. IF PAYING BY PERSONAL CHECK, SHIPMENT WILL BE MADE AFTER CHECK CLEARS. METHOD OF PAYMENT FOR WINNERS OUTSIDE OF UNITED STATES WILL BE DETERMINED AT A LATER DATE. PAYMENT EXPECTED WITHIN 10 BUSINESS DAYS AFTER AUCTION ENDS. Click below to... View my other auctions _ Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045795128">
    <Name>DEPT 56 SV CHOPPING FIREWOOD - MIB - SET/2</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>New Jersey</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:10:19</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:10:19</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="chardi" Rating="242"/>
    <Description>Snow Village _Chopping Firewood This item is part of the Department 56 Snow Village #54863. This piece was introduced in 1995 and is current. Set of 2. Father chops wood as son stacks into ventilated cords. Materials are ceramic and wood. This item is in mint condition in original sleeve and only removed for inspection. Buyer to pay a fixed shipping/handing and insurance fee of $5.00. Payments should be received within ten days of auction_s close. Item shipped immediately with cashier_s check, Pay Pal or money order, personal checks must clear before item is shipped. Feel free to contact me with any questions. Please view my other auctions. Thank You!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045795866">
    <Name>17 #1 Comics Worth A LOOK! NM-MINT!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$19.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$19.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Mankato</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:12:00</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:12:00</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lazyacre" Rating="191"/>
    <Description>ones#2 17 #1 Comics Worth A LOOK!! NM-MINT!! This lot consists of ; 17 #1 comics in nm-mint condition except for Rima the Jungle Girl which is in fine condition, the starting bid is less than 1/2 of The Overstreet Price Guide Value. _ These comics have been bagged and boarded since they were first sold, check out the scans and judge for yourself. _ TERMS AND SHIPPING By bidding on this auction, you agree to the following terms: Payment must be received within 10 days. Money orders shipped immediately. Checks need 10 days to clear. You pay shipping only _ no handling charge. All comics sent priority mail with delivery confirmation. Shipping rates are as follows; (5 regular size comics = 1 lb.) 1-5 comics $3.90 6-10 comics $4.35 11-15 comics $5.55 16-20 comics $6.75 21-25 comics $7.95 Thanks for bidding! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045796439">
    <Name>Pampered Cheff meat pounder</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Utensils</Category>
    <Category>Other Utensils</Category>
    <Currently>$2.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="rickflash" Rating="119">
          <Location>Vic</Location>
          <Country>Canada</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 12:25:14</Time>
        <Amount>$2.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Montclair, NJ</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:13:14</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:13:14</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="gmckelv@aol.com" Rating="91"/>
    <Description>This is a brand new meat pounder to make your meat flat. Works great. I have two of these. I use the other one all the time. It makes your meat (like chicken and steak) more flat and thin. Shipping is 3.95 Paypal or money order Check out my other auction and safe on shipping Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions sales are final.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045796776">
    <Name>1998 HALLMARK 1917 CURTISS JENNY PLANE 2nd</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Series Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$11.51</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>5</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="realgrafs" Rating="885">
          <Location>NEW YORK</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 14:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$5.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="littlericky1" Rating="694">
          <Location>C.C.CA.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 11:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$7.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="sacauction" Rating="1113">
          <Location>Sacramento California</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 08:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$8.51</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="wdgould" Rating="1415">
          <Location>Mid Michigan</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 05:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$10.01</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="marvinski" Rating="306">
          <Location>MOTTRAM, CHESHIRE</Location>
          <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 02:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$11.51</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Englewood, CO</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:14:15</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:14:15</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="mannor" Rating="63"/>
    <Description>This is #2 in the Sky's the Limit series. The 1917 Curtiss JN-4D _Jenny,_ 1998 Hallmark Ornament. The ornament and box are both mint. This is a non smoking home. The winning bidder will pay $4.00 S&amp;H in the USA. Your package will be shipped by the USPS Priority mail. Insurance is additional, and based on the final value. We assume no liability for the items shipped without insurance. (We ship outside of the USA only if paid via Paypal and bidder pays actual cost of shipping.) Payment expected within 10 days of the close of the auction. Methods of payment accepted are Paypal, money orders, and cashier's checks for immediate shipping upon receipt. Personal checks also welcome, but will delay shipping for 10 working days while check clears my bank. Please explore my other auctions and combine purchases to save on shipping costs. Note that I also have the first and third planes in this series up for auction as well! THANKS for your time.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045797007">
    <Name>Spiderman Pg 22 issue 247 Marvel Comics</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Original Comic Art</Category>
    <Category>Other Original Art</Category>
    <Currently>$31.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$20.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>4</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="bizzzybone" Rating="617">
          <Location>Ca</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 17:14:32</Time>
        <Amount>$22.75</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="marathon517" Rating="75">
          <Location>Castle Country, UT</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 17:14:32</Time>
        <Amount>$25.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="digipitch" Rating="10">
          <Location>San Francisco</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 17:14:32</Time>
        <Amount>$28.25</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="JW" Rating="346">
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 17:14:32</Time>
        <Amount>$31.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Midwest</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:14:32</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:14:32</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dyad" Rating="314"/>
    <Description>This is the one of a kind original page by Luke Ross! The actual page is on 11" x 17" comic paper. Checks, Money Orders, and Cashier Checks accepted. $5.00 shipping (within the USA) &amp; handling will be added to the winning bid. Insurance and international orders are extra. Payment must be received within 10 working days of first contact. Serious bidders only, please! If you don't really want it, don't bid. Please do not bid if not planning on buying. Lately we are getting back into people bidding, and not replying to our e-mails. Without exception, it has been folks with 0-3 feedbacks, newcomers to Ebay, and while we're glad you're here! But if you want to bid, we ask that you email us your contact information so we can take your bid seriously. So if you can't afford it, don't bid. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045798681">
    <Name>COMIC READER #94-95 FANZINES (1973) CHAYKIN!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Magazines</Category>
    <Category>Fanzines, Fan Clubs</Category>
    <Currently>$11.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$11.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Prescott, Arizona</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:17:41</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:17:41</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="cparadise" Rating="6506"/>
    <Description>This is The Comic Reader #94-95 (condition averages VF; Fanzines!), published by TCR Publications, 1973!!! Features: Howard Chaykin cover issue #94, Ronn Sutton cover issue #95, Marvel, DC, Warren, Underground Comix, EC, Comic Strips, Conan, Spiderman, Shazam, Will Eisner The Spirit, Fanzine Reviews, Maryland Minicon, New York Comic Art Convention, Jonah Hex, Worlds Unknown, Vault of Horror, Comic Art Fan Awards, and more!! WE SHIP WORLDWIDE!!! Write to ask for shipping rates outside the USA! (**WINNERS OF MULTIPLE AUCTIONS CAN COMBINE TO SAVE ON SHIPPING**) After you bid on this item, we want to see you bidding on other items from us. However, we realize that with all the auctions we run, it is hard to look through them and find what you might want. To help you out, we have come up with 4 different ways, not generally offered by eBay, to search our auctions . 1) Click here to search our other auctions alphabetically starting from A to Z (numbers come 1st) then the As, Bs, Cs, Ds, Es, etc.! 2) Click here to search our other auctions alphabetically starting from Z to A. In this order Zs, Ys, Xs, Ws, Vs, Us, etc.! 3) Click here to search our other auctions by lowest current price to highest current price, $3.95, $4.95, $5.95, etc.! 4) Click here to search our other auctions by items closing the soonest (this is less organized but you can get last minute deals easier here)! Good Luck Bidding!! Shipping Terms: High bidder pays either $2.50 Book Rate shipping (10-21 days for delivery) or $4.00 Priority shipping (3-5 days for delivery). To cover the cost of our packing materials and employee's wages who pack the orders, all orders are subject to an 80_ handling fee. Insurance is an extra $1.10(per $50 of value) and is required on auctions closing above $25. If you choose no insurance and your package is lost or damaged, no refund is possible. We have been in business for 10 years so bid with confidence. Payment may be made with Pay-Pal (at our address of wantlist@cableone.net), with Money Order, Check, or directly with VISA, MASTERCARD, or DISCOVER. To pay by credit card directly please call us at (928)717-1030 and leave your name, item #, credit card #, expiration date, address, and telephone #. Please speak slow and clear as you have about 2 minutes to record this information. To pay by check or money order please send payment to: Randy Tusha P.O. Box 4224 Prescott, AZ 86302-4224 Payment must be received within 10 days of close of auction. Positive feedback will only be left for those paying promptly, and only after you have received your order and are satisfied. Negative feedback will be left for anyone who doesn't pay! ***SPECIAL NOTE*** WE ARE CLOSED ON WEEKENDS! We contact all winners on Mon-Wed following the auctions. Randy &amp; Michelle Tusha Hours: Monday - Friday 10:00 A.M to 6:00 P.M. Mountain Time (928)717-1030 Besides our normal 300-400 auctions per week: Click here to see our HIGHER DOLLAR items, listed on EBAY! Click here to e-mail us with questions about this or any other item we are listing on eBay!!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045799297">
    <Name>Unusual Vintage Tennis Shaving Mug</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Shaving</Category>
    <Currently>$20.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$20.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>MA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:19:45</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:19:45</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="elmwood97" Rating="500"/>
    <Description>This nice shaving mug has a transfer tennis scene on two sides. It stands 3 __T. x 6_W including the handle. I would guess it to be at least 50 years or older. It is marked Arthur Wood England on bottom. There is all over crazing and a __ chip on inside of handle. The transfers also have some wear. Buyer to pay S/H/I and payment must be received within 10 days of auction close. Foreign buyers must put their purchase on a credit card no exceptions. RETURN POLICY: If you find your item is not as represented, we have a 7 day return policy. Any of our price and/or inventory stickers must be intact and not removed. Please contact us first for permission to return. Also, repack in the same wrapping and box that you received it in and return to us via insured mail. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045800287">
    <Name>1847 Rogers Bros. serving knife</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Tableware</Category>
    <Category>Flatware</Category>
    <Currently>$7.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$7.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Elephant Butte Lake...., NM</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:20:13</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:20:13</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="kreser" Rating="755"/>
    <Description>The length on this old serving knife is 14", and while the condition isn't the best, it may still fill out a set somewhere. In tiny print on the handle it says "1847 ROGERS BROS.". Please email me with any questions, see my other auctions, and buyer to pay actual shipping (postage only, no handling or packing fee). We also accept paypal, so you can use your credit card if you like. Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045802751">
    <Name>Marvel Grab Bag - Avengers, Iron Man, etc.</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$4.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Los Angeles, CA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:26:34</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:26:34</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="spartacus3131" Rating="28"/>
    <Description>Avengers A nice little mix of comics Avengers X-Men Classics Iron Man Prince Namor _ This a collection of various comics and characters that I never did decide to collect. Hopefully, you may have some holes in your collection that this group can fill. This auction includes the following:_ Prince Namor Limited Series: Issues 1 - 3 (missing issue #4) X-Men classics: Issues 1, 3 (Reprints of earlier classics) Iron Man: Issues 180 - 182 Avengers: Issues 202, 215, 243 - 246 All comics have been stored in plastic sleeves and have been read at least once. You can judge for yourself the overall condition and quality of the issues. Shipping (for Continental U.S.A. locations) has been included in the auction price so this collection has been priced accordingly. What you bid is what you pay!!! All bidders outside the Continental U.S. are welcome, however, shipping will be actual cost. Check out my other auctions! Good deals! Free shipping! Payment Options: PayPal is preferred. I will accept BidPay, Money Orders, and Cashier's Checks. Item will be shipped immediately when using these methods. Personal Checks are accepted but there will be a 10 day delay from the time I receive the check (notifications via e-mail). Click on a picture to enlarge ') //-- Supersize Picture ') //-- Supersize Picture ') //-- Supersize Picture ') //-- Supersize Picture Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item listing for payment instructions.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045803227">
    <Name>Battle chaser prelude in mint condition</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>metairie,la</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:26:00</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:26:00</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dathmaul" Rating="1651"/>
    <Description>This is a copy of the comic titled battle chasers prelude.The book is in mint condition and comes with a bag and board. I accept money orders and paypal.The highest bidder will pay 3.50 for shipping in the u.s. or 4.50 for shipping to canada.You can save alot on shipping if you win multiple auctions of mine so please take the time to check out my other auctions for some more great deals.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045808456">
    <Name>DICKENS VILLAGE VICTORIA STATION W/BOX RET.</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Dickens Village</Category>
    <Currently>$100.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$100.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Grand Haven, Michigan</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:37:18</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:37:18</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dickens_donnie" Rating="0"/>
    <Description>Dept 56 Dickens Village series "VICTORIA STATION" (no. 5574-3) was originally issued in 1989. This piece was designed after Victoria Station in London. It is one of the largest pieces in the collection. The station, box, and sleeve are all in excellent condition. Buyer will pay actual shipping (and insurance if requested by the buyer-we recommend it since we can not be responsible for the piece once it leaves our hands)to be determined at sale. Payment is appreciated in 7 days, auction will be voided if payment is not received within 2 weeks. Money orders and cashiers checks will ship the next day. Personal checks are OK but will delay shipping by 7 business days. We also have the Victoria Station Train Platform that is a wonderful compliment to this piece. HAPPY HOLIDAYS! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Checks and money orders should be sent to Donald Wolffis; 413 Sandpiper; Grand Haven, MI 49417..items will be sent after personal checks clear..money orders will be sent the next day.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045808742">
    <Name>Ice-O-Mat Hand Crank Wall Mount Ice Crusher</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Barware</Category>
    <Category>Other Barware</Category>
    <Currently>$7.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$7.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kamtak" Rating="773">
          <Location>HAPPY HOLIDAYS!!!</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 11:37:19</Time>
        <Amount>$7.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Dinuba, CA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:37:19</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:37:19</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="halford@jps.net" Rating="556"/>
    <Description>This is an Ice - O - Mat ice crusher from the 1940's. It is made of heavy metal with a baked enamel coating for the top and a heavy plastic removable bottom. It comes complete with the wall mounting bracket which allows it to be lifted off for emptying. Just put ice in the top and turn the crank handle clockwise for finely chopped ice or counter clockwise for coarsely chopped ice. The top is hinged and the bottom removes by means of release buttons on the sides. Please email any questions. Thanks for looking. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045811067">
    <Name>Hallmark The Flinstones Keepsake Ornament</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$5.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Colgate, WI</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:41:19</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:41:19</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="boxerbubbles@aol.com" Rating="45"/>
    <Description>This item is a Hallmark ornament. Its from the Keepsake Ornament collection. The title is The Flinstones, Betty and Wilma. This ornament is new, in its original packaging. On the back of the box it says... "Even in the Stone Age, a holiday shopping spree is just the thing for two best friends to enjoy. With the help of their turtle powered cart, Betty and Wilma are sure to find the perfect gifts for their Bedrock friends and family." The price tag on the ornament says $14.95. Please email me with any questions. We accept paypal or money orders. Winning bidder to pay $2.00 for shipping. Insurance is available for $1.10. Thanks for looking. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045811715">
    <Name>SECRET SOCIETY OF SUPER-VILLAINS 6,11-JLA</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Bronze Age (1970-79)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$3.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$3.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Scottsdale, Az</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:42:22</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:42:22</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dash@swlink.net" Rating="1077"/>
    <Description>Here is a great 2 issue lot of a classic anti-hero title from 1970s DC COMICS. Great stuff as the SECRET SOCIETY takes on the JUSTICE LEAGUE OF AMERICA &amp; the JUSTICE SOCIETY OF AMERICA with CAPTAIN COMET leading the charge. Great villains in this including SINESTRO, BLOCKBUSTER, WIZARD, PLANT MASTER, COPPERHEAD, &amp; PROFESSOR ZOOM to name a few. These issues are hard to come by and make for great reading with non-stop action. These are in fine/very fine to very fine condition. Click here to view my other auctions! Good Luck Bidding!! High bidder pays $3.95 S&amp;H. Insurance is an extra $1.10 per $50.00. Checks must clear before shipping. Items paid with money orders sent within 48 hours of receipt. Payment must be received within 10 days of close of auction. Positive feedback will only be left for those paying promptly. Do not bid if you do not intend to pay! (**WINNERS OF MULTIPLE AUCTIONS CAN COMBINE TO SAVE ON SHIPPING**) ******* INTERNATIONAL SHIPPING AVAILABLE !!! ******* Click here to E-Mail Me . Payment may be made with Money Order, Check, or Paypal.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045812494">
    <Name>SON OF SATAN 1</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Bronze Age (1970-79)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$1.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>central pa.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:43:43</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:43:43</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="rpuck1" Rating="422"/>
    <Description>hello. this weekend i will be listing about 125 silver and bronze age books all starting at 1.50, so be sure to check my other auctions and combine to save on shipping. i won't go into the details about each book, just a grade, so assume the book has the properties of this grade. if you have a question or want more details about a book just email me. this book is son of satan 1 in vf cond. shipping 3.50, payment by paypal or money order. all payments due within 14 days after close of auction. if i do not receive the payment within this time, a non-paying bidder alert will be filed followed by negative feedback. shipping to the u.s. only. sorry about the blurry pictures but it's the best i can do for now. thanks for looking and good luck.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045812621">
    <Name>Alley OOP Newspaper Comic Strips 1970</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Newspaper Comics</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Beautiful Sunny CA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:44:03</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:44:03</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="shan29" Rating="966"/>
    <Description>11 different Sunday strips. Each measures 10 x 14"- half page size. All in fine condition, by V.T. Hamlin from 1970. Dates are as follows: 4-26, 8-9, 11-1, 11-8, 11-15, 11-22, 11-29, 12-6, 12-13, 12-20, 12-27. TERMS: United States buyers to pay $3.75 Shipping/Handling charges. Any international buyers, anywhere outside our U.S., will pay extra S/H rates to be determined upon completion of auction. Also insurance is recommended, but always OPTIONAL. I am NOT responsible for any items getting lost or damaged in the mail. Checks and money orders only please. Checks may be held up to 10 days for clearance. I do NOT accept Paypal or Billpoint. Thanks for bidding and please do check out my other auctions! May God bless you!! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045814102">
    <Name>NEW Snow For Your Village FREE SHIPPING</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$1.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Birmingham, AL</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:46:03</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:46:03</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="aly-son" Rating="713"/>
    <Description>This auction is for a brand new 2 oz. bag of iridescent snow, a very nice touch to any village! It is brand new-never out of the package. All litems come from a smoke free home. I prefer paypal but also accept money orders. USE BUY IT NOW AND GET FREE SHIPPING! If not bought with BIN Shipping in a padded envelope is $2.00. Bids start low-you can't go wrong here Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Please send payment via paypal to alyson@visionsix.com (final bid + shipping cost as listed in item description)</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045814261">
    <Name>'79 AVON G.WASHINGTON BUST COLOGNE FULL MIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Avon</Category>
    <Category>Bottles</Category>
    <Currently>$5.15</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.15</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Michiana</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:47:08</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:47:08</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="melwillsell2u" Rating="198"/>
    <Description>Gold colored George Washington Bust cologne never opened and mint in box. Box shows some wear, but George is mint and ready. Comes complete with styrofoam formed packing.Wild Country after shave and sticker still on the bottom. Numbered 40329. Feel free to ask any questions B4 bidding. No Paypal or Billpoint please, Personal Checks, Money Orders, Cashiers Checks are welcome. Shipping will be $5.15 Priority Mail plus INS. If desired. If no INS. is requested, I will not be responsible for items after I mail them. However I do take pride in responsible care and packaging of items. ( See Feedback) Thank You for looking and Good Luck if You decide to bid. International buyers please remember USA funds only and expect to pay actual shipping charges to your Country. Thanks for looking and Good Luck if you decide to bid. Payment should be received within 14 days of auction end, unless prior arrangements made. Non paying bidders will receive negative feedback.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045814355">
    <Name>12NM/MT TITANS COMICS ISSUES#24-#35(NEW SER.)</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$11.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$11.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Colorado Springs, CO</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:46:26</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:46:26</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dimensionxcomics" Rating="620"/>
    <Description>12 NM/MT TITANS COMICS ISSUES #24 THROUGH #35 (NEW SERIES) WOW, USE THE LOW BUY IT NOW PRICE TO GUARENTEE IT'S YOURS! You are bidding on 12 NM/MT TITANS COMICS ISSUES #24 THROUGH #35 (NEW SERIES)....WOW...Good luck! All items will be shipped via USPS Priority Mail. Shipping and Handling charges are $5.95 . Will only ship to United States and Canada. If you are bidding in Canada please email us to inquire about shipping charges. Also note that for shipping to Canada we only accept credit cards, postal money orders, Billpoint, Bidpay, and Paypal. Insurance available at an additional charge. We accept personal checks, money orders, and credit cards through PayPal and Bidpay. We also accept Billpoint. If you have any questions regarding the item(s) or wish to request a picture, feel free to contact us at ed@dimensionxcomics.com . Thanks!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045815184">
    <Name>Vintage Colored Aluminum Water Pitcher</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Other Kitchenware</Category>
    <Currently>$7.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$7.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Lone Star State</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:48:23</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:48:23</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="canyonoaks" Rating="380"/>
    <Description>This is a vintage aluminum water pitcher in the familiar neon yellow/gold/green measuring 7.5" tall with ice lip. Good condition with lots of "character" from years of use but still a real beauty !!! Great addition to your collection !!!!!!!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045815781">
    <Name>Harbour Lights HL256 SEGUIN ISLAND-ME</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Harbour Lights</Category>
    <Currently>$41.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$41.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>RI</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:50:02</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:50:02</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="tonysgifts.com" Rating="627"/>
    <Description>Harbour Lights HL256 SEGUIN ISLAND-ME mint in original box, buyer to pay shipping costs, I also accept PAYPAL. Visit Tony's Gifts and Collectibles today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045816244">
    <Name>White Pig Cookie Jar</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Cookie Jars</Category>
    <Category>Modern (1970-Now)</Category>
    <Currently>$19.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Callahan, Florida</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:51:06</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:51:06</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="jnj@net-magic.net" Rating="24"/>
    <Description>WHITE PIG COOKIE JAR WHITE PIG COOKIE JAR _ _ THIS COOKIE JAR IS BELIEVED TO BE UNMARKED MCCOY._ IT IS WHITE IN COLOR, 8 1/2 INCHES HIGH,_ and 8 1/2 INCHES LONG._ THERE ARE NO CHIPS OR CRACKS and IS IN VERY GOOD TO FINE CONDITION. _ SEE PICTURE Seller reserves right to refuse negative bidders._ Buyer pays actual_ Shipping and Handling. (Item Shipped by Priority Mail w/delivery confirmation and insurance.) ____ Items paid for by Money Order shipped the day that payment is received. Payment Methods Our preferred method of payment is by U.S. Postal Money Order. We accept Certified Funds and Other Money Orders only._ We do not accept checks ._ All Money Orders and Certified funds get same day shipping. Shipping &amp; Handling All of our items are pre-packed before the end of the auction. We use an outside service for packaging, handling, and shipping. They charge us $2.50 per auction for packaging plus actual shipping and insurance charges._ We do not make a profit on shipping._ Multiple auction bidders will receive lower overall shipping charges but must pay the $2.50 per auction packaging cost that we incur._ Seller Responsibility The seller warrants that the description of the item is accurate to the best of our knowledge._ We do allow refunds (less shipping) within 3 days of shipment on items that were accidentally misrepresented._ We will contact the winning bidder within 24 hours after the auction ends.__ Seller reserves the right to sell item to the next highest bidder if no response is received within 72 hours. _ If your payment is not received within 14 days of the auction closing then the item will be either resold or sold to the next highest bidder._ Buyer Responsibility Buyer assumes all responsibility for verifying that the item offered is compatible_ to their system needs._ We do not (any longer) give refunds for failure to know how to make the product work with your system and or needs._ Buyer must respond to e-mail from the Seller within 72 hours of the auction end or be subject to negative feedback. Buyer must send payment in the time frame stated above or will be subject to negative feedback. _ GOOD LUCK I'm always glad to answer questions: JnJ@net-magic.net _ Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See listing for payment instruction, shipping or returns.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045817176">
    <Name>German Shot Glass Heidelberg Nekan</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Barware</Category>
    <Category>Shot Glasses</Category>
    <Currently>$2.25</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$4.30</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$1.75</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>3</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="bronwynread2@aol.com" Rating="1689">
          <Location>Pgh, PA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 21:52:51</Time>
        <Amount>$1.92</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="amaritz" Rating="189">
          <Location>West Midlands</Location>
          <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 01:52:51</Time>
        <Amount>$2.08</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="bama314" Rating="1162">
          <Location>Alabama</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 05:52:51</Time>
        <Amount>$2.25</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Upstate New York</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:52:51</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:52:51</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="mljosey" Rating="82"/>
    <Description>This is a german shot glass with a green stem of Heidelberg Nekan. The glass stands 3" high, no chips or breakage. The Fired on gold is either a bit worn on the side or didn't take in the firing process, looks more like the later. This is a nice piece for anyone who collects shot glasses. Please email me with any questions. Shipping is $2.07 including insurance. Click on a picture to enlarge ') //-- ') //-- Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $0.97 Shipping Insurance per item (required) $1.10 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions I prefer Paypal or money orders.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045818086">
    <Name>Wonder Woman &amp; The Atom Comic 1977-1978</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Bronze Age (1970-79)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$5.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Zanesville Ohio</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:55:01</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:55:01</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="ladysattic777" Rating="385"/>
    <Description>This auction is for a Wonder Woman &amp; The Atom comic book. It is by DC Comics and is Vol 3 #14 December-January 1977-1978. The binding staples have tore the paper a little but the book is still together and in good shape. Winning bidder to pay by either money order, cashier check or paypal $1.50 shipping. NO CASH OR PERSONAL CHECKS! . Will only ship inside the United States. If you have any questions please ask before bidding. PLEASE MAKE SURE YOU WANT THIS ITEM AS ALL SALES ARE FINAL. Thanks for looking and please check my other auctions for more great deals.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045819073">
    <Name>Vintage Hostess Set Corn Brushes Butter Dish</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Other Kitchenware</Category>
    <Currently>$10.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$10.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Eagle Emporium, Eagle, PA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:56:08</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:56:08</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="info@eagle-emporium.com" Rating="991"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://www.eagle-emporium.com/marble2.jpg) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Vintage Hostess Set Corn Brushes Butter Dish Here is a nice boxed set in great condition. It contains 4 plastic handled (corn shaped) brushes with nylon bristles and 4 yellow butter dishes. The dishes are marked - Genuine Coorsite Porcelain. All are in perfect condition. The original box shows somw wear and slight damage. The original instructions are included. This was produced by Silver-Chamberlin Co., Clayton, NJ USA For more information about who we are and the products we offer, please visit our Me page. ABOUT ME! MasterCard Visa Discover AmericanExpress Items which close together can ship together. The shipping and insurance charge for the first auction will be $4.95. Shipping and insurance will be $1.00 for each additional auction shipped. If you have any questions, please email before bidding. Email us!! Contact is expected within three days of the close of the auction. Payment is expected within 10 days. We ship promptly upon receipt of payment by UPS Ground only. Actual address--No P O Boxes PLEASE! Buyer pays S/H/I of $4.95 unless otherwise noted. . Continental US-lower 48 only. Satisfaction guaranteed. We will refund the full purchase price if item is not as represented. Sorry S/H/I not refundable. Click here to see our other listings. PA residents add 6% sales tax or provide a completed tax form with payment. Free counters provided by Honesty.com This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $4.95 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (6.000% if shipped to PA) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions Pay through Ebay payments or pay us directly at https://secure.bee.net/eagle-emporium We accept Visa MasterCard Discover &amp; American Express</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045819439">
    <Name>COPYRIGHT J.S.N.Y. 1974 SALT &amp; PEPPER "H.K."</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Salt, Pepper Shakers</Category>
    <Category>Other Shakers</Category>
    <Currently>$2.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Valley Center</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:56:55</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:56:55</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="frmrbrn" Rating="53"/>
    <Description>YOU ARE BIDDING ON A VERY UNUSUAL COPYRIGHT SALT AND PEPPER SHAKER. THEY ARE PLASTIC. THEY ARE MADE IN HONG KONG.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045819711">
    <Name>Joe Camel- 3=75th. Birthday Thermo-Serv Mugs</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Advertising</Category>
    <Category>Tobacciana</Category>
    <Category>Cigarette</Category>
    <Category>Camel</Category>
    <Currently>$4.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Pacific Northwest</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:58:10</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:58:10</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="station521" Rating="194"/>
    <Description>Joe Camel - 3 Blue 75th Birthday Thermo-Serv Mugs Set of Three Camel 75th. Birthday Thermo-Serv Mugs. Brilliant blue color with picture of Joe Camel "75th Birthday" on front and back. Excellent unused condition dated 1988 RJRTC. Thanks for viewing and Good Luck Bidding! Email us with any questions. All sales Final. Payment Terms: Cashiers check, money order, personal check, Bid Pay and Pay Pal gladly accepted. Items purchased with a personal check will be shipped after check clears, usually 10 days. US Funds Only. Shipping Terms: Buyer pays minimal shipping and handling charges within the United States, plus additional if insurance is requested. All payments must be received within 10 days from close of auction</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045820207">
    <Name>Web of Spiderman 102 Maximum Carnage</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$2.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Morgan Hill, CA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:58:46</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:58:46</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="junkuneed" Rating="100"/>
    <Description>This is a mint Web of Spiderman #102. This is the 6th issue in the Maximum Carnage series with Carnage and Venom. Shipping will be either $3.50 for Priority Mail or $1.50 for media mail depending on which you prefer. Check out my other auctions and save on shipping. Payment can either be a money order, cashiers check or personal check but I will need to wait for a personal check to clear before I can ship. Insurance is extra if desired. Email me if you have any questions. Thanks. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045821287">
    <Name>Dept 56 Snow Village Haunted Mansion</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$137.50</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$225.14</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$0.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>11</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="bases929" Rating="289">
          <Location>Cleveland, Ohio</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 06:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$13.40</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="pubdebar" Rating="497">
          <Location>LOud_ac (22)</Location>
          <Country>France</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 18:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$25.81</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="nsvernon@socket.net" Rating="373">
          <Location>Ulman, MO</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 06:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$38.22</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="yestrecord@aol.com" Rating="4127">
          <Location>VT</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 18:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$50.63</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jeanantoine8" Rating="9">
          <Location>BASTIA</Location>
          <Country>France</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 06:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$63.04</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="sunny6" Rating="301">
          <Location>Clearwater, Florida</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 18:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$75.45</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="made@swbell.net" Rating="274">
          <Location>Dallas, Tx</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 06:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$87.86</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jojodisknee" Rating="2436">
          <Location>Philadelphia, The city that loves you back !</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 18:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$100.27</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ricanpower18" Rating="82">
          <Location>Van Nuys, CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 06:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$112.68</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="efocher" Rating="0">
          <Location>Spokane</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 18:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$125.09</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="millstor@swbell.net" Rating="244">
          <Location>Dallas, Texas USA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-14-01 06:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$137.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Maine</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:00:31</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:00:31</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="flttech" Rating="49"/>
    <Description>Green roof. Straight from a dealers shelf. Sleeve has a few small holes in it (maybe you can see from the picture). Taken out for pictures, inspection, and to check the operation of the electronics. I accept Paypal, Ebay payments, money orders, or personal checks. Checks will have to clear before item ships(usually 7 days from the day I receive it). All other forms of payment will ship immediately. I ship by priority mail unless the buyer wants some other form. Shipping with insurance will be $12 to the lower 48. Other locations will be at actual cost. I will be listing many Dept 56 and Snow Village items this weekend, all starting at 99 cents with no reserve! Take a look and maybe there_s something you can use. Thanks</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045823269">
    <Name>Superman Doomsday Hunter Prey tpb</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Graphic Novels, TPBs</Category>
    <Currently>$7.97</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$7.97</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Omaha NE</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:03:10</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:03:10</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="mbrvd632@cs.com" Rating="735"/>
    <Description>Superman Doomsday Hunter Prey tpb rerpints #1-3 of the mini series by Dan Jurgens. Published in 1995. NM-mint, winner pays $4 s&amp;h ($10 outside the US) good luck!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045823967">
    <Name>HORIZON OF HOPE CLASSIC BASKET SET</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Combos</Category>
    <Currently>$23.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>3</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="psteig" Rating="183">
          <Location>Tyler, TX</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 22:03:29</Time>
        <Amount>$13.83</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="mtbergeron" Rating="351">
          <Location>in a van, down by the river</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 02:03:29</Time>
        <Amount>$18.67</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="sussberg" Rating="1390">
          <Location>Bakersfield, CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 06:03:29</Time>
        <Amount>$23.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>MUSIC CITY, USA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:03:29</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:03:29</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="tnstampco@aol.com" Rating="142"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:18px; color:#FC1230; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#000000; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #000000; } HORIZON OF HOPE CLASSIC BASKET SET Click image to view larger version 2001 CLASSIC HORIZON OF HOPE BASKET SET What a nice gift for a Cancer Survivor. This is a brand new Classic Horizon of Hope set with protector, your choice of Liner--either Pastel Plaid or Botanical Fields, Woodcrafts Lid, and Pewter Hope Tie-On, and Product card are included. This set was only available from the Longaberger Co. during July and August 2001 and is the seventh in a series of Cancer Awarenes Baskets by the Longaberger Co. International Buyers please email me for correct postage amount. Let me know if you want to add insurance. Please email me for correct postage to your country. Please see my other auctions for more jewelry and Retired Longaberger Baskets. Visit my website for waterless cookware and other items to use in your kitchen and additional Retired Longaberger Baskets and accessories. www.allaroundthekitchen.com Payment I accept the following forms of payment: c2it(sm) by Citibank, PayPal, Yahoo! PayDirect, Billpoint, Money Order, Personal Check. Shipping &amp; Handling $7.00 USPS First Class $8.25 USPS Priority Full service auction management with free online payment service: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045826238">
    <Name>OLD BIG BOY SODA BOTTLE - FLORA, IN</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bottles: Modern (1900-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Sodas</Category>
    <Currently>$6.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$6.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jharley78" Rating="81">
          <Location>Syracuse, N.Y.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:06:06</Time>
        <Amount>$6.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Indiana</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:06:06</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:06:06</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="realtiques" Rating="377"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#ffffff; } a.textLink { color: #FFCB00;} } HR { color: #ffffff; } OLD BIG BOY SODA BOTTLE - FLORA, IN Click image to view larger version This 9 ounce clear glass Soda Bottle is embossed with the letter " B " - Vertically " Big Boy " on three sides. Bottom is embossed " Flora, Indiana ". Stands 9 in. tall - Shows case wear and a small chip on top rim. U.S. Shipping is $ 4.95. Indiana residents add 5% for sales tax. Buyer pays cost of shipping and insurance as listed for shipment in US. International shipping will depend on country and location. VISIT NOBLESVILLE ANTIQUE MALL IN NOBLESVILLE, INDIANA - A GENUINE INDIANA ANTIQUE EXPERIENCE! Payment I accept the following forms of payment: Money Order, Personal Check. Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045826392">
    <Name>3 VERY OLD COOKIE CUTTERS</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Cookie Cutters</Category>
    <Currently>$4.30</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.30</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Florida</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:06:36</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:06:36</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="brass109@hotmail.com" Rating="189"/>
    <Description>l am offering you these 3 old cookie cutters.One is a star-shape with green wood handle,one is rond shape with a black wood handle and one is a diamond shape with a red handle.They are in a good condition.l accept:pay-pal,personal cheque or money order.Buyer pays actual shipping cost.Have fun bidding!Thanks. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045829564">
    <Name>HALLMARK 1990 HOME FOR THE OWLIDAYS MIB NR</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$2.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Roswell, GA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:11:19</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:11:19</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="cam_tech" Rating="1544"/>
    <Description>Hallmark Christmas Ornaments New In Box .spanstyle { position:absolute; visibility:visible; top:-50px; font-size:14pt; font-family:Comic Sans MS; font-weight:bold; color:RED; } var x,y var step=20 var flag=0 // Your snappy message. Important: the space at the end of the sentence!!! var message="HAPPY CHRISTMAS! ! " message=message.split("") var xpos=new Array() for (i=0;i =1; i--) { xpos[i]=xpos[i-1]+step ypos[i]=ypos[i-1] } xpos[0]=x+step ypos[0]=y for (i=0; i =1; i--) { xpos[i]=xpos[i-1]+step ypos[i]=ypos[i-1] } xpos[0]=x+step ypos[0]=y for (i=0; i ") document.write(message[i]) document.write(" ") } if (document.layers){ document.captureEvents(Event.MOUSEMOVE); } document.onmousemove = handlerMM; // - End of JavaScript - -- 1990 HOME FOR THE OWLIDAYS This is an ornament from 1990 that is in mint condition. It has been stored in a plastic container, and the box doesn't even have shelf wear. This cute little owl is holding a suitcase that says Home for the Owlidays on it. Winning bidder to pay bid price plus $4.75 USPS Priority Mail which includes Confirmation of Delivery within 7 days of auctions end unless prior notice is given. Insurance is extra, and optional. International shipments will be quoted . Please send your address so I can get your order ready to go at the end of the auction. This will expedite your order. Please see my other auctions to combine for shipping savings... and please read my feedback so you can bid with confidence...glenda Thanks for taking the time to look and HAPPY BIDDING !!! s e mails always welcome glenda Thank you for viewing my auction ! View All Our Auctions , Auctiva Showcase We accept PayPal !</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045829698">
    <Name>Corkscrew - Wood Handle - Italy - Cork Screw</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Barware</Category>
    <Category>Corkscrews</Category>
    <Currently>$1.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>I Love NY!</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:12:24</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:12:24</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="krystl1" Rating="166"/>
    <Description>This is a nice corkscrew from Italy. Says E.B. Italy on handle and Italy on metal "collar". Some rust on metal shaft and washer above collar but corkscrew itself and collar are fine. Measures 5 1/2" long. handle is 3 1/2" across. Nice one if you collect corkscrews! Terms: Winning U.S. bidder pays $3.50 Priority shipping unless other arrangements are made. I will include delivery confirmation at no additional charge. Insurance will be included at my expense for purchases over $10.00. International winners pay their actual shipping. Item shipped within 48 hours upon receipt of Postal money order or use of Pay Pal or when personal check or other payment clears bank. Click here to email me with any questions before bidding! Thank You for looking! Check out my other auctions!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045831574">
    <Name>JW Miniature Apple Basket</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Baskets</Category>
    <Currently>$175.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$175.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Ocala, FL</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:14:58</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:14:58</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="gladdins@aol.com" Rating="1"/>
    <Description>1998 JW Miniature Apple Basket, liner, protector and box. Excellent condition. Smoke free home. Don't miss this opportunity to add this beautiful basket to your collection. Will accept M/C,Visa, CC or money order. Product will be shipped via UPS upon receipt of payment. Shipping fee is 10.00. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045834998">
    <Name>Flowers baby feeder bottle</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bottles: Antique (Pre-1900)</Category>
    <Category>Other Antique Bottles</Category>
    <Currently>$24.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$24.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>FL</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:20:03</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:20:03</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="wizecat" Rating="343"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#FFFFFF; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #ffffff; } Flowers baby feeder bottle Click image to view larger version BUY IT NOW $24.95. WE HAVE HIGHLIGHTED THE EMBOSSING WITH A BLACK FELT PEN BECAUSE I AM SUCH A LOUSY PHOTOGRAPHER!! THIS WILL WASH OFF. This guaranteed original and genuine hand finished Flower's baby feeder bottle is in very good condition with no chips, cracks or other damage. THE BACK IS MARKED IN GRADUATIONS FROM 2-18. This measures 8.0" long. We accept VISA/MASTERCARD. We can be contacted on 1-941-9267944.Winning bidder to pay $6.50 P&amp;H&amp;I. Payment I accept the following forms of payment: Visa/Master Card, Money Order, Personal Check. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045835690">
    <Name>MARVEL COMIC RADIO AD SCRIPT:CAPTAIN AMERICA</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Other Comics</Category>
    <Currently>$3.75</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$3.75</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="journey792" Rating="600">
          <Location>bklyn</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:21:13</Time>
        <Amount>$3.75</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>New York!</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:21:13</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:21:13</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="mr-bones" Rating="1693"/>
    <Description>INTERNATIONAL BIDDERS WELCOME! BID NOW:THIS AUCTION CAN END AT ANY TIME! Hello, Marvel Comics superheroes! This auction is for a comic book store RADIO SCRIPTS booklet. The cover features Avengers leader CAPTAIN AMERICA (with art by DC artist Kevin Maguire). With this radio station ad script kit, Marvel encouraged retailers to create their own co-op advertisements for on-the-air radio broadcasting spots, and these scripts were designed as a fun way for comic books stores to perform and record their radio ads "the Marvel Way". The scripts in this booklet promoted titles such as the Amazing Spider-man, Capt America, the Silver Surfer, Daredevil, the Avengers, Ghost Rider, Conan the Barbarian, the Uncanny X-Men, the Incredible Hulk, the Fantastic Four, etc. This extremely RARE Marvel artifact came out in 1992, and was sent absolutely, strictly, to comic book retail shops to boost sales of trade paperback &amp; graphic novel releases, comic books, etc. This item is in UNUSED NEAR MINT condition. Remember to check out OTHER similar Marvel promos such as this in my other auctions! PLEASE READ TERMS BEFORE BIDDING: Win more than 1 spectacular auction &amp; SAVE ON SHIPPING when items are paid for together. I ship QUICKLY and your items will be packed VERY WELL! (Check my feedback!) USA winners pay $3.50 for postage/handling/insurance. NEW YORK STATE RESIDENTS: Please add the appropriate NYS sales tax for your County for the total amount (high bid plus postage/handling/insurance amount). Canadian winners pay $3.50 for postage/handling/insurance &amp; pay by Paypal, Bidpay, Billpoint, Citybank C2it, or international POSTAL money orders only, payable in US dollars. No checks accepted, unfortunately. All other countries pay $7.50 shipping &amp; handling for airmail shipping. Payment can be made by Paypal, Bidpay, Billpoint, Citybank C2it, or international POSTAL money orders only, payable in US dollars. Sorry, but no checks accepted. Payment to be received within 10 days of auction's end. Thanks very much Super-heroes, and remember to aim your web shooter at my OTHER AUCTIONS! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $3.50 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (8.000% if shipped to NY) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions n/a</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045837317">
    <Name>1964 House of Mystery 143 Martian Manhunter</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Silver Age (1956-69)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$19.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>St. Louis, Mo</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:24:27</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:24:27</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="comic52@aol.com" Rating="833"/>
    <Description>Solid VG copy of House of Mystery No. 143, with first J'Onn J'onzz Manhunter from Mars cover. Nice bright colors. Light overall wear, creasing bottom right corner, diaganoal crease part-way through the cover. Overall, very nice book. Please click View Seller's Other Auctions for more great comics, way below guide price. Winning bidder adds $2.00 for regular U.S. postage or $3.50 for boxed priority mail in the U.S. Missouri winning bidder adds state sales tax. Thank you. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045837812">
    <Name>Keepsake 'North Pole Mr. Potato Head'</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$2.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>hickville</Location>
    <Country>Canada</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:25:27</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-18-01 18:25:27</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="badchefluence" Rating="51"/>
    <Description>This auction is for a mint condition, never out of the package, hallmark keepsake christmas ornament of 'north pole mr. potato head' from christmas 1999. original retail was $14.25. winner will pay fixed shipping of $3.00 in canada and the us, $5.00 everywhere else. i accept well hidden us cash, money orders, and paypal. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045837884">
    <Name>1956 Photo Jack Benny, Frank Sinatra, Fisher</Name>
    <Category>Movies &amp; Television</Category>
    <Category>Memorabilia</Category>
    <Category>Television</Category>
    <Category>Photos</Category>
    <Currently>$9.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Upstate, NY</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:25:09</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:25:09</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="easyseller" Rating="128"/>
    <Description>Auction Wizard 2000 Listing Template - AW2KLOT#:56 1956 Photo Jack Benny, Frank Sinatra, Fisher This neat photo is Stamped on back by the United Press and also was attached an explaination of the photo of Singers Frank Sinatra and Eddie Fisher and Comedian Jack Benny. It is dated 11/10/56 and is Jack Benny outgoing, installing Frank Sinatra as the new Abbot of the Friar Organization. Great Photo! We prefer paypay, but also accept checks and money orders. Payment must be received within 10 days of auction end. USA (48 States) buyers to pay $2.00 for shipping. Auction Wizard 2000 - The Complete Auction Management Software Solution Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045837917">
    <Name>Dept 56 Snow Village Two for the Road</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$6.75</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$9.73</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$0.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>4</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="all-tied-up" Rating="214">
          <Location>Omaha, Nebraska</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 18:25:21</Time>
        <Amount>$2.43</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="cr1972" Rating="4">
          <Location>Barrington,RI</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 18:25:21</Time>
        <Amount>$3.87</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="showbizkids" Rating="1517">
          <Location>Northern California</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 18:25:21</Time>
        <Amount>$5.31</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="funkymums" Rating="406">
          <Location>Funky Cheshire</Location>
          <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 18:25:21</Time>
        <Amount>$6.75</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Maine</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:25:21</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:25:21</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="flttech" Rating="49"/>
    <Description>This is a new item only taken out for inspection and pictures. I accept Paypal, Ebay payments, money orders, or personal checks. Checks will have to clear before item ships(usually 7 days from the day I receive it). All other forms of payment will ship immediately. I ship by priority mail unless the buyer wants some other form. Shipping with insurance will be $5 to the lower 48. All other locations at actual cost. I will be listing many Dept 56 and Snow Village items this weekend, all starting at 99 cents with no reserve! Take a look and maybe there_s something you can use. Thanks</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045838416">
    <Name>10-ASSORTED BATMAN COMIC BOOKS-AWESOME!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Collections</Category>
    <Currently>$4.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>PA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:26:08</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:26:08</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="littlegiant2" Rating="5223"/>
    <Description>YOU ARE BIDDING ON A LOT OF 10 ASSORTED BATMAN COMIC BOOKS.GREAT STARTER COLLECTION OR EVEN JUST TO ADD TO YOUR COLLECTION OF COMICS.THESE ARE FROM A COLLECTION OF OVER 500,000 COMIC BOOKS AND WILL BE RANDOMLY PACKED AT TIME OF DELIVERY.AS AN ADDED BONUS EACH COMIC WILL COME IN A PROTECTIVE COMIC BOOK PLASTIC BAG WITH BACKING BOARDS FOR SAFE VIEWING OR STORAGE..BUYER PAYS SHIPPING AND HANDLING COST OF $4.95.PAYMENT MAY BE CASH,CHECK,CASHIER'S CHECK,MONEY ORDER OR PAYPAL.ITEMS PAID FOR WITH A CHECK ARE HELD 10 DAYS TO ASSURE CHECK CLEARANCE.PAYMENT MUST BE RECEIVED WITHIN 10 DAYS OF AUCTION END.BUYER MUST CONTACT US WITHIN 3 DAYS OF AUCTION END.CHECK OUT OUR OTHER AUCTIONS @ LITTLEGIANT2</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045839142">
    <Name>2001 HEARTLAND BAKERY</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Baskets</Category>
    <Currently>$20.51</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$3.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>9</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="captwhiz" Rating="1054">
          <Location>NJ,USA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 08:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$4.95</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="rpbrown@oz.net" Rating="3291">
          <Location>Bellevue, WA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 22:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$6.89</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="luvmychin" Rating="132">
          <Location>Ville Platte, Louisiana</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$8.84</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="mickerde" Rating="127">
          <Location>paypal preferred</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 02:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$10.78</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="fireworksnc" Rating="220">
          <Location>Yanceyville,NC</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 16:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$12.73</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="glennstq" Rating="176">
          <Location>California,Mo.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 06:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$14.67</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="stuffrus2000" Rating="522">
          <Location>66018</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 20:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$16.62</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="num1inmem" Rating="199">
          <Location>Chicago</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 10:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$18.56</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="basketcaseco" Rating="87">
          <Location>IOWA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-14-01 00:28:17</Time>
        <Amount>$20.51</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>LITTLE HEISKEL</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:28:17</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:28:17</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="heartsonfire" Rating="0"/>
    <Description>SAME SIZE AS BREAD,WITH LEATHER LOOP HANDLES AND BLUE/GREEN SHOESTRING WEAVE. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $6.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions WILL TAKE 10 DAYS FOR PERSONAL CHECKS TO CLEAR.OTHERWISE I WILL SHIP RIGHT AWAY.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045840369">
    <Name>X-Men 215 1987 vfn</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$1.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Utica, N.Y.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:30:22</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:30:22</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="leonhare" Rating="866"/>
    <Description>Basic S&amp;H $3.00. 1-5 comics. S&amp;H $3.50. 6-10 comics. Send payment to Leon Hare P.O. Box 4833 Utica, N.Y. 13504-4833.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045840994">
    <Name>SHAZAM #1 2/73 CGC NM 9.4!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Bronze Age (1970-79)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$58.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>6</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="video-town" Rating="1637">
          <Location>Addison, IL</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 13:10:33</Time>
        <Amount>$17.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="meaganjoe" Rating="573">
          <Location>~We accept Paypal and Billpoint~</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 07:50:33</Time>
        <Amount>$25.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="catocrew" Rating="0">
          <Location>Albuquerque,New Mexico</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 02:30:33</Time>
        <Amount>$34.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="spock104@aol.com" Rating="98">
          <Location>Chattanooga</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 21:10:33</Time>
        <Amount>$42.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="garagepunk65@yahoo.com" Rating="327">
          <Location>SANTA ANA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 15:50:33</Time>
        <Amount>$50.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="internationalcomicbookco" Rating="370">
          <Location>Brandon, Manitoba</Location>
          <Country>Canada</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 10:30:33</Time>
        <Amount>$58.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>LOWER HUDSON VALLEY, NEW YORK</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:30:33</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:30:33</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="mrmystery48" Rating="644"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#FFFFFF; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #ffffff; } SHAZAM #1 2/73 CGC NM 9.4! Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version D.C.COMICS,2/73. GRADED A NM 9.4 BY THE TOUGH GRADERS AT CGC. THEY ALSO NOTED WHITE PAGES. THIS IS AN IMPORTANT BOOK WHICH IS STARTING TO BE RECOGNIZED FOR WHAT IT IS BY COLLECTORS. THIS IS THE FIRST REVIVAL OF CAPT.MARVEL SINCE THE GOLDEN AGE. C.C.BECK COVER AND ART. ESCALATING IN VALUE AND TILL CHEAP IN THE GUIDE. GORGEOUS BOOK IN NM CONDITION. ADD $5.00 FOR PRIORITY MAIL SHIPPING. FOREIGN ORDERS WILL BE ACTUAL COST TO SEND. INSURANCE IF DESIRED IS EXTRA. I GUARANTEE EVERYTHING I SELL SO BID WITH CONFIDENCE. Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Money Order, Personal Check. Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045841067">
    <Name>SUB-MARINER 21,22,23,24,25,26 (1970) FN+/ VFN</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Bronze Age (1970-79)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$5.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="vfast" Rating="65">
          <Location>Connecticut</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:31:38</Time>
        <Amount>$5.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>AUSTIN, TEXAS</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:31:38</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:31:38</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="jaims" Rating="164"/>
    <Description>SUB-MARINER 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26 Marvel's Sub-Mariner books. All six books from the first 6 months of 1970 and bidding starts at less than a buck apiece! All books are 15 centers. Sorry about the bad photo. Books are in fantastic shape. These books still have glossy covers. Very small defects. Some spine strss and corner wear. I would grade these books Fine+ to Very Fine. There is a small chip missing from the back cove of issue 26. Interior pages are off-white to cream. Little bit of tanning on some of the back covers. Bags and boards not included. If you want bags and board, add 15 cents per book. Add $5.20 for shipping costs (priority mail). If you want to save a little money, I'll ship the book regular mail for $3.25 postage. Buyer to prepay with M.O. or check. (Checks may delay shipment by 7-10 days to clear bank.) Check out my other auctions. Buy more to save on postage. I've got more Subbys on sale so buy them all and get a good run. Hey, thanks for looking!! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045841432">
    <Name>Victorian Trade Card #3 Geo.C. Newman, Phila.</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Autographs, Paper &amp; Writing</Category>
    <Category>Paper</Category>
    <Category>Ephemera</Category>
    <Currently>$4.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Desert Boomtown!</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:31:18</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:31:18</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="theheatgoeson" Rating="526"/>
    <Description>Brilliant color litho Victorian card advertising GEO. C. NEWMAN store, 806 Market St., Philadelphia. "Mirrors, Pictures, Frames and Works of Art." Measures 4 7/8 by 3 1/8 ins. Gorgeous image of bonneted young girl leaning on a tree branch. Slight crease lower right corner, minor tear bottom center. This is one of four different Newman cards listed. PLEASE DO NOT USE THE eBAY CHECKOUT PROCEDURE--IT CREATES DUPLICATE E-MAIL EXCHANGES. WE WILL NOTIFY YOU WITH COMPLETE INFORMATION IF YOU ARE THE WINNING BIDDER. We accept payment by MasterCard and Visa through PayPal, and ship immediately on notification. We welcome and recommend money orders or cashier's checks, and we ship within 24 hours of receiving payment. We also welcome BidPay money orders. A personal or business check may wait to clear. Winning bidder will be notified of actual shipping, handling and insurance costs. Please view our other auction listings. Thanks for your interest, and good luck bidding! Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Money Order, Personal Check. Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045842209">
    <Name>Superman 1942 Sunday Comic Nazi Strip Framed</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Original Comic Art</Category>
    <Category>Other Original Art</Category>
    <Currently>$59.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$183.13</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$59.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>South Eastern United States</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:33:10</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:33:10</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="jean.valjean" Rating="1341"/>
    <Description>Please click on the below link to view all my eBay auctions! www.BidPay.com This original 1942 Sunday Comic Strip features Superman capturing Nazi saboteurs! Of particular interest is the Daily Planet newspaper panel (panel 6 in the scan below) that features the by-line of Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster, where they note that real American Heroes at the U.S. Army Quartermaster Corps at Holibard, Maryland are doing a great job. The strip ends with the classic Lois-tells-Clark-he-missed-Superman-again plot devise. Strip is professionally framed and matted, measuring 13 inches by 18 inches, is in mint condition, and will be shipped with the utmost care. Please note, this is an actual, original Sunday comic strip from 1942. It is not a litho, laser copy, or print but an actual 59 year old comic strip! Buyer pays $6.95 shipping in the United States, international bidders please contact me. I welcome any questions you may have. NO RESERVE! Please feel free to view my other auctions and to check out my eBay AboutMe page. Thanks! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Visit Empire Enterprises today! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $6.95 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.20 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions Please see my eBay AboutMe page. Thanks!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045843581">
    <Name>INCREDIBLE HULK 103 &amp; 104 RHINO APP NR</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Silver Age (1956-69)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="mcnerd44" Rating="881">
          <Location>Cerritos, CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:35:27</Time>
        <Amount>$9.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Toronto, Ontario</Location>
    <Country>Canada</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:35:27</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:35:27</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="strangeworlds" Rating="252"/>
    <Description>STRANGE WORLDS PRESENTS _ The Incredible Hulk #103 &amp; 104 Marvel Comics May, June 1968 Two early issues, one featuring the Rhino, take a look at my other listings for other Hulk issues that are currently up for auction. This is a NO RESERVE auction so whoever places the high bid always wins! Don't miss out! Check out MY OTHER AUCTIONS for more great Silver and Bronze Age items. GRADE: #103 - GVG; #104 - FVF A scan of the one of the items is below. If you would like a detailed description and/or a scan of this or any other item I have up for auction please e-mail me your request. All books are graded according to Overstreet standards. Books may contain unlisted flaws typical of grade. So the grade we assigned will take into account all positive and negative factors of the condition of the book. Consult your copy of the Overstreet Comic Book Grading Guide. Please take the time to check out our other auctions and book mark them as we are continuously adding new items. Bid with confidence from a seller who has maintained an excellent feedback and has been in the business for over 25 years buying and selling comics with many satisfied customers. We will gladly combine orders from our other auctions to save you on shipping. TERMS: WINNING BIDDER TO PAY FOR SHIPPING AND HANDLING, INSURANCE IS OPTIONAL AND EXTRA. PAYMENT TO BE RECEIVED WITHIN 10 DAYS AFTER NOTIFICATION, ITEM SHIPPED NEXT DAY . ONCE THE ITEM IS IN THE HANDS OF THE POSTAL SERVICE WE NO LONGER ASSUME ANY RESPONSIBILTY. NOTE IF SENDING A POSTAL MONEY ORDER PLEASE ENSURE THAT IT IS AN ORANGE INTERNATIONAL U.S. POSTAL MONEY ORDER AND NOT THE GREEN U.S. POSTAL MONEY ORDER AS THESE ARE ONLY NEGOTIABLE THE U.S. AND POSSESSIONS . _</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045844320">
    <Name>Tupperware Quick Shake Container</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Tupperware</Category>
    <Category>Contemporary (1970-Now)</Category>
    <Currently>$3.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$3.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Wonderful Sunny North Texas</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:36:14</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:36:14</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="pfaubion" Rating="398"/>
    <Description>This auction is for a mixing/blending container by Tupperware. Dressings, drinks, pancakes mixes, and marinades are yours in a shake, thanks to a removable blending insert. It has standard measurements on one side and metric ones on the other. The 2-cup capacity container stands 8_ high and 4 1/8_ in diameter. It is in excellent condition. Please see the picture below for more details. Buyer pays actual shipping costs. International shipping will be based on the destination location. We accept VISA and MasterCard through PayPal. We also take BidPay, Discover, American Express, and money orders/cashier checks. Personal checks will be accepted but items will not be shipped for 15 days after receipt of check. Payment must be received within ten days from end of auction. We DO NOT use the checkout feature. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045846149">
    <Name>Department 56 Dickens Village City Workers</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Dickens Village</Category>
    <Currently>$24.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$24.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Katrina's Collections</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:39:38</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:39:38</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="katrina7" Rating="1704"/>
    <Description>Department 56 ~City Workers~ Dickens Village Series Item No: 59676 Issue Date: 1987 Retired Date: 1988 Set of 4 Description This item is in its original box with sleeve and is in excellent condition. Please note that all boxes and sleeves are in excellent condition unless otherwise stated. Also, if applicable, all light cords, trees, road etc. are included unless otherwise stated. All pictures are the property of www.katrinascollections.com and may not be used or copied without prior permission. Shipping High bidder to pay 6.00 shipping, handling and insurance in the US only. Insurance is included in the shipping price and is not optional. Please check my other auctions for more great deals on Department 56 merchandise. If you are the high bidder on more than one auction, we will be happy to save you some money on shipping costs by combining your purchases into one shipment. Other Fees Pennsylvania residents must add 6% to the final bid price for sales tax. Methods of Payment We accept: **Visa ** Mastercard **PayPal **Billpoint **Cashiers checks **Money orders **Personal checks are welcome but I do delay shipping 7 days. All other forms of payment will ship within 2 business days of receipt. We do not ship on Saturday or Sunday. **Sorry, no CODs. ** If you do not have a PayPal or Billpoint account and still wish to use Visa or Mastercard, I am able to accept Visa/MC directly. Terms Payment must be received within 10 days of my notification or the item will be relisted and the high bidder will be reported to ebay as a non-paying bidder. If you are the high bidder on multiple auctions, please email me for a total amount due including combined shipping before making any online payments. If you have any questions, please email me before bidding! Thanks for looking! Click below to... View My Other Auctions Email Me! Katrina's Collections 302 National Pike East Brownsville, PA 15417 www.katrinascollections.com</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045846223">
    <Name>MARVEL HEROES # 1 DF SIGNED 1ST PRINT COA</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$60.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$24.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>3</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="nutting" Rating="680">
          <Location>San Francisco</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 22:39:36</Time>
        <Amount>$36.66</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ame_0120@yahoo.com" Rating="2794">
          <Location>CHECK OUT OUR OTHER AUCTIONS</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 02:39:36</Time>
        <Amount>$48.33</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="tocon" Rating="1505">
          <Location>PA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 06:39:36</Time>
        <Amount>$60.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>MY CLOSET</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:39:36</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:39:36</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="silverage59" Rating="500"/>
    <Description>THIS AUCTION IS FOR THE DF SIGNED VERSION OF HEROES # 1. IT IS ALSO THE 1ST PRINTING OF THE BOOK AND IS SIGNED BY NEAL ADAMS, ADAM KUBERT, JAE LEE, JOE QUESADA, TOM PALMER, AND EVEN EVAN DORKIN OF "MILK &amp; CHEESE" FAME. QUITE A MOVING TRIBUTE, AS THERE ARE PAGES IN THE BOOK THAT BROUGHT TEARS TO MY EYES AND IS DEFINITELY WORTHY OF SETTING BACK TO GIVE TO YOUR GRANDKIDS. THIS IS # 2030 OF 3000 AND IS STILL SEALED AND COMES WITH CERTICATE OF AUTHENTICITY. THIS IS A NO RESERVE AUCTION! Payment- Paypal(which allows you to pay with Visa/Mastercard) or Money Order. Personal checks will be accepted if feedback is above 100 and you don't have a bunch of negatives. Shipping- $5.00 for USPS Priority Box w/delivery confirmation or $5.50 Airmail to Canada. Please note that I do not ship bookrate. Strict grader, lightning fast shipping,checkout my feedback for the evidence and bid with confidence! THANKS FOR LOOKING!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045846537">
    <Name>Precious Moments - He Leadeth Me</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="sloman2l" Rating="2">
          <Location>Somerset, NJ</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:40:36</Time>
        <Amount>$9.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Wauwatosa</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:40:36</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:40:36</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="waltera317a" Rating="69"/>
    <Description>This darling little shepherd boy is leading his sheep. He is in mint condition and comes with the original box. Winning bidder to pay $6.00 shipping. I accept paypal, billpoint, money orders and checks. (must clear)Thanks for looking, and good luck. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045848321">
    <Name>Hallmark - FOOTBALL LEGENDS - Joe Namath NIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Series Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$8.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$8.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Lake Charles, LA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:42:48</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-18-01 18:42:48</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="gildlily" Rating="267"/>
    <Description>Handcrafted and is the 3rd in the Football Legends Series. Also has a Scoreboard trading card enclosed. Paypal is okay but not credit cards. Buyer pays actual postage. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Carolyn at cardgif@aol.com will contact you after the auction is complete. It may take her a few days.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045848891">
    <Name>PRECIOUS MOMENTS 111066W MUSICAL 1994</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>GOD BLESS AMERICA!!</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:43:46</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:43:46</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="tarootaz" Rating="24"/>
    <Description>PRECIOUS MOMENTS MUSICAL # 111066W DATED 1994 " May Your Christmas Be a Happy Home " Tune: " Home for the Holidays " _ This Precious Moments Musical Porcelain Figurine is titled " May Your Christmas Be a Happy Home " and plays the tune " Home for the Holidays ". This unusual Precious Moments figurine has the number #111066W on a separate label on the back and is dated 1994. It has the usual trademark on the bottom and reads "The Enesco Precious Moments Collection". I haven't been able to find any other information on it. This Christmas figurine is the home of a Precious Moment's family. The front is beautifully stencilled with a charming scene of the father reading a book to his family at Christmas time. This musical figurine is in perfect condition! (no box). There is a wind up key for the music, and it also has an on/off lever! It is 5 3/4" high and the about 5" wide. *** I have other Precious Moments Musical Porcelain Figures up for auction so please check out my auctions as I will combine shipping! *** Payment and Shipping Terms: Buyer pays actual shipping and delivery confirmation. Insurance is additional. You may pay with personal check, money order, Paypal or Billpoint. Personal checks must clear before item is shipped (item held for 7 to 10 day after check received for check to clear). Payment is due within 10 days following the close of auction. I ship within 2 business days following receipt of payment. Seller assumes no responsibility for uninsured items or items lost in the mail. If you have any questions please feel free to e-mail me . Thanks for stopping by and be sure to check out my other auctions ! (combine auctions to save on shipping costs)</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045853944">
    <Name>Avon Roadster Car Bottle Collection</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Avon</Category>
    <Category>Bottles</Category>
    <Currently>$1.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>East Central IL</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:51:45</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:51:45</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="cmickel" Rating="1178"/>
    <Description>Avon Roadster Car Bottle Collection Description Here are 4 Avon car bottles. One is a gold Packard Roadster. It is 6" in length. Another is a great looking white and red Thomas Flyer 1908 car bottle. It is 7" in length. The next one is in its own box, a Haynes-Apperson 1902 vehicle in light green glass and is about 5 _" in length. The last is a black and red Electric Charger that is about 5" in length. All are in very good condition. Payment &amp; Shipping Information Shipping Cost: Shipping Method: $6.45 Priority Accepted Payment: PayPal ,_Money Order/Cashiers Check,_Personal Check_</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045854027">
    <Name>Vintage Wicker Poodle Box Purse</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Flue Covers</Category>
    <Currently>$14.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$14.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="priceizright" Rating="930">
          <Location>Manchester, New Hampshire</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:51:57</Time>
        <Amount>$14.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Connecticut</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:51:57</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:51:57</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="annie2bq@aol.com" Rating="3578"/>
    <Description>Vintage wicker purse, velvet and chenille poodle on top with a miniature pair of binoculars and horse racing form and programs, 6 1/2" x 7 1/2" x 4 1/2", the wicker covering on the handle has slid down on one side and there is a spot where one of the little paper forms must have come off the top of the purse because there is a spot of glue with nothing on it, otherwise very good condition, buyer to pay postage by priority mail Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045854831">
    <Name>1985 Hallmark * KATYBETH * ornament LIGHTED</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$5.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="chocolatewar" Rating="300">
          <Location>hk</Location>
          <Country>China</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 00:53:25</Time>
        <Amount>$5.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Oklahoma</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:53:25</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 18:53:25</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="cwacollectibles@aol.com" Rating="1706"/>
    <Description>Up for bids is the 1985 Hallmark "KATYBETH" LIGHTED ornament. KATYBETH SITS ON A RAINBOW THAT WILL LIGHT UP WITH COLORS when you plug the provided connector cord into your tree lights. See photo below. Ornament is MINT. Box has a little wear with price tag intact. Add to your collection today. Shipping to be 4.00 and we will gladly combine with any of our other auctions to save you on shipping costs. We accept PAYPAL, Money Order or personal checks. NO HOLD on personal checks with good feedback. Please see our other auctions for LOTS of GREAT ornaments at EXCELLENT prices. Shop NOW for Christmas! We ALWAYS email our customers promptly after the auction ends. We pack your treasures SECURELY and ship IMMEDIATELY via priority mail. Thanks for viewing our auctions and happy bidding.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045855296">
    <Name>Precious Moments - Noah's Ark</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$5.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Wauwatosa</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:54:03</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:54:03</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="waltera317a" Rating="69"/>
    <Description>This is a precious moments Noah's Ark Nightlight. It has the number of #346594 and is so cute. It is in mint conditon and comes in the original box. Would be adorable in a child's room. Winning bidder to pay $3.95 shipping. I accept paypal, billpoint, money orders and checks (must clear). Thanks for looking Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045857524">
    <Name>TOMB RAIDER ORIGINAL ART MUSEUM EDITION #5</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Original Comic Art</Category>
    <Category>Drawings, Sketches</Category>
    <Currently>$351.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>9</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="dragonbreathxx" Rating="734">
          <Location>Westfield,NC</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 08:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$47.88</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="uhs2000" Rating="507">
          <Location>new jersey</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 22:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$85.77</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="strczk" Rating="97">
          <Location>Home of the Blues Brothers, IL</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$123.66</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="youngseabox@aol.com" Rating="1287">
          <Location>Home of Rock n Roll and The Blues!!!</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 02:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$161.55</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="crittercrossing" Rating="63">
          <Location>INDY</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 16:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$199.44</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="cdbrazil" Rating="86">
          <Location>AIR MAIL SHIPPING WORLDWIDE!</Location>
          <Country>Brazil</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 06:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$237.33</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="lynnarie" Rating="544">
          <Location>northwest Mississippi</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 20:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$275.22</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="radr2" Rating="126">
          <Location>Near Knoxville TN</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 10:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$313.11</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="gr8giftsonline" Rating="236">
          <Location>East Tennessee</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-14-01 00:57:03</Time>
        <Amount>$351.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>California</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:57:03</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:57:03</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="fedman98" Rating="467"/>
    <Description>_ BUY-IT NOW INCLUDES SHIPPING/INSURANCE. Up for auction is a very rare Michael Turner Tomb Raider Original Art Museum Edition hand signed by Michael Turner. Mint condition. Michael Turner did a total of 10 Tomb Raider original art pieces with an original and unique hand drawn art of Tomb Raider. This one is number 5 of only 10. Art measures approx. 5" x 7". Comes sealed and with signed COA from Jay Company. Any other questions, feel free to email. Checks take 7 days to clear. International orders MUST pay by Paypal only. US Priority Shipping is $4.50 for priority mail anywhere in the U.S. Insurance is extra and I am not responsible for damaged items that are not insured. International air shipping pay $12.00 shipped in a box for safe shipping. HIGH BIDDER MUST PAY WITHIN 7 DAYS OR YOU LOSE AUCTION. BILLPOINT, PAYPAL, CHECK OR MONEY ORDER ACCEPTED. Payments must be recieved within 10 days after auction ends or item goes to next highest bidder and negative feedback will be left. Personal checks must clear. Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Money Order, Personal Check. _ Click image to view larger version _ Click image to view larger version _ Click image to view larger version _ Click image to view larger version _ Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045857782">
    <Name>Byers Choice 1992 LIL DICKENS Red Suit</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Byers Choice</Category>
    <Currently>$5.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="rompinmopr@aol.com" Rating="738">
          <Location>Maryland</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:57:26</Time>
        <Amount>$5.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Reno, NV</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:57:26</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:57:26</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bought2much" Rating="680"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://members.aol.com/bought2much/Snow.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Byers Choice 1992 LIL DICKENS Red Suit Here's a Byers Choice 1992 LIL DICKENS Toddler, dressed in a red snowsuit, with plaid scarf, holding a gift in his hands. He's is in mint condition, and comes to you from my non-smoking home. I have many Byers Choice carolers to sell during the next few weeks, so please check my listings often. Buyer to add $6 for USPS Priority Mail shipping. Please see my other listings, as I am always happy to reduce shipping costs on combined wins NO RESERVE! Bid freely. Payment is due within 10 days of auction close. I accept PayPal or money orders. I no longer accept personal checks unless Buyer's feedback rating is above 50+. Click HERE to see my other listings and SAVE on shipping costs.. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045858344">
    <Name>ENESCO BLUE DRESS MUSICAL ANGEL FIGURINE</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Other Enesco Items</Category>
    <Currently>$1.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Oklahoma</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 18:58:09</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 18:58:09</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="cjbchillie" Rating="426"/>
    <Description>ENESCO BLUE DRESS MUSICAL ANGEL FIGURINE This is an Enesco musical angel figurine dressed in blue. She is designed by Giftware. She is new but does not have a box. Thanks for looking and check out my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $5.00 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.10 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions Please send to: Chillie Bills PO Box 217 Lehigh, Ok. 74556 I'm not responsible for uninsured items.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045861321">
    <Name>GUARDIAN OVAL COOKING OR SERVING TRAY</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Metalware</Category>
    <Category>Aluminum</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Florida</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:01:49</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:01:49</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="trigold" Rating="72"/>
    <Description>New Page 1 GUARDIAN OVAL COOKING OR SERVING TRAY._ Guardian oval Tray 15 inches long, includes handles and 10 inches wide. Smooth bottom, like new._ In clean and shiny condition, has a hammered finish on the inside, the same as the outside. Ideal for oven use, serving tray, cook-and-serve or display piece._ Makes a great addition to a "Guardian Cookware" collection. Buyer pays actual shipping to their destination.... Payment method: www.billpoint.com ~ www.paypal.com ~ www.bidpay.com ~ Money Order ~ Electronic check ~ Personal check ~ Bank Draft/Cashiers Check_</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045862688">
    <Name>MEMORIES OF YESTERDAY "CAN I KEEP HER MOMMY"</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Memories of Yesterday</Category>
    <Currently>$3.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$3.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Idaho</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:03:11</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:03:11</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="geodehound" Rating="788"/>
    <Description>.titledata {font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:18px; color:#000000; font-weight : bold;} .description {font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#000000;} .link {font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline;} HR { color: #000000; } MEMORIES OF YESTERDAY "CAN I KEEP HER MOMMY" MABEL LUCIE ATTWELL - " CAN I KEEP HER,MOMMY?" DATED 1996 - Enesco #527025 - APPROX. 3 1/2 Inches Tall - PORCELAIN ORNAMENT - COMPLETE WITH TAG, AND BOOKLET. A Very Fine Collectible. Please E-Mail with any questions. Thank-you and Good Luck! Items are shipped uninsured unless asked for to be insurance. Insurance 1.10 needs to be added to s/h to Ins. up to $50.00. PayPal account will be sent to address from PayPal. All auctions winners will recive a winning bid notice most time in 1 hour. Just fill it out and it will have all information of the item and how much shipping is. If 2 or more items s/h will be Divvied among the items equally on each winning bid notice. Adding the combined total on each winning bid notice will give total charge in one box. You will be sent a notice as soon as we ship your auction item from time of payment. Auction will be paid for in 10 days from close or item will be relisted and feedback will be left. To see all of my other auctions. Please visit our e-store: WWW.GEODEHOUND.COM IDAHO RESIDENTS MUST PAY 5% SALES TAX Bulk listing tools, image hosting, auction management and more: AuctionWatch Free counters provided by Honesty.com . Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Money Order, Personal Check, CASH. Shipping &amp; Handling $4.45 USPS Priority Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045863548">
    <Name>Byers Choice 1994 CONSTABLE *1st year*</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Byers Choice</Category>
    <Currently>$36.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>15</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="doboy" Rating="1195">
          <Location>Cook County IL</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 04:24:09</Time>
        <Amount>$11.72</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="marybeth303" Rating="1298">
          <Location>West Michigan</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 13:44:09</Time>
        <Amount>$13.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="cmsteen@prodigy.net" Rating="669">
          <Location>MIAMI, FL</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 23:04:09</Time>
        <Amount>$15.26</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="mandybone" Rating="120">
          <Location>tn</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 08:24:09</Time>
        <Amount>$17.03</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="rp125" Rating="475">
          <Location>WOLCOTT, IN.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 17:44:09</Time>
        <Amount>$18.80</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jshaffer@toolcity.net" Rating="3708">
          <Location>Venango, PA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 03:04:09</Time>
        <Amount>$20.57</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="mommyforlife2017" Rating="97">
          <Location>The Sunshine State</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 12:24:09</Time>
        <Amount>$22.34</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="maxx2221" Rating="237">
          <Location>Amherst, MA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 21:44:09</Time>
        <Amount>$24.11</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="doubled.sr" Rating="1481">
          <Location>Chicago</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 07:04:09</Time>
        <Amount>$25.88</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="99walker" Rating="825">
          <Location>ALS AUCTION EVERETT WA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 16:24:09</Time>
        <Amount>$27.65</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="bluerock@cstone.net" Rating="287">
          <Location>Beautiful Virginia</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 01:44:09</Time>
        <Amount>$29.42</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="pamkaplan@aol.com" Rating="879">
          <Location>Gold Paw Country</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 11:04:09</Time>
        <Amount>$31.19</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="shipitfast" Rating="119">
          <Location>Western</Location>
          <Country>Canada</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 20:24:09</Time>
        <Amount>$32.96</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="gypsytraders" Rating="461">
          <Location>Sunny S. CA Desert</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-14-01 05:44:09</Time>
        <Amount>$34.73</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="frannancy" Rating="1987">
          <Location>New York</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-14-01 15:04:09</Time>
        <Amount>$36.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Reno, NV</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:04:09</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:04:09</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bought2much" Rating="680"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://members.aol.com/bought2much/Snow.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Byers Choice 1994 CONSTABLE *1st year* The Byers Choice CONSTABLE was only produced from 1994-1996; this one is from the first year of production - 1994. He's dressed in his navy blue "bobby" uniform, with cap, nightstick, and whistle. He looks very stern, but is actually holding a Christmas gift behind his back. He's is in mint condition, and comes to you from my non-smoking home. I have many Byers Choice carolers to sell during the next few weeks, so please check my listings often. Buyer to add $8 for USPS Priority Mail shipping. Please see my other listings, as I am always happy to reduce shipping costs on combined wins NO RESERVE! Bid freely. Payment is due within 10 days of auction close. I accept PayPal or money orders. I no longer accept personal checks unless Buyer's feedback rating is above 50+. Click HERE to see my other listings and SAVE on shipping costs.. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045866029">
    <Name>Norman Rockwell Glasses &amp; Mugs</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Other Kitchenware</Category>
    <Currently>$5.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="familyjohnson" Rating="0">
          <Location>Highlands Ranch, Colorado</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:08:27</Time>
        <Amount>$5.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>The WB of Ohio</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:08:27</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:08:27</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="vampyrevixon" Rating="77"/>
    <Description>You are bidding on 4 Norman Rockwell Glasses and 4 Norman Rockwell Mugs. Picture as sown below. Same condition as shown below. Great for a collection, or extra dishes around the house. Email me with questions. Auction is for US citizens only...which means I only ship to US as well! Buyer pays shipping which is 3.95. Will ship in time for christmas. All items go out priority mail! I ONLY ACCEPT MONEY ORDERS!!!! Good Luck and happy bidding! Click on a picture to enlarge ') //-- ') //-- Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $3.95 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.10 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions Please send payment to address given. I will ship in time for christmas. If you email me within 1 day of auction, and i receive your payment within 4 days of auctions end, I will send the shipping costs back to you! Thanx for Bidding!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045866045">
    <Name>ASSORTMENT OF 11 COOKIE AND BISCUIT CUTTERS</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Cookie Cutters</Category>
    <Currently>$5.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="cgorham101@aol.com" Rating="642">
          <Location>Gadsden, Alabama</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:08:30</Time>
        <Amount>$5.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>USA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:08:30</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:08:30</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="attapulgus" Rating="47"/>
    <Description>Four red plastic cookie cutters, each about 3-4 inches wide. Three aluminum cookie cutters. Two red-handled biscuit cutters. One tin or other metal biscuit cutter with sharp serrated cutting edge. One odd-shaped tin or other metal cookie cutter. All are in excellent condition. Please e-mail with questions. Buyer pays shipping and handling ($6.60) by Priority Mail. Insurance, if desired, is extra. Appropriate State and Local Sales Tax applies to sales with shipments to Georgia addresses. Money order, cashier's check, PayPal, Billpoint. Please see feedback. Please see other auctions.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045867996">
    <Name>Comics Buyer's Guide #1266, February 20, 1998</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Magazines</Category>
    <Category>Other Magazines</Category>
    <Currently>$1.25</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$5.31</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$1.25</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Clinton, MD</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:10:42</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:10:42</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="jmr82@cs.com" Rating="1992"/>
    <Description>Comic Buyer's guide - February 20, 1998, #1266. This is an 86-page magazine consisting of: 'Captain America' comes to Fox Kids this fall - the shield-slinger's World War II adventures are animated for the small screen Dwayne McDuffie and Serge Clermont join Acclaim - The creators are writing X-O Manowar and Shadowman respectively Ask Mr. Silver Age - Mr. Silver Age leads off our "Magic in Comics" theme with his prepubescent memories of Zatanna But I Disagree - What was all the to do about last week? Dateline @!!? - The Rocketeer pays Fred a visit Point of View - After several days in New York, Mark heads for Vegas Ten Comics Magies - Wheter drawkcab or forward, here are 10 ways magic is performed or found in our panelogical hobby Tony's Tips - Tony Keys in on an anime tip Ad information CBG Calendar Classifieds Comics Guide liComics Strip comics Trader For Art's Sake Mass o'Media Now Appearing Oh, So? Retailer Directory Showcase The Spirit Subscription Service What, Where, and When Winner to pay $2.25 (Media Mail) or $4.25 (Priority Mail) S/H --Insurance optional at $1.10 (US only). International bidders, please contact me for shipping rate. I will accept cash (at your own risk), checks (US only), money orders (US only, with some exception), PayPal, Billpoint or BidPay. International bidders must send cash, use Billpoint or PayPal if country is on accepted list, or use BidPay, with the exception of POSTAL money orders from some countries. Payment due within 9 days after auction ends. If payment is made by PayPal, I will ONLY ship to a confirmed address unless prior arrangements are agreed upon. Please do not ask or tell me what to put on customs forms. They will be filled out accurately. If you are the winner of multiple auctions, shipping will be combined.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045868055">
    <Name>KEEPSAKE ORNAMENT PRESSED TIN EASTER EGG NEST</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Series Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$5.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>SEASON GREETINGS</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:11:10</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:11:10</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="nomoreclutter" Rating="45"/>
    <Description>YOU ARE BIDDING ON A HALLMARK KEEPSAKE ORNAMENT EASTER EGG NEST. SCULPTED BY LINDA SICKMAN. PRESSED TIN ~ DATED 1999. In original packaging and never played with. Comes from a smoke free home. High bidder to pay 4.00 FOR SHIPPING AND HANDLING. Insurance is 1.15 extra. PLEASE NOTE I CANNOT BE HELD RESPONSIBLE IF YOU DECIDED TO NOT TO INSURE ITEM. Payment to be made by money order, cashiers check, paypal or cash. Please respond within 3 days from close of auction. Payment due within 7 days there after. GOOD LUCK AND THANK YOU FOR BIDDING!!!!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045870009">
    <Name>BUTTERFLY CANDY SOAP CRAFT MOLD MOLDS</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Molds</Category>
    <Currently>$1.68</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.68</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="krystl1" Rating="166">
          <Location>I Love NY!</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:13:36</Time>
        <Amount>$1.68</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>PA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:13:36</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:13:36</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="gremlinstr" Rating="2600"/>
    <Description>BUTTERFLY CANDY SOAP CRAFT MOLD MOLDS Products for this auction are supplied by: Streich's Cake and Candy Supply For information about us and our products please visit our &amp;nbsp " About Me Page " Description of this item: 12 CAVITY BUTTERFLY MOLD. THESE WORK GREAT FOR LITTLE MINT FLAVORED CANDIES. WORKS GREAT AS CAKE LAY-ONS. ALSO WORKS NICE AS LITTLE SOAP EMBEDS. Type of mold: FDA approved plastic: _NEW , NEVER USED_, We buy direct from the manufacturer, so these have never been in a garage/estate sale I can quarantee safe for Candy or other food related molding!! Everything we advertise and sell on this auction site is in stock! We _never_ wait until you pay for the item and then order it from the manufacturer. EVERYTHING ships immediatley upon payment! Shipping and Warranty Policy Click Here to review our policy before bidding: Shipping Policy Read about our new shipping system, Helps speed postal processing of your items. Quality of Items We carry the largest supply and variety of molds found any where on the Internet. (Over 5,000+ in stock at all times) Over the years we have found the best quality products from some of the better suppliers, we have weeded out the low quality and stuck with top quality products. SHIPPING: We try our best to offer the cheapest rates possible, and never intentionally try to profit from shipping overcharges! Insurance is an option, it is buyers choice whether you wish to pay the additional costs, $1.10 per package on either first class or priority mail. Shipping rates for this item: Priority mail for $3.95 (includes tracking) or first class for 2.10 (no tracking or insurance) . To save on shipping purchases we will gladly combine purchases from auctions with purchases from our online store. However purchases from our store cannot be be combined with ebay purchases for shipping. Again please review our Shipping policy link above for further details and options: Pa residents are subject to the states 6% sales tax. Payment info: We will accept your checks with the usual clearing time, so for immediate shipping I recommend a money order. Payment on these MUST be received within 7 days of close of auction. Paypal Payments: We will only accept Paypal payments from "non-credit card" transactions. This means you must pay from a balance from your account, or make a bank draft payment. Our Account name: streich@email.com Credit Card Payments: Visa Mastercard &amp; Amex We will also accept these payments, but only if your bid is $0.50 more than our listing amount: (starting bid). We don't have any hidden charges in our auctions or shipping fees to cover the additional costs of processing these extra charges. If you wish to use any of the Credit cards you wll need to notify us so we can send you to the proper pages. At the End of the Auction Normally witin 24 hours after the close of the auction you will recieve an automated email detailing the amount of the closing price and shipping charges. You will receive one even if you have multiple auctions. (this helps us keep our records cleaner). If you have multiple auctions just let us know after you receive the email notification and we will combine them for shipping breaks. We also have no problems waiting until all auctions are finished before doing a final bill. Questions ? We do try very hard to answer all questions regarding our items. Usually you will get a response within a few hours of your request. Normally we like to have one of the owners answer your questions, if one will not be available for an extended period you be notified. For questions: streich@email.com Please include the auction number or good description of item in question; Ruby Lane Antiques &amp; Collectibles Free Software to Submit this Auction provided by Auction Submit (tm)</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045870959">
    <Name>COMEDY TRAGEDY MASKS CANDY SOAP CRAFT MOLD</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Molds</Category>
    <Currently>$2.25</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.68</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="plcarlson81" Rating="70">
          <Location>MIDWEST ...ND...God Bless AMERICA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 04:50:52</Time>
        <Amount>$1.96</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="designergoodness" Rating="216">
          <Location>due East</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 14:26:52</Time>
        <Amount>$2.25</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>PA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:14:52</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:14:52</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="gremlinstr" Rating="2600"/>
    <Description>COMEDY TRAGEDY MASKS CANDY SOAP CRAFT MOLD Products for this auction are supplied by: Streich's Cake and Candy Supply For information about us and our products please visit our &amp;nbsp " About Me Page " Description of this item: THIS IS A GREAT TWO CAVITY TRAGEDY COMEDY MASK MOLD. THIS MOLD ALSO HAS LITTLE MUSICAL SYMBOLS ALL AROUND IT. GREAT FOR CANDIES, SOAPS OR PLASTER CRAFTS. Type of mold: FDA approved plastic: _NEW , NEVER USED_, We buy direct from the manufacturer, so these have never been in a garage/estate sale I can quarantee safe for Candy or other food related molding!! Everything we advertise and sell on this auction site is in stock! We _never_ wait until you pay for the item and then order it from the manufacturer. EVERYTHING ships immediatley upon payment! Shipping and Warranty Policy Click Here to review our policy before bidding: Shipping Policy Read about our new shipping system, Helps speed postal processing of your items. Quality of Items We carry the largest supply and variety of molds found any where on the Internet. (Over 5,000+ in stock at all times) Over the years we have found the best quality products from some of the better suppliers, we have weeded out the low quality and stuck with top quality products. SHIPPING: We try our best to offer the cheapest rates possible, and never intentionally try to profit from shipping overcharges! Insurance is an option, it is buyers choice whether you wish to pay the additional costs, $1.10 per package on either first class or priority mail. Shipping rates for this item: Priority mail for $3.95 (includes tracking) or first class for 2.10 (no tracking or insurance) . To save on shipping purchases we will gladly combine purchases from auctions with purchases from our online store. However purchases from our store cannot be be combined with ebay purchases for shipping. Again please review our Shipping policy link above for further details and options: Pa residents are subject to the states 6% sales tax. Payment info: We will accept your checks with the usual clearing time, so for immediate shipping I recommend a money order. Payment on these MUST be received within 7 days of close of auction. Paypal Payments: We will only accept Paypal payments from "non-credit card" transactions. This means you must pay from a balance from your account, or make a bank draft payment. Our Account name: streich@email.com Credit Card Payments: Visa Mastercard &amp; Amex We will also accept these payments, but only if your bid is $0.50 more than our listing amount: (starting bid). We don't have any hidden charges in our auctions or shipping fees to cover the additional costs of processing these extra charges. If you wish to use any of the Credit cards you wll need to notify us so we can send you to the proper pages. At the End of the Auction Normally witin 24 hours after the close of the auction you will recieve an automated email detailing the amount of the closing price and shipping charges. You will receive one even if you have multiple auctions. (this helps us keep our records cleaner). If you have multiple auctions just let us know after you receive the email notification and we will combine them for shipping breaks. We also have no problems waiting until all auctions are finished before doing a final bill. Questions ? We do try very hard to answer all questions regarding our items. Usually you will get a response within a few hours of your request. Normally we like to have one of the owners answer your questions, if one will not be available for an extended period you be notified. For questions: streich@email.com Please include the auction number or good description of item in question; Ruby Lane Antiques &amp; Collectibles Free Software to Submit this Auction provided by Auction Submit (tm)</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045871355">
    <Name>TEXACO--SUGAR SHAKER &amp; MATCHING S&amp;P SET</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Salt, Pepper Shakers</Category>
    <Category>Other Shakers</Category>
    <Currently>$10.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$10.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>granada hills,ca.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:15:46</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:15:46</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="harval1" Rating="1053"/>
    <Description>THIS AUCTION IS FOR A SET OF 3 PIECES. A GLASS SUGAR SHAKER AND A MATCHING SALT AND PEPPER SET. EACH PIECE HAS A CHROME TOP. THIS 3 PIECE SET LOOKS LIKE IT CAME FROM AN OLD DINER OR RESTAURANT BUT IT IS A NICE REPRODUCTION. THE PRICE IS LOW FOR A QUICK SALE. I HAVE A FEW SETS AVAILABLE. WINNER PAYS $5.00 SHIPPING COST FOR PRIORITY MAIL. E MAIL ME FOR A PICTURE. ******great xmas gift****** Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $0.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045871701">
    <Name>Byers Choice Cries of London DOLL MAKER 1995</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Byers Choice</Category>
    <Currently>$29.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>8</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ckandjm" Rating="58">
          <Location>Casselberry</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 10:32:09</Time>
        <Amount>$4.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="Glen" Rating="345">
          <Location>Bay Area</Location>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 01:48:31</Time>
        <Amount>$8.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="nickmass@aol.com" Rating="340">
          <Location>NY SAVE ON SHIPPING WIN MULTIPLE HALLMARKS</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 17:04:53</Time>
        <Amount>$11.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="flyball-sports" Rating="1483">
          <Location>Jacksonville,Fl</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 08:21:15</Time>
        <Amount>$15.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="edanddanielar" Rating="14">
          <Location>Cromwell, CT</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 23:37:37</Time>
        <Amount>$18.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ecworldauctions" Rating="642">
          <Location>Los Angeles, CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 14:53:58</Time>
        <Amount>$22.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ebay@penniesonthedollar.com" Rating="1726">
          <Location>Orlando, Florida</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 06:10:20</Time>
        <Amount>$25.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ripley99" Rating="168">
          <Location>Mega city II</Location>
          <Country>Canada</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 21:26:42</Time>
        <Amount>$29.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Reno, NV</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:15:48</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:15:48</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bought2much" Rating="680"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://members.aol.com/bought2much/Snow.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Byers Choice Cries of London DOLL MAKER 1995 The DOLL MAKER was the Byers Choice Cries of London edition for the year 1995.. Ours has a green shawl over her gray hair &amp; shoulder, grey waistcoat, white apron &amp; green tweed skirt. She has one doll in her hands, and 2 more in her basket. She's is in mint condition, with her hang tag attached and comes to you from my non-smoking home. I have many Byers Choice carolers to sell during the next few weeks, so please check my listings often. Buyer to add $8 for USPS Priority Mail shipping. Please see my other listings, as I am always happy to reduce shipping costs on combined wins. Payment is due within 10 days of auction close. I accept PayPal or money orders. I no longer accept personal checks unless Buyer's feedback rating is above 50+. Click HERE to see my other listings and SAVE on shipping costs.. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045872004">
    <Name>RADKO ~ Snow White &amp; Seven Dwarfs LE Set MINT</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Christopher Radko</Category>
    <Currently>$199.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$199.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="smileshop" Rating="620">
          <Location>God Bless the U.S.A.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:16:26</Time>
        <Amount>$199.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Worcester, MA ~ Birthplace Of Smiley ~</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:16:26</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:16:26</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="worldsmile@aol.com" Rating="530"/>
    <Description>~*~ From Christopher Radko And The Walt Disney Companies Gallery Store Comes SNOW WHITE And The SEVEN DWARFS ~ Petite Dopey, Happy, Grumpy, Bashful, Sleepy, Sneezy And Doc Join Lovely Snow White In This 1999 LIMITED EDITION Of 3000 Sets ~ This Auction Is For An Eight Piece LOW NUMBERED MATCHED SET ~ 735/3000 ~ This Radko Collection Is Sure To Be The One To Have This Year As Disney Re-releases The Classic Film This Fall For The First Time In Many Years ~ MINT ~ NEW ~ STILL SEALED In Celophane Wrap ~ Original Christopher Radko Disney Black Box With Gold Script Logo ~ This Ornament Set Has Never Been Used Or Displayed ~ It Has Been Stored Since Purchased ~ Opened Only For Inspection ~ The Photo Is Not From You're Actual Set ~ It Is For Example From Disney's Catalog ~ The Original Disney Gallery Store Price Tag (Still Attached) Was $275.00 ~ Shipped U.S.P.O. Priority For $8.00 Within The USA ~ Insurance Additional And Your Choice! ~ Billpoint, Paypal nd Money Orders Welcome ~ Thanks for stopping by ~ Please Visit My Other Auctions To Combine For Shipping ~ OH! And... Have A Happy Day!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045874211">
    <Name>HARMONY KINGDOM ~ ARIA AMOROSA ~ RETIRED</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Harmony Kingdom</Category>
    <Currently>$1.25</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="wheelnut.nz" Rating="688">
          <Location>Shipped Worldwide With Care.</Location>
          <Country>New Zealand</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 04:55:40</Time>
        <Amount>$1.12</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="froggiamu@aol.com" Rating="3336">
          <Location>New Port Richey, Florida</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 14:31:40</Time>
        <Amount>$1.25</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Portland, OR</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:19:40</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:19:40</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="suncookie" Rating="202"/>
    <Description>HARMONY KINGDOM ~ ARIA AMOROSA ~ RETIRED Name: Aria Amorosa Artist: Peter Calvesbert Item No: TJES Collection Name: Treasure Jest Subset Name: Small Treasure Jest Exclusive To: Made In: England Status: Retired Carving Date: 1997 Release Date: 1/1/1998 In Store Date: Retirement Date: 7/1/1998 Edition Size: 9530 US Issue Price in USD: $45 UK Issue Price in GBP: 29.5 CAN Issue Price in CND: $70 Category: Box Figurine Dimensions (Inches): 1.93 x 2.83 x 2.95 S e c r e t s This box figurine depicts two seals, lovingly entwined, mouths open in song. A plimsol line with numerical markings runs down the belly of one of them, a representation of the amount of oil that can be extracted from an elephant seal. Peter carved the cigarette lighter under the other seal s flipper after a beach-combing trip in North Wales where he found the beach littered with plastic lighters. Peter s mouse looks out startled from under another flipper. The inspiration for the rat carved inside was a topical news item that Peter misheard on the radio at the time of carving: the monster rat catastrophe. It turns out that it was the Montserrat catastrophe, a volcano threatening to erupt in the Caribbean. Hallmarks include , heart, HBC logo, ed.#, and Pc, with "P. Calvesbert" on the base. 1ST EDITION, NEVER DISPLAYED. THIS BOX WAS FROM THE FIRST RELEASE AND THE NOSE OF THE MOUSE INSIDE IS RED. THE FLIPPERS OF THE SEA LION ARE GREY. ARIA AMOROSE HAS NEVER BEEN DISPLAYED AND IS IN PRISTINE CONDITION, . SHIPPING, HANDLING AND INSURANCE, $7.00. ALL MY AUCTIONS YIELD NOTHING BUT THE BEST! GOOD LUCK!! This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Visit Suncookie today! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $5.50 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.50 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045875982">
    <Name>832561 FRIENDS OF THE FEATHER LIFES JOURNEY</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Friends of the Feather</Category>
    <Currently>$22.49</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$14.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>5</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="heritagevalleysales" Rating="112">
          <Location>The Heritage Valley</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 16:22:18</Time>
        <Amount>$16.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="niltiak2@aol.com" Rating="197">
          <Location>Cleveland, OH</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:22:18</Time>
        <Amount>$17.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="aqcl@earthlink.net" Rating="80">
          <Location>Hillsborough, NC</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 10:22:18</Time>
        <Amount>$19.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jns4sale" Rating="753">
          <Location>Beautiful OHIO</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 07:22:18</Time>
        <Amount>$20.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="bhoot58" Rating="4">
          <Location>Fort Collins, Colorado</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 04:22:18</Time>
        <Amount>$22.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Indiana</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:22:18</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:22:18</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="papergirl" Rating="2555"/>
    <Description>LIFES JOURNEY HOLDS MANY SECRETS / GIRLS TALKING IN TREE You are bidding on a mint edition FRIENDS OF THE FEATHER figurine. This item is brand new in its mint box. Item also includes all paper work from Enesco. All of our merchandise is purchased direct and is guaranteed mint. We will provide you with a money back guarantee if you wish to return your item because it is not as described. All items are shipped via 3-day priority mail most of the time within 48hrs upon receiving payment. Postage rates will be figured on weight after the auction. We will ship international, and Canadian orders. All non- U.S. postage rates will be figured you're your winning. We accept Visa, MasterCard, Discover card as payment via our own secure server. If you have any questions about the items we have up for auction feel free to email us anytime at papergirl@cnz.com Visit Sharables Gifts And Collectibles today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045876418">
    <Name>1995 CHRISTMAS COVE LIGHTHOUSE</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jbear@iolinc.net" Rating="431">
          <Location>West Virginia</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:23:01</Time>
        <Amount>$9.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>NEW JERSEY</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:23:01</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:23:01</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="rat33@warwick.net" Rating="3075"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#6A5B44; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#6A5B44; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #000000; } 1995 CHRISTMAS COVE LIGHTHOUSE Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version well these are really wonderful houses in the snow village series!! if you have a chance take a look at the others that i have listed. all of them have their outer sleeve and then the styrofoam case all of the outer sleeves do show some wear and all have some writing on them all of the houses are included with the bulbs and the plug that gets stuck into the house to light them up PLS NOTE THAT I SELL ALL OF MY ELECTRICAL PARTS AS IS they all did work when i tested them. also all of the houses do have some light wear around the factory holes for the lights from display useage. and i have photoed all of the base markings for you pls note that my pictures were taken inside so the item will look MUCH better in person as i am a crummy photographer to begin with! great bunch of houses though in this lot you are getting: the 1995 light house there are 4 small areas of dinging at the base (they really are very small i nit pick on these houses!) and then on the top piece of the lighthouse that is seperate there is a tiny ding on the bottom of its base no other chips or cracks all in all a great house! good luck and GOD BLESS AMERICA PASSING THRU TIME ANTIQUES &amp; COLLECTIBLES NEW JERSEY USA PLEASE NOTE: I WILL NOT RESPOND TO ANY INQUIRIES AT THE END OF AUCTION FROM BIDDDERS THAT USE THE EBAY "CHECK OUT" OPTION PLS BE CONSIDERATE TO SELLERS AND WAIT TO BE CONTACTED THIS NEW SYSTEM OF EBAY'S IS DIFFICULT FOR ME TO USE AND I WILL NOT USE IT. AS STATED BELOW YOU WILL RECEIVE AN AUTOMATED EMAIL FROM ME AT THE END OF THE AUCTION STATING ALL OF THE SHIPPING SPECIFICS IT IS IMPORTANT THAT YOUT RY TO USE THIS AS IT HELPS ME WITH SHIPPING AND GETTING YOUR ITEM TO YOU FASTER. I APPRECIATE YOUR UNDERSTANDING. I STILL WELCOME ALL QUESTIONS FROM PROSPECTIVE BIDDERS BUT PLS USE THE "ASK A SELLER A QUESTION" ON EBAY I WILL RESPOND TO ALL. AND ONE MORE TIME I WILL NOT GET BACK TO YOU IF YOU USE THE CHECK OUT FEATURE. PLS WAIT FOR THE AUTOMATED EMAIL THANKS YOU AGAIN ALL OF MY OTHER POLICIES FOLLOW: Please review my EBAY ABOUT ME Page for my shipping and selling policies. PLS NOTE BECAUSE I CAN NOT EDIT THAT PAGE FOR SOME REASON THE FOLLOWING IS INCORRECT: I DO NOT AND WILL NOT ACCEPT BIDS FROM INTERNATIONAL MEMBERS I ONLY SHIP IN THE UNITED STATES ENERGY COSTS HAVE DRIVEN THE COST OF SHIPPING OVERSEAS UP AND EVERYONE OF MY INTERNATIONAL BIDDERS HAS REFUSED TO PAY ACTUAL SHIPPING SO PLS!!! DO NOT BID ON MY ITEM IF YOU ARE NOT FROM THE USA THANKS if you have any questions or need any clarification pls contact me before bidding i will provide whatever information you require. my items are described honestly and accurately to the best of my ability (refer to my feedback) so all sales should be considered final. SHIPPING INFORMATION: buyer pays priority USPS shipping w/small handling fee included (covers shipping materials I DO NOT SKIMP!! (refer to my feedback regarding my packing) insurance is REQUIRED to cover postal damage/loss. insurance is not included in email high bidder notification pls add $1.10 for final value up to $50., $2.00 for value of $50-$100, $3.00 for value of $100.01-199.99 and then for every hundred dollars of value add one more dollar. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO INSURE IF YOU CHOOSE TO DO SO PLS STATE THIS WITH PAYMENT INSUFFICIENT INSURANCE PAYMENT WILL RESULT OF ITEM SHIPPING UNINSURED NEW JERSEY RESIDENTS MUST ADD 6% TAX TO FINAL HIGH BID if you do not pay the 6% or provide tax ID the item will not ship and will be held until tax payment received. thanks for looking at my auction and GOOD LUCK if you decide to bid appropriate feedback is always given on a reciprocation basis MY HIGH BIDDER NOTIFICATION IS NOW AUTOMATED SO WHEN SENDING PAYMENT PLEASE BE SURE TO INCLUDE A DESCRIPTION OF THE ITEM YOU WON THE EBAY# AND YOUR U.S.P.S. MAILING ADDRESS THIS WILL WILL SPEED UP THE SHIPPING PROCESS THANKS RICH xx xx Payment I accept the following forms of payment: Money Order, Personal Check, I DO NOT ACCEPT PAYPAL. Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045877276">
    <Name>Mary Engelbreit Cherry Cameo Potholder</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Mary Engelbreit</Category>
    <Currently>$2.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="debwalk" Rating="135">
          <Location>WILD WONDERFUL WEST VIRGINIA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:24:02</Time>
        <Amount>$2.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Broken Arrow,OK</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:24:02</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:24:02</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="blackberryhillfarm" Rating="868"/>
    <Description>Mary Engelbreit Cherry Cameo Potholder Click picture to enlarge Mary Engelbreit Cherry Cameo Potholder Description Straight from the manufacturer comes this delightful Mary Engelbreit Cherry Cameo Potholder!Mary Engelbreit shows us a world where goodness prevails as she has transferred her trademark black and white checkered borders,cherries and cozy images to products that capture the eyes and hearts of women everywhere.The potholder measures roughly 5" x5" and is made of 50/50 polyester /cotton blend.Don't miss out on this great gift at a great price!We accept paypal,billpoint,mastecard,visa,money order,or personal check for payment.The first linen item ships at $4 USPS priority mail.Each additional linen item ships at an additional $1 in shipping with the same shipment.Merry Christmas from Blackberry Hill Farm! Payment and Shipping Info Payment Options Money Order/Cashier's Check or Personal Check or Visa or MasterCard _ _ _ Shipping See item description for Shipping Charges. No International Shipping Quantity Available 1 Use the REAL selling tools a million sellers do - Andale!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045878499">
    <Name>833614 MARYS MOO MOOS JOHN DEERE WEDDING</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Mary's Moo Moos</Category>
    <Currently>$24.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$24.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Indiana</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:25:16</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:25:16</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="papergirl" Rating="2555"/>
    <Description>JOHN DEERE HAY WAGON RISER MUSICAL / TUNE: WEDDING MARCH You are bidding on a mint edition MARYS MOO MOOS figurine. This item is brand new in its mint box. Item also includes all paper work from Enesco. All of our merchandise is purchased direct and is guaranteed mint. We have owned and operated a store for a number of years. All items are new store stock. We also have a web site for your shopping convenience with a search engine. We will provide you with a money back guarantee if you wish to return your item because it is not as described. All items are shipped via 3-day priority mail most of the time within 48hrs upon receiving payment. Postage rates will be figured on weight after the auction. We will ship international, and Canadian orders. All non- U.S. postage rates will be figured you're your winning. We accept Visa, MasterCard, Discover card as payment via our own secure server. If you have any questions about the items we have up for auction feel free to email us anytime at papergirl@cnz.com Visit Sharables Gifts And Collectibles today! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045878644">
    <Name>Timber Wolf and Feathers Pewter Keytag</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Keychains</Category>
    <Currently>$6.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$6.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Williams Bay, Wisconsin</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:25:25</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:25:25</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bucklepros" Rating="5822"/>
    <Description>This Keytag is made from hand poured fine pewter then carefully hand finished and colored. Keytag is approx 1.5 inches across Made in the U.S.A. Lifetime Guarantee against defects in workmanship. Shipping and Handling $2.00 in U.S.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045879504">
    <Name>50s Style Pink Cocktail Elephants &amp; Stirrers</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Barware</Category>
    <Category>Swizzle/Stir Sticks</Category>
    <Currently>$4.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Th retro-riffic 50's idolicious stunning galleria of kitsch!</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:26:16</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:26:16</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="funnstuf" Rating="964"/>
    <Description/>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045879775">
    <Name>1940s Bronze Bausch &amp; Lomb Science Award</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Historical Memorabilia</Category>
    <Category>Other Historical Items</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>rochester, new york</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:26:51</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:26:51</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="kh433@aol.com" Rating="948"/>
    <Description>2" x 2-1/2" x 3/8" thick bronze medal/paperweight. Pictures a goddess below whom it says "Bausch &amp; Lomb Honorary Science Award". The back was never inscribed. I am sure this was made by Bastian Bros. Co. in the late 1940s. Buyer to pay $2.50 postage (U.S.). I accept PAYPAL. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $2.00 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045882782">
    <Name>'97 Our Lady of Guadalupe pewter (min) BIN $6</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Miniature Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$4.97</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.97</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>chicago</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:30:05</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:30:05</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lipsiervice" Rating="906"/>
    <Description>'97 Our Lady of Guadalupe pewter (min) BIN $6 1997 Our Lady of Guadalupe (miniature) presented by: LIPSIERVICE Retail Price $8.95 CHRISTMAS IS JUST AROUND THE CORNER AND SELECT ORNAMENTS ARE 30% - 60% OFF !!! SHIPPING SPECIAL !!! BUY 6 OR MORE ORNAMENTS AND RECEIVE FREE SHIPPING ! ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- THIS ORNAMENTS FEATURES : NEW IN BOX HONORS PATRON SAINT OF MEXICO FINE PEWTER ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- SHIPPING INFORMATION : FIRST CLASS MAIL PRIORITY MAIL $3.95 $5.15 (AUTOMATICALLY INSURED) (AUTOMATICALLY INSURED) INTERNATIONAL SHIPPING VARIES SO PLEASE EMAIL FOR RATE (MULTIPLE PURCHASES CAN BE COMBINED TO SAVE ON SHIPPING) ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- CLICK ABOVE for any questions regarding our auctions or to receive your ... ... FREE color catalog to ORDER all 2001 ornaments ! ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- To view all of our auctions and receive FREE shipping, click below ! (some auctions are over but most items are still available) SIGN UP WITH PAY PAL NOW AND GET $5.00 ! IT'S FAST, FREE, AND SECURE ! NO RESERVE Click here to view my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045885108">
    <Name>Sterling Silver Cream Ladle</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Tableware</Category>
    <Category>Flatware</Category>
    <Currently>$5.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="figuredealer" Rating="103">
          <Location>Billpoint &amp; Paypal accepted</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:32:35</Time>
        <Amount>$5.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Buffalo,Mo.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:32:35</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:32:35</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="buffalojo2000" Rating="19"/>
    <Description>This beautiful ladle measures 4 1/2 in. from tip to tip. It is marked on the back with the numbers 925 over a line and 000 under the line then STERLING at the side. The curve in the handle looks as if it was bent at one time but in no way distracts from the elegance of this piece. Perfect for your Christmas table. Modestly priced and no reserve. Successful bidder should respond to this auction within 3 days and payment should be received within 10 days of this auction.Buyer should add $4.00 for shipping in the U.S.A. and if you prefer insurance another $1.10. Thank you for viewiing my auction. God Bless America Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045885477">
    <Name>'97 The Flight at Kitty Hawk 1ST BIN $12</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Series Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$9.97</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.97</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>chicago</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:32:52</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:32:52</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lipsiervice" Rating="906"/>
    <Description>'97 The Flight at Kitty Hawk 1ST BIN $12 1997 The Flight at Kitty Hawk presented by: LIPSIERVICE Retail Price $14.95 CHRISTMAS IS ALMOST HERE, AND SELECT ORNAMENTS ARE 30% - 60% OFF !!! SHIPPING SPECIAL !!! BUY 6 OR MORE ORNAMENTS AND RECEIVE FREE SHIPPING ! ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- THIS ORNAMENTS FEATURES : NEW IN BOX 1st IN THE "SKY'S THE LIMIT" SERIES WE HAVE OTHER ITEMS FROM THIS SERIES ALSO ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- SHIPPING INFORMATION : FIRST CLASS MAIL PRIORITY MAIL $3.95 $5.15 (AUTOMATICALLY INSURED) (AUTOMATICALLY INSURED) INTERNATIONAL SHIPPING VARIES SO PLEASE EMAIL FOR RATE (MULTIPLE PURCHASES CAN BE COMBINED TO SAVE ON SHIPPING) ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- CLICK ABOVE for any questions regarding our auctions or to receive your ... ... FREE color catalog to ORDER all 2001 ornaments ! ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- To view all of our auctions and receive FREE shipping, click below ! (some auctions are over but most items are still available) SIGN UP WITH PAY PAL NOW AND GET $5.00 ! IT'S FAST, FREE, AND SECURE ! NO RESERVE Click here to view my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045885631">
    <Name>LONGABERGER BASKET 2001 HOH LID CLASSIC</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Baskets</Category>
    <Currently>$16.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$16.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>My House</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:33:00</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:33:00</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="basket-girl.com" Rating="552"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://basket-girl.com/ebay/snow.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } LONGABERGER BASKET 2001 HOH LID CLASSIC See our other auctions &amp; ebaY store. Many more of the same &amp; related items. PLEASE USE EBAY CHECKOUT TO GET YOUR ITEMS FASTER SEE OTHER AUCTIONS FOR MORE OF THE SAME ALL LONGABERGER PRODUCTS ARE IN NEW CONDITION NO RESERVE Buyer to pay $5.00 for shipping and handling. USA only. For Large items Alaska &amp; Hawaii will be higher. Click here to view all auctions on one page. A happy customer is a repeat customer! Buyer Satisfaction is our policy! :) We offer a 100% Satisfaction Guarantee on all Products. The Item Purchased Must be returned In The Original Condition as received. We Will Refund or Credit your Credit Card Or Papal Account Within 30 Days Of Receipt of item Under no circumstances do we refund shipping. Under No Circumstances Do We Do Partial Refunds All Items Are Shipped insured By a Private Insurance against Damage or Loss in Shipping. All Refunds will be made through Billpoint or PayPal No Checks will be mailed All sales are considered Final 7 days after you receive the item Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045886235">
    <Name>WEREWOLF BY NIGHT 1</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Bronze Age (1970-79)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$2.00</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$12.03</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$1.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="craftygurrl" Rating="22">
          <Location>Redwood City</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 05:10:13</Time>
        <Amount>$1.75</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="lizashby" Rating="599">
          <Location>Long Island</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 14:46:13</Time>
        <Amount>$2.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>central pa.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:34:13</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:34:13</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="rpuck1" Rating="422"/>
    <Description>hello. this weekend i will be listing about 125 silver and bronze age books all starting at 1.50, so be sure to check my other auctions and combine to save on shipping. i won't go into the details about each book, just a grade, so assume the book has the properties of this grade. if you have a question or want more details about a book just email me. this book is werewolf by night 1 in fn cond. shipping 3.50, payment by paypal or money order. all payments due within 14 days after close of auction. if i do not receive the payment within this time, a non-paying bidder alert will be filed followed by negative feedback. shipping to the u.s. only. sorry about the blurry pictures but it's the best i can do for now. thanks for looking and good luck.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045886807">
    <Name>RETIRED MAIL BOX AND BENCH ACCESSORY SET</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Charming Tails</Category>
    <Currently>$5.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$23.96</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$5.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Houston</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:34:13</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 19:34:13</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="featherstone2" Rating="2995"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://users2.ev1.net/~husky2/photos/images/whitemar.jpg) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } RETIRED MAIL BOX AND BENCH ACCESSORY SET This is a retired accessory set to the Charming Tails collection by Dean Griff. It is the park bench and mailbox. It is a really cute set that certainly adds charm. This is a new piece in perfect condition and with the box. The lucky winner pays $3.75 shipping (insurance is additional) We do not require insurance but do strongly recommend it. As I am sure you understand, we cannot be responsible for any broken or lost packages that you have not purchased insurance for. (insurance is .01-50.00 $1.10, 50.01-100.00 $2.00, 100.01-200.00 $3.00 and $1.00 for each additional $100.00 of value.) We will be happy to ship internationally but may charge a $5.00 handling fee for items under $50.00 because of the extra time required to process an international order. Thank you so much for you bid and good luck!!! We take Checks, Money orders, and Paypal. We ship priority mail. NO RESERVE Click here to view my other auctions. This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045890436">
    <Name>Dept. 56, SANTA'S WORKSHOP, BIN FREE SHIPPING</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>North Pole</Category>
    <Currently>$100.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$100.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="gjensen268" Rating="110">
          <Location>Alma, NE</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:40:41</Time>
        <Amount>$100.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Elwood,New York</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:40:41</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:40:41</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="z00ke0pler" Rating="85"/>
    <Description>BUY IT NOW AND GET FREE SHIPPING! Hard to find--One of the oldest pieces in the collection. Issued in 1990 and retired 1993. Wonderfully detailed, large piece. A must-have centerpiece for any North Pole collection. Only displayed 3 times. Box and sleeve in good condition. The piece itself is in excellent condition. NO chips,cracks or repairs. From a non-smoking home. Selling many pieces from North Pole collection. Check out my other auctions. I highly recommend the following accessories: "Trimming the North Pole" and "Santa &amp; Mrs. Claus" Also, looks great next to "Rt. 1, North Pole, Home of Mr. &amp; Mrs. Claus." Multiple purchase will be shipped together to save you postage. Please email me with the pieces you want shipped together. I accept PAYPAL, BILLPOINT, MONEY ORDERS (Sorry No Personal Checks). I will ship all packages the next day. Priority Mail (2-3 days) w/ Delevery Confirmation 7.00. I strongly recommend Insurance for $4.00. May your holidays be healthy and happy. Looking forward to hearing from you. Good Luck!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045890959">
    <Name>AMAZING ADVENTURES 1</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Bronze Age (1970-79)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$1.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$1.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>central pa.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:42:03</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:42:03</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="rpuck1" Rating="422"/>
    <Description>hello. this weekend i will be listing about 125 silver and bronze age books all starting at 1.50, so be sure to check my other auctions and combine to save on shipping. i won't go into the details about each book, just a grade, so assume the book has the properties of this grade. if you have a question or want more details about a book just email me. this book is amazing adventures 1 in fn cond. shipping 3.50, payment by paypal or money order. all payments due within 14 days after close of auction. if i do not receive the payment within this time, a non-paying bidder alert will be filed followed by negative feedback. shipping to the u.s. only. sorry about the blurry pictures but it's the best i can do for now. thanks for looking and good luck.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045894261">
    <Name>Huge Glass Goblet Alpha Epsilon Phi LARGE !</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Barware</Category>
    <Category>Other Barware</Category>
    <Currently>$2.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>New Buffalo, MI</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:46:52</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:46:52</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="marcella44" Rating="917"/>
    <Description>NO RESERVE! This is a HUGE Stemware Goblet that measures 11" high and 7" across top opening. This may have been a Dusty Bottle Special Fraternity Goblet. Before any real Toga party....the goblet is filled with a shot from any and every Dusty bottle on the bar.......and then things started happening. Or maybe you would call it a Big Ol' Beer (Wine) Swillin' Deal. It would look great on your bar filled with peanuts, etc., or could be used as a trifle style serving glass. Or turn the letters to the back and fill with Christmas ornaments.. Use your imagination.. It has 3 Greek letters etched on the side that stand for Alpha Epsilon Phi. Condition is excellent. Really a very pretty glass. TERMS Winner to confirm their bid by furnishing your mailing address within 3 business days. Payment is bid amount plus Actual Priority Shipping charges. Please mail payment within 10 days of auction end. Insurance is your option. I do package carefully, but it's your choice. I do not charge a handling fee and will not hold your check to clear. I will mail all orders the first business day after receipt of payment by check, money order, or Sacajewea dollars. :^) I will also accept Paypal for bids over $10.00. I welcome international bidders, but shipping will be higher. You can wait until end of auction or you can email me for quote. Multiple orders can be combined when practical to save on shipping. All questions welcome. Good luck and happy trading. GOD BLESS AMERICA !</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045896144">
    <Name>2 ISSUES OF GHOSTS- 19 &amp; 31 - VF CONDITION!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Bronze Age (1970-79)</Category>
    <Category>Horror, Sci-Fi</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Fall River, MA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:49:06</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:49:06</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="aqualityfurniture" Rating="2698"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://www.aqualityfurniture.com/backgr/crinklep.jpg) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Click picture to see actual image size. 2 ISSUES OF GHOSTS- 19 &amp; 31 - VF CONDITION! Here we have two issues from that classic horror series from the 70's, Ghosts. # 19 &amp; 13 are both in FN to VF condition and ready to add to your ghostly collection. Please see shipping costs/methods and insurance requirements below. For larger items please click here to email us for a quote. All breakables and items valued near and above $50 will have insurance required. If the item is shipped via FedEx this coverage is automatic up to $100 in value, 40_ for each additional $100 coverage. For USPS delivery, $1.25 up to $50, $1.00 each additional $100. All uninsured parcels become the responsiblity of the bidder once said parcel is duly delivered to the appropriate carrier. The following types of payment are accepted: money orders, personal checks*, and all major credit cards. Payment must be received within 10 business days in order to avoid negative feedback and being reported to eBay as a non-payer. This will also expedite shipping of your item. * All returned checks will be accessed a $25 service fee. Buyer to pay $2.50 for shipping and handling. All international bidders MUST email us for an adjusted S&amp;H quote! Click here to view my other auctions. Ma residents pay a 5% sales tax. SHIPPING METHODS: The bidder may at any time request the shipping service of their choice, to which will be added an appropriate handling fee. MEDIA: We have been shipping media items (records, books, etc.) by Media mail, but have experienced slow delivery times, so we are trying to move away from this service. Smaller, light-weight media items over 13 ozs. are still quoted for Media mail and the bidder may request a different delivery service. However, we WILL NOT be held responsible for the long amount of time any Media mail shipment may take. SMALLER ITEMS: Other smaller items up to 13 ozs. are shipped first class. All other items are shipped either Priority mail or FedEx. Usually anything over a few pounds is shipped via FedEx, hence the higher costs. However, their exemplary service is guarenteed, carries automatic insurance up to $100 in value, and is trackable with out additional cost. Any item shipped through the USPS Priority service without requesting additional services such as delivery confirmation can not be tracked, nor will we be held responsibility for its not being delivered (see insurance disclaimer above). LARGER ITEMS: Larger items such as furniture and such are shipped either with BAX Global or a local mover we use who makes east coast runs every two-three weeks. HANDLING FEES: Since our shipping department needs to eat (and we require him to wear shoes, please! ), and shipping materials do cost money (really!) all items have an appropriate handling fee. Basically, the more time and care taken to prepare an item for safe transport, the higher the fee. We do our best to provide both cost effective and careful handling of packaging your item. This fee is not negotiable is usually reflected in all posted S&amp;H charges, or added to shipping quotes for larger items. Free counters provided by Honesty.com This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045896338">
    <Name>Precious Moments Nativity Goat E-2364 - NM</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$41.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$19.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>5</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="lmcathome" Rating="82">
          <Location>Pikeville, KY</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 16:50:42</Time>
        <Amount>$24.19</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="wcbearlyworn" Rating="1800">
          <Location>CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 13:50:42</Time>
        <Amount>$28.39</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="blcampagna@prodigy.net" Rating="241">
          <Location>Baton Rouge, LA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 10:50:42</Time>
        <Amount>$32.60</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="icanfind" Rating="107">
          <Location>Indiana</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 07:50:42</Time>
        <Amount>$36.80</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="starsigz" Rating="783">
          <Location>L.A.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 04:50:42</Time>
        <Amount>$41.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Not Far From The Windy City</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:50:42</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:50:42</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lamarron" Rating="34"/>
    <Description>You are bidding on a Precious Moments Goat E-2364 figurine with No Mark. There are no chips or cracks the figurine is in good condition. Bottom of goat is stamped 1982 Jonathan &amp; David Lic Enesco Imports E-2364. Comes with original box with sticker on box stating: item no. E-2364, description goat ornament contents 1 pc., color or style 1982 Jonathon &amp; David. Buyer pays 3.00 priority shipping insurance is extra. I accept U.S. postal money orders only. U.S. bidders ONLY please. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045896463">
    <Name>Hallmark 1980 Christmas Cardinals</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$5.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$5.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>West Lafayette, IN</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:49:55</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:49:55</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="shirleysglass" Rating="1165"/>
    <Description>Hallmark 1980 Christmas Cardinals This auction features the 1980 Christmas Cardinals Glass Ball ornament by Hallmark (QX 224-1). The ball has spots and is darkening. The box is in good condition with no price tag and just slight wear on the top. Shipping is $4.00. NO RESERVE! Buyer to pay shipping as quoted in the ad and insurance if desired. Insurance is $1.10 for items under $50, $2.00 for items from $50 to $100. For items over $100, the insurance fee is $2.00 plus $1.00 for each additional $100 in coverage. All quoted shipping/insurance is for U.S. shipping. Credit cards or electronic checks accepted through Billpoint or PayPal. I also take Bidpay. Please allow time for personal check to clear or send m.o. for quick shipping. Please check out the other auctions we currently have running on eBay. If you win multiple auctions, I will combine them to save you shipping! Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045896857">
    <Name>ROGER BROS SOUTHERN SPLENDID 68 PC SET</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Metalware</Category>
    <Category>Silverplate</Category>
    <Currently>$74.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$74.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Fall River, MA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:50:42</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:50:42</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="aqualityfurniture" Rating="2698"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://www.aqualityfurniture.com/backgr/gold.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Click picture to see actual image size. ROGER BROS SOUTHERN SPLENDID 68 PC SET Up for auction this wek is a 61Pc set of Rogers Bros Souothern Splendid aka Royal Pageant pattern which was made in 1962. This set is in great shape virtaully no tarnish on the silver plate at all. In this set you get: 7 regular spoons 16 regular spoons 1 butter knife 8 Parfait Spoons 8 Shrimp forks 8 large spoons 8 large forks 8 knives 2 serving spoons 1 large serving spoon 1 serving fork Plus you get a very nice looking case that has a pull out draw. This would make a nice set to have this holiday season. SHIPPING AND HANDLING TO BE DETERMINED AT END OF AUCTION AND WILL BE DEPEND ON LOCATION OF BUYER. Please see shipping costs/methods and insurance requirements below. For larger items please click here to email us for a quote. All breakables and items valued near and above $50 will have insurance required. If the item is shipped via FedEx this coverage is automatic up to $100 in value, 40_ for each additional $100 coverage. For USPS delivery, $1.25 up to $50, $1.00 each additional $100. All uninsured parcels become the responsiblity of the bidder once said parcel is duly delivered to the appropriate carrier. DELIVERY CAN BE MADE WITHIN A 250 MILE RADIUS OF OUR STORE ON OUR LARGER ITEMS. PLEASE EMAIL FOR A DELIVERY QUOTE The following types of payment are accepted: money orders, personal checks*, and all major credit cards. Payment must be received within 10 business days in order to avoid negative feedback and being reported to eBay as a non-payer. This will also expedite shipping of your item. * All returned checks will be accessed a $25 service fee. Ma residents pay a 5% sales tax. SHIPPING METHODS: The bidder may at any time request the shipping service of their choice, to which will be added an appropriate handling fee. MEDIA: We have been shipping media items (records, books, etc.) by Media mail, but have experienced slow delivery times, so we are trying to move away from this service. Smaller, light-weight media items over 13 ozs. are still quoted for Media mail and the bidder may request a different delivery service. However, we WILL NOT be held responsible for the long amount of time any Media mail shipment may take. SMALLER ITEMS: Other smaller items up to 13 ozs. are shipped first class. All other items are shipped either Priority mail or FedEx. Usually anything over a few pounds is shipped via FedEx, hence the higher costs. However, their exemplary service is guarenteed, carries automatic insurance up to $100 in value, and is trackable with out additional cost. Any item shipped through the USPS Priority service without requesting additional services such as delivery confirmation can not be tracked, nor will we be held responsibility for its not being delivered (see insurance disclaimer above). LARGER ITEMS: Larger items such as furniture and such are shipped either with BAX Global or a local mover we use who makes east coast runs every two-three weeks. HANDLING FEES: Since our shipping department needs to eat (and we require him to wear shoes, please! ), and shipping materials do cost money (really!) all items have an appropriate handling fee. Basically, the more time and care taken to prepare an item for safe transport, the higher the fee. We do our best to provide both cost effective and careful handling of packaging your item. This fee is not negotiable and is usually reflected in all posted S&amp;H charges, or added to shipping quotes for larger items. Free counters provided by Honesty.com This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045897062">
    <Name>ONIEDA TUDOR ELAINE SILVERWARE SET</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Metalware</Category>
    <Category>Silverplate</Category>
    <Currently>$29.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$29.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Fall River, MA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:51:08</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:51:08</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="aqualityfurniture" Rating="2698"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://www.aqualityfurniture.com/backgr/gold.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Click picture to see actual image size. ONIEDA TUDOR ELAINE SILVERWARE SET Up for auction this week is a Onieda Tudor Elaine silverware set from 1926. This set is in decent shape and does show some wear. This set consists of: 8 large spoons 6 spoons 4 forks 2 serving spoons 7 large forks 7 knives. This set comes in a nice blue leather like case. SHIPPING AND HANDLING TO BE DETERMINED AT END OF AUCTION AND WILL DEPEND ON BUYER LOCATION. Please see shipping costs/methods and insurance requirements below. For larger items please click here to email us for a quote. All breakables and items valued near and above $50 will have insurance required. If the item is shipped via FedEx this coverage is automatic up to $100 in value, 40_ for each additional $100 coverage. For USPS delivery, $1.25 up to $50, $1.00 each additional $100. All uninsured parcels become the responsiblity of the bidder once said parcel is duly delivered to the appropriate carrier. DELIVERY CAN BE MADE WITHIN A 250 MILE RADIUS OF OUR STORE ON OUR LARGER ITEMS. PLEASE EMAIL FOR A DELIVERY QUOTE The following types of payment are accepted: money orders, personal checks*, and all major credit cards. Payment must be received within 10 business days in order to avoid negative feedback and being reported to eBay as a non-payer. This will also expedite shipping of your item. * All returned checks will be accessed a $25 service fee. Ma residents pay a 5% sales tax. SHIPPING METHODS: The bidder may at any time request the shipping service of their choice, to which will be added an appropriate handling fee. MEDIA: We have been shipping media items (records, books, etc.) by Media mail, but have experienced slow delivery times, so we are trying to move away from this service. Smaller, light-weight media items over 13 ozs. are still quoted for Media mail and the bidder may request a different delivery service. However, we WILL NOT be held responsible for the long amount of time any Media mail shipment may take. SMALLER ITEMS: Other smaller items up to 13 ozs. are shipped first class. All other items are shipped either Priority mail or FedEx. Usually anything over a few pounds is shipped via FedEx, hence the higher costs. However, their exemplary service is guarenteed, carries automatic insurance up to $100 in value, and is trackable with out additional cost. Any item shipped through the USPS Priority service without requesting additional services such as delivery confirmation can not be tracked, nor will we be held responsibility for its not being delivered (see insurance disclaimer above). LARGER ITEMS: Larger items such as furniture and such are shipped either with BAX Global or a local mover we use who makes east coast runs every two-three weeks. HANDLING FEES: Since our shipping department needs to eat (and we require him to wear shoes, please! ), and shipping materials do cost money (really!) all items have an appropriate handling fee. Basically, the more time and care taken to prepare an item for safe transport, the higher the fee. We do our best to provide both cost effective and careful handling of packaging your item. This fee is not negotiable and is usually reflected in all posted S&amp;H charges, or added to shipping quotes for larger items. Free counters provided by Honesty.com This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045898369">
    <Name>SCHNAUZER DOGS COTTON THROW BLANKET</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Animals</Category>
    <Category>Dog</Category>
    <Category>Schnauzer</Category>
    <Currently>$29.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$29.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Nashua, NH</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:53:30</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 19:53:30</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="partyman1" Rating="12311"/>
    <Description>SCHNAUZER DOGS COTTON THROW BLANKET Description Schnauzer Dogs Beautiful 100% Cotton Tapestry Throw Blanket - measures a large 47x60 inches! This is a high quality Woven throw, made in USA. Great decoration for you home, office, excellent to hang on wall, fold on bed, etc. Brand new unopened condition, from non-smoking environment, makes an excellent gift. Easy payment - we accept Paypal, Billpoint, Visa, Master Card, Check or Money Order. Buyer please pay $7 for professional packaging and shipment to your doorstep, nationwide! Good luck with your bids on this beautiful 100% Cotton Dog Throw Blanket! Payment and Shipping Info Payment Options Credit Card, Money Order / Cashier's Check, PayPal, Personal Check, Billpoint Shipping/Handling Rate $7.00 Insurance Rate See Item Description Shipping Options UPS - Ground, US Postal Service Sales Tax 0% for in-state buyers / 0% for out-of-state buyers Terms Thank you for your winning bid! BILLPOINT is our most preffered method of payment (we also accept paypal, check, or money order). We will contact you shortly, but in the meantime, our address is below if you'd like to send payment. Again, thank you very much! CJI Collectibles, LLC 491 Amherst St. Nashua, NH 03063 *** WE SHIP TO USA ONLY *** THIS MEANS YOU! NO EXCEPTIONS! ***</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045901760">
    <Name>Vintage Foley Food Mill Bakelite Handle NR</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Utensils</Category>
    <Category>Colanders, Strainers</Category>
    <Currently>$6.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>7</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="gilvanblight" Rating="902">
          <Location>Windsor, Ontario</Location>
          <Country>Canada</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 12:48:34</Time>
        <Amount>$3.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="photoman4u" Rating="242">
          <Location>PHOTOLAND</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 05:36:34</Time>
        <Amount>$3.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="auggdogg" Rating="847">
          <Location>TUCSON, ARIZONA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 22:24:34</Time>
        <Amount>$4.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="babydollhp" Rating="10">
          <Location>Groton, CT Go Navy!!!!!</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 15:12:34</Time>
        <Amount>$5.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="vick441" Rating="1114">
          <Location>Cookeville, Tennessee 38501</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 08:00:34</Time>
        <Amount>$5.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="mc-one" Rating="384">
          <Location>OK</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 00:48:34</Time>
        <Amount>$6.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="the86" Rating="131">
          <Location>Washington, PA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 17:36:34</Time>
        <Amount>$6.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Western, NY</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 20:00:34</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 20:00:34</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="ognibbn" Rating="507"/>
    <Description>Christmas is right around the corner. What a great gift idea!! VINTAGE FOLEY FOOD MILL This is a nice example of an older Foley food mill. It is in great shape and great working order. Handle and knob are made of bakelite. Handle has a hook on the end to hang it by. What every cook needs. See 3 pictures. Item will be shipped Priority Mail. Shipping will be $5.20. Insurance is extra and is based on the final sale price. (International shipping is extra and based on location.) Happy Bidding!! I prefer Paypal also accept Money Orders &amp; Checks. If you have any questions, please email me. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045902586">
    <Name>Dept 56 Classic Cars '50's Hot Rod MIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Dickens Village</Category>
    <Currently>$13.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$13.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>New England</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 19:59:48</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 19:59:48</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="washedashore" Rating="109"/>
    <Description>Dept 56 Classic Cars '50's Hot Rod MIB MIB ! NEVER DISPLAYED! This is the Dept 56 Snow Village piece #56-55282, a 1950's Hot Rod. This vehicle is part of the first release from the Classic Cars Collection,new from Department 56. The Snow Village Classic Cars Collection includes vintage cars from the 1940's &amp; 50. Each piece features a ceramic body with die-cast parts and moveable wheels. This is a classic handpainted 1950's Hot Rod with chrome exhausts and air intake and fine detailing. The car is MIB and has only been removed for inspection and photographing. Please check back often to see my new Dept 56 auctions. I Accept money orders, personal and cashier's checks and I also accept online payments (MC VISA &amp; Discover Card) through Billpoint. I may require your personal check to clear my bank before your item is shipped. I ask that you mail your payment or use the Billpoint online option within five days of the end of the auction. My email address is cjbstruthers@yahoo.com and I will do my best to answer your questions. I will leave feedback for all winning bidders. Sorry, I DO NOT accept Paypal. This delightful Dept 56 piece will be shipped anywhere within the continental U.S. for $4.99 s/h/ins. Please email for shipping charges to other locations. Please click here to see my other auctions. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Pro Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $4.99 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (5.000% if shipped to MA) Payment Instructions Insurance is included at no additional charge. Billpoint (eBay) Payment is available. Items can be combined from multiple auctions for lower s/h/i rates. If you purchase multiple items and are using Billpoint DO NOT use the Pay Now button as it will result in incorrect shipping charges. Email me &amp; I will send a correct Billpoint Invoice. Sorry, I DO NOT take Paypal. Thanks for bidding on my auction.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045905071">
    <Name>NEW! Mr. Everlove TJ's Best Dressed</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Boyds</Category>
    <Currently>$17.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$17.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Oklahoma City</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 20:03:09</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 20:03:09</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="imstoys" Rating="321"/>
    <Description>Mr. Everlove TJ's Best Dressed Collection Boyd's Bears 912655 BRAND NEW IN BOX A MUST HAVE FOR CHRISTMAS. SOME OF OUR PRODUCTS HAVE SOME TO SLIGHT MOISTURE DAMAGE ON THE BOXES. THE PRODUCTS ARE ALL BRAND NEW IN THE BOX. SOME OF THE BOXES WILL HAVE SLIGHT DAMAGE. PLEASE SEE OUR FEEDBACK. WE ONLY SELL TOP NOTCH PRODUCTS. IMS TOYS IMS TOYS knows the importants of the holiday season. That's why IMS TOYS is proud to bring you the best selection of Christmas gifts on the net!! We make sure that every product we sell is of the best quality. IMS TOYS' exceptional customer service department will make sure that your order is processed in a very speedy manner, and that your product will make it in plenty of time to be safely stored underneath any Christmas tree. TRY OUR NEW EBAY SEARCH ENGINE!! Search IMS TOYS IMS TOYS brought it to you first! Search IMS TOYS for all of your CHRISTMAS needs! View all of our CD Auctions by clicking HERE! View our CHRISTMAS GIFT auctions for TOYS, BABY PRODUCTS, MOVIES, AND MORE by clicking HERE! Accepted Forms of Payment Because we desire to get your package shipped to you as quickly as possible, we recommend paying with either a credit or debit card. We accept Visa and Mastercard through PayPal. PayPal, the #1 payment service for eBay auctions, is free and secure. All PayPal paid orders will be shipped within 36 hours. All mailed in payments are shipped once a week on Fridays. Visit PayPal or pay when the auction ends by clicking the box below: function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppslv"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"I prefer PayPal, the #1 payment service in online auctions!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay with PayPal!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("BID")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("DESC")=0){c4++;}}if(c2=2){dw(2);}else if(c1=2){if(c2=1){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}}else if((c30)&amp;&amp;(c4==0)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f12="ViewBids";f13="item=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){document.links[i].href=((document.links[i].href)+"&amp;jitem_id="+f14+"&amp;jmagic=1");}} Money orders, or cashiers checks. We highly recommend paying with PayPal to expedite your order. All payments must be in U.S. funds. Standard Shipping &amp; Handling Rates Standard (Insured) UPS Ground (USA): $8.00 for first item. UPS Delivers within 3-5 business days, occasionally up to 7 business days - shipping to U.S. We gladly combine shipping on multiple items for our auctions. Shipping delays may occur over observed holidays. We are sorry, but at this time, we do not accept international orders, including Canada. We ship to the contiguous 48 states only. Customer Service (Contacting Us) If you have any questions about this product or any other products you see on our auctions, please contact our customer service department at: toys@imsmailbox.com</Description>
  </Item>
 </Items>
