<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE Items SYSTEM "items.dtd">
<Items>
  <Item ItemID="1045769659">
    <Name>SPRINGERLE COOKIE BOARD ** NO RESERVE**</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Other Kitchenware</Category>
    <Currently>$14.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$14.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="torrisattic" Rating="223">
          <Location>Happy Holidays</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:23:53</Time>
        <Amount>$14.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Sunny South</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:23:53</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:23:53</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="do-south" Rating="21"/>
    <Description>Wood Springerle cookie borad depicting a FISH, flowers &amp; birds. It will imprint 8 designs in all. It is app. 3" x 8" in size. Nice patina...no cracks. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Contact must be made within 3 days of close of auction. Item must be paid for within 10 days by PayPal or Money Order for next day shipping. Personal checks must clear bank prior to shipping. International buyers must pay by PayPal or Postal Money Orders for US dollars. Buyer to pay shipping/handling and insurance if desired. Satisfaction is guaranteed if notified within 3 days of receipt of item.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045770692">
    <Name>Lanam Co. Lid to fit Longaberger Envelope NEW</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$13.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$13.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="dpaustintx" Rating="100">
          <Location>SEE MY OTHER AUCTIONS</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:25:30</Time>
        <Amount>$13.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Ohio - The Buckeye State!</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:25:30</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:25:30</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dog415@msn.com" Rating="178"/>
    <Description>You are bidding on an oak lid made by the Lanam Company to fit the Longaberger Envelope Basket. This lid has never been used or displayed, stored in my smoke free home. It features laser engraving and hand painting and is just what you need to complete your basket. Buyer to pay actual shipping. I will accept money order, paypal or personal check but will hold until check clears. Over the next few days, I will be selling several baskets and lids from my personal collection. Most have never been used or displayed. Be sure to check my other auctions. Feel free to email me with questions. Thanks for lookig!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045771355">
    <Name>Nabisco OREO Cookie Stacked Cookies Jar NR!!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Cookie Jars</Category>
    <Category>Modern (1970-Now)</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Great State of, Kentucky</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:26:02</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:26:02</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="kywildman" Rating="128"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#FFFFFF; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #ffffff; } Nabisco OREO Cookie Stacked Cookies Jar NR!!! Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Here is a wonderful Nabisco OREO Cookie Jar. Stands about 12 inches tall and features a stack of very large OREO Cookies with a comical Oreo Cookie with a face as the handle at the top. Part of the Nabisco Classics collection. Has two very small nicks in the back otherwise no cracks or crazing. If you have any questions, please email me before you bid as all sales are final and I want you to be happy with your purchase! Happy bidding! Buyer to pay actual shipping unless otherwise noted in auction description. Payments to be recieved within 10 days of close of auction. We happily take Paypal, Visa, MasterCard, Money Orders Cashier's Checks and Personal Checks, from US buyers only. Internationala Buyers payments accepted via USD Money Order or Cash Only there will be a 10 day delay in shipping your item after receiving payment by personal check. This allows enough time for the check to clear the bank. There will be a $25.00 charge for any check returned unpaid. Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Visa/Master Card, Discover, Money Order, Personal Check. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773325">
    <Name>OVERSTREET COMIC BOOK PRICE GUIDE #8 (1978)!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Other Modern Age</Category>
    <Currently>$11.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$11.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="grandmap2823" Rating="1084">
          <Location>Paypal Preferred</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:29:40</Time>
        <Amount>$11.95</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Prescott, Arizona</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:29:40</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:29:40</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="cparadise" Rating="6506"/>
    <Description>This is The Official Overstreet Comic Book Price Guide #8 (condition VF/nm; softcover), published by Overstreet Publications, 1978!!! Contents include: Grading, Storage, How to Start Collecting, Collecting Back Issues, Buying and Selling, Conventions, History of Fandom, Fanzines, Collecting Strips, Collecting Original Art, price lists, and more!! WE SHIP WORLDWIDE!!! Write to ask for shipping rates outside the USA! (**WINNERS OF MULTIPLE AUCTIONS CAN COMBINE TO SAVE ON SHIPPING**) After you bid on this item, we want to see you bidding on other items from us. However, we realize that with all the auctions we run, it is hard to look through them and find what you might want. To help you out, we have come up with 4 different ways, not generally offered by eBay, to search our auctions . 1) Click here to search our other auctions alphabetically starting from A to Z (numbers come 1st) then the As, Bs, Cs, Ds, Es, etc.! 2) Click here to search our other auctions alphabetically starting from Z to A. In this order Zs, Ys, Xs, Ws, Vs, Us, etc.! 3) Click here to search our other auctions by lowest current price to highest current price, $3.95, $4.95, $5.95, etc.! 4) Click here to search our other auctions by items closing the soonest (this is less organized but you can get last minute deals easier here)! Good Luck Bidding!! Shipping Terms: High bidder pays either $2.50 Book Rate shipping (10-21 days for delivery) or $4.00 Priority shipping (3-5 days for delivery) To cover the cost of our packing materials and employee's wages who pack the orders, all orders are subject to an 80_ handling fee. Insurance is an extra $1.10(per $50 of value) and is required on auctions closing above $25. If you choose no insurance and your package is lost or damaged, no refund is possible. We have been in business for 10 years so bid with confidence. Payment may be made with Pay-Pal (at our address of wantlist@cableone.net), with Money Order, Check, or directly with VISA, MASTERCARD, or DISCOVER. To pay by credit card directly please call us at (928)717-1030 and leave your name, item #, credit card #, expiration date, address, and telephone #. Please speak slow and clear as you have about 2 minutes to record this information. To pay by check or money order please send payment to: Randy Tusha P.O. Box 4224 Prescott, AZ 86302-4224 Payment must be received within 10 days of close of auction. Positive feedback will only be left for those paying promptly, and only after you have received your order and are satisfied. Negative feedback will be left for anyone who doesn't pay! ***SPECIAL NOTE*** WE ARE CLOSED ON WEEKENDS! We contact all winners on Mon-Wed following the auctions. Randy &amp; Michelle Tusha Hours: Monday - Friday 10:00 A.M to 6:00 P.M. Mountain Time (928)717-1030 Besides our normal 300-400 auctions per week: Click here to see our HIGHER DOLLAR items, listed on EBAY! Click here to e-mail us with questions about this or any other item we are listing on eBay!!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773349">
    <Name>Great 3color DIRIGO acl soda bottle BOAT lake</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bottles: Modern (1900-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Sodas</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$48.64</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>DEACON JONE'S LOCKER</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:30:55</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:30:55</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dknjonz" Rating="385"/>
    <Description>Fantastic "near-mint/mint" condition- no chips, cracks, or case wear; super-glossy, three color painted label and smooth, scratch-free glass. Twelve ounce size, from Dirigo Bottling Co., Portland, Maine. 1942. A real beauty! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773721">
    <Name>ELVIS PRESLEY BLACK AND WHITE.NR</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Art, Animation &amp; Photo Images</Category>
    <Category>Photographic Images</Category>
    <Category>Contemporary (1940-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Celebrity</Category>
    <Category>Other</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>MISSOURI</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:30:59</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:30:59</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="angel65767" Rating="63"/>
    <Description>IT IS A BLACK AND WHITE PICTURE OF ELVIS PRESLEY,IT IS NOT A CUT OUT EITHER.I,VE HAD IT FOR A LONG WHILE.IT IS ABOUT A 13 BY 10 PICTURE WITH FRAME.BUYER PAYS SHIPING AND HANDLING ALSO INSURANCE.THANK YOU FOR STOPING BY.GOOD LUCK ON BIDDING.NR</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045776745">
    <Name>Vintage Mirro Cookie-Pastry Press W/Recipes</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bakeware</Category>
    <Currently>$26.00</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$113.32</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$8.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>6</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kathyh05" Rating="1050">
          <Location>Calif</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 11:15:38</Time>
        <Amount>$11.82</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jaci888" Rating="1262">
          <Location>OR</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 05:55:38</Time>
        <Amount>$14.66</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="worldsawayimport@aol.com" Rating="2220">
          <Location>Beautiful Lake Tahoe, CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 00:35:38</Time>
        <Amount>$17.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="blagnothing666" Rating="214">
          <Location>Kingston PA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 19:15:38</Time>
        <Amount>$20.33</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="rose-noire" Rating="341">
          <Location>Northern California</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 13:55:38</Time>
        <Amount>$23.16</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="judyandjef@aol.com" Rating="1126">
          <Location>Fl.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 08:35:38</Time>
        <Amount>$26.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Northville, MI 48167</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:35:38</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:35:38</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="meldarr" Rating="3402"/>
    <Description>Vintage Mirro Cookie-Pastry Press W/Recipes This is a vintage Mirro brand cookie-pastry press in the original box with recipes. You are getting the aluminum press, 12 cookie plates and 3 pastry tips, and an instruction/recipe book. This is in very good condition -- looks like it was never used. All the pieces fit down into a styrofoam base and there is a box bottom only -- I think a lid of some type is missing, but the base fits over the styrofoam. If you are planning to make holiday Spritz cookies -- this is just what you need! NO RESERVE! Buyer agrees by bidding to pay $5.20 for shipping in the U.S. Most likely, the shipping quote is priority mail through the USPS, but I also use first class, or media mail if appropriate. Insurance is optional at $1.10 for the first $50. coverage. If you opt to not have insurance it is understood that you are shipping at your own risk. If I have not given a quote above it is because this weighs more than 5 lbs. wrapped and the costs vary depending on where you live -- You can get an exact quote by going to the postal website at www.usps.gov -- my zip code is 48167. I cannot ship UPS. International rates will be higher -- write me for a quote before you bid if you are concerned about the cost. Bid on more than one item to save shipping costs!! ALL THE FINE PRINT: Personal checks, money orders, PayPal, Billpoint or Bidpay are accepted. I make every effort to ship as soon as possible with any type of payment. Since I list a wide variety of collectibles, I can't be an expert on everything. I do try to be as accurate as possible in my item descriptions, but I may inadvertently leave out some information because I'm not that familiar with a particular piece. If you have any questions, please feel free to e-mail me. Thank you for looking!! Michigan residents must pay 6% sales tax or provide me with your tax ID#. Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="iid=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Free counters provided by Honesty.com This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $6.30 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (6.000% if shipped to MI) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions If the shipping amount is listed as $1.10 only, that is just the insurance. It is because this weighs more than 5 lbs. wrapped. I will need to calculate the shipping cost based on your address. Returns allowed if item not as listed.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045780900">
    <Name>FATHOM 0 GREEN PRISM VAR SIGNED LIM 250 RARE</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Other Modern Age</Category>
    <Currently>$22.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$22.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>AUBURN CA.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:43:45</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:43:45</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="scout0001" Rating="1127"/>
    <Description>THIS IS THE GREEN PRISIM VARIANT SIGNED BY TURNER AND LIMITED TO 250 COPIES. VERY LIMITED AND VERY RARE. NM CONDITION. BUYER TO PAY $3.50 PRIORITY.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045781414">
    <Name>Longaberger Double Chocolate Cocoa Tin</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$4.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$30.83</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$4.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Lehigh Valley, PA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:45:07</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:45:07</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bonaire3" Rating="157"/>
    <Description>This Double Chocolate Cocoa Tin is brand new from the Homestead. It contains 2.5 oz of Double Chocolate Cocoa. This item was produced exclusively for the Longaberger Company by McSteven's, Inc. It is labeled collectable mini tin #369. Priority shipping &amp; handling is $3.50. I accpet PayPay, Billpoint, and money orders. Personal checks will be accepted from eBayers with a positive feedback rating of 40+. Payment must be received within 10 days of auction close or auction considered void. See my other auctions and save on shipping. Please e-mail with questions prior to bidding. Thank you.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045781936">
    <Name>Longaberger/Mary's Moo Moos HOMESTEAD SIGN!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$30.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$29.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kidsgalorenmoreaw" Rating="172">
          <Location>Lake Wales, Fl.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 02:21:58</Time>
        <Amount>$30.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="badangel49" Rating="1">
          <Location>La Plata, MD</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 11:57:58</Time>
        <Amount>$30.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Dayton, Ohio</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:45:58</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:45:58</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="terih" Rating="4171"/>
    <Description>Hello! This is a great new Longaberger/Enesco Mary's Moo Moos exclusive item! This is a resin piece with a Mary's Moo Moo standing next to the 'Welcome To The Longaberger Homestead' sign. She is holding the classic Apple basket filled with daisies. This is a very detailed item! Just check out the picture. The back of the sign also shows the back of the cow, sign, and more daisies! Bottom states'"From our hearts to you a little moo and daisies too" The Longaberger Company Exclusive'. This is brand new and includes its original box with registration card. Measures 5 1/2" x 3 1/4". Buyer pays $4.50 shipping. Insurance is additional. Credit cards by Paypal, MO, and personal checks accepted. Please click on my "me" page for all the specifics and fine print. Also check out all of my other auctions. I combine items to save you on shipping. E-mail response expected within 3 days, payment within 14 days. Thanks for looking! Teri Click HERE to see my other auctions! I combine items to save you shipping! Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="iid=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045782248">
    <Name>57pc ROGERS PRECIOUS MIRROR FLATWARE W/BOX</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Tableware</Category>
    <Category>Flatware</Category>
    <Currently>$69.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$69.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>merlin</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:46:05</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:46:05</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="$303" Rating="534"/>
    <Description>57pc ROGERS PRECIOUS MIRROR FLATWARE W/BOX THIS IS A VERY NICE SET OF ROGERS FLATWARE. ITS PRECIOUS MIRROR PATTERN AND THE PIECES ARE : 8-8 1/2 INCH KNIFES , 8-7 INCH SOUP SPOONS , 16-6 INCH TEA SPOONS , 8-7 1/2 INCH FORKS , 8-6 3/4 INCH FORKS , 1-8 3/4 INCH SERVING FORK , 1-6 INCH LADLE , 2-8 1/4 INCH SERVING SPOONS , 1-9 1/2 INCH PIE SERVER , 1-9 INCH VEGETABLE SERVER , 1-7 3/4 INCH TOMATO SERVER , 1-6 INCH SUGAR SPOON , AND 1-6 3/4 INCH BUTTER KNIFE. THE SET IS IN VERY NICE CONDITION WITH NO TABLE WARE AND LITTLE TARNISH. THE CHEST IS MADE WITH DOVE TAIL CONSTRUCTION AND IN GREAT CONDITION. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045785902">
    <Name>Longaberger Serving Solutions 8x8 Bskt &amp; Prot</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Dinnerware, Serving</Category>
    <Currently>$40.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$40.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="craftskitty" Rating="33">
          <Location>Grand Rapids,Mi</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:54:10</Time>
        <Amount>$40.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Exeter, CA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:54:10</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:54:10</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bethmicari" Rating="28"/>
    <Description>Just in time for the holidays. You are bidding on a BRAND NEW Longaberger SERVING SOLUTIONS 8 X 8 BASKET, DIVIDED PROTECTOR AND REGULAR PROTECTOR . This is brand new, never been used. Please see my other auctions for other Longaberger Items. Thanks for shopping and have a nice Holiday Season. Buyer to pay 5.95 shipping.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045788253">
    <Name>Home Interior Rooster SconcesPr. / MIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>HOMCO</Category>
    <Currently>$18.95</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$36.59</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$18.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>York, Pa.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:59:11</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:59:11</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bbw55" Rating="595"/>
    <Description>Two Home Interior Hostess Only "Morning Rooster Sconces" in black metal. Measures 4-1/4" x 5-1/4" x 13". Both are mint in the box. I have votive cups available for separate purchase if needed. Shipping in the U.S. priority mail will be $3.95, plus $1.10 optional ins. I accept money orders, cashiers checks, bidpay and paypal. Personal checks accepted with a 14 banking business hold to clear. Payment is to be received within 10 days of auction close. Visit my other auctions for more Home Interior and I will combine on shipping when possible. New items added weekly.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045788549">
    <Name>DEPARTMENT 56 SNOWBABIE MAKE IT SHINE NEW</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snowbabies</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$61.32</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Eighty Four</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:59:48</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:59:48</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="louber" Rating="1417"/>
    <Description>DEPARTMENT 56 SNOWBABIE MAKE IT SHINE NEW THIS IS A BRANDE NEW DEPARTMENT 56 SNOWBABIE NAMED "MAKE IT SHINE". IT IS MINT IN THE ORIGINAL PACKAGING. THIS IS AN EXCLUSIVE SNOWBABIE AND CAN'T BE BOUGHT IN ANY STORE. THIS BEAUTIFUL SNOWBABIE HAS ANGEL WINGS ON ITS BACK. SHE IS PLACING A SWAROVSKI CRYSTAL STAR ATOP THE CHRISTMAS TREE, WHILE HER PENGUIN FRIEND WATCHES WITH EXCITEMENT. IT MEASURES 3 3/4" H x 3"W AND IS MADE OF BISQUE PORCELAIN, WITH HAND PAINTED FACIAL FEATURES AND HAND APPLIED BISQUE CRYSTALS. PAYMENTS CAN BE MADE BY MONEY ORDERS, CHECKS AND BIDPAY ONLY. WINNING BIDDER WILL PAY $3.95 SHIPPING. INSURANCE IS EXTRA. THANKS FOR LOOKING AND HAPPY HOLIDAYS. click on image to enlarge Please visit our other auctions! Powered by The Auction Solution Copyright 2001 Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions PAYMENTS MUST BE RECEIVED WITHIN 10 DAYS AFTER THE AUCTION HAS ENDED.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045788675">
    <Name>DICKENS VILLAGE RETIRED WOOL SHOP W/BOX</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Dickens Village</Category>
    <Currently>$75.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$75.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Grand Haven, Michigan</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:00:00</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:00:00</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dickens_donnie" Rating="0"/>
    <Description>Dept 56 Dickens Village Series "WOOL SHOP" (no. 5924-2) issued in 1987 and retired in 1990. There are ivy sided turret rounds out one front corner of the shop. Wood framing around the 3 front windows. The shop is part of the Cobbelstone Shops series. It is in excellent condition along with the original box and sleeve. Buyer will pay actual shipping (and insurance if requested by the buyer-we recommend it since we can not be responsible for the item once it leaves our hands) to be determined at the time of sale. Payment is appreciated in 7 days, auction will be voided if payment is not received within 2 weeks. Money order and cashiers checks will ship the next day. Personal checks are OK but will delay shipping by 7 business days. We have additional hard to find pieces, please let us know if you are looking for a specific one. HAPPY HOLIDAYS! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Checks and money orders should be sent to Donald Wolffis; 413 Sandpiper; Grand Haven, MI 49417..items will be sent after personal checks clear..money orders will be sent the next day.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045788878">
    <Name>SNOWBABIES - I'M AN ARTIST - SET OF 3 - MIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snowbabies</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>New Jersey</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:59:56</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:59:56</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="chardi" Rating="242"/>
    <Description>Snowbabies _I_m an Artist Part of the Department 56 Snowbabies, number 69069. This piece was introduced in 2000. Set of Three. Item is in mint condition in original sleeve and only removed for inspection. Buyer to pay a fixed shipping/handing and insurance fee of $6.00. Payments should be received within ten days of auction_s close. Item shipped immediately with cashier_s check, Paypal, or money order. Personal checks must clear before item is shipped. Feel free to contact me with any questions. Please view my other auctions. Thank You!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045789448">
    <Name>God Of War XENA Season 6 9 CARD SET **NEW**</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Trading Cards</Category>
    <Category>Science Fiction</Category>
    <Category>Other Sci-Fi</Category>
    <Currently>$3.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$3.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>FARGO, ND.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:00:27</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-18-01 17:00:27</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lantrn1" Rating="6352"/>
    <Description>THIS MINT CARD SET HAS 9 CARDS. YOU ARE BIDDING ON THE SET ONLY. THIS HAS JUST COME OUT FROM RITTENHOUSE. PLEASE SEE MY OTHER AUCTIONS FOR AUTOGRAPHS, COSTUME CARDS AND OTHER INSERTS. SHIPPING IS $1.50. MULTIPLE WINNERS CAN COMBINE FOR CHEAPER SHIPPING COSTS. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045789543">
    <Name>Aphrodite XENA Season 6 COSTUME CARD #R3</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Trading Cards</Category>
    <Category>Science Fiction</Category>
    <Category>Other Sci-Fi</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="*2ndhand*" Rating="216">
          <Location>Adirondacks</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 05:00:31</Time>
        <Amount>$9.95</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>FARGO, ND.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:00:31</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-18-01 17:00:31</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lantrn1" Rating="6352"/>
    <Description>THIS MINT COSTUME CARD COMES ONE TO A BOX. YOU ARE BIDDING ON THIS CARD ONLY. THIS SET HAS JUST COME OUT FROM RITTENHOUSE. PLEASE SEE MY OTHER AUCTIONS FOR AUTOGRAPHS, COSTUME CARDS AND OTHER INSERTS. SHIPPING IS $1.00. MULTIPLE WINNERS CAN COMBINE FOR CHEAPER SHIPPING COSTS. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045790496">
    <Name>Dept 56 Snow Village Lionel Electric Shop NIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$27.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$27.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kdeitrick" Rating="178">
          <Location>SUNSHINE STATE</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 11:02:16</Time>
        <Amount>$27.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>U.S.A.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:02:16</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:02:16</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="tbenterprises" Rating="10"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#ffffff; } a.textLink { color:#93A836;} HR { color: #ffffff; } Dept 56 Snow Village Lionel Electric Shop NIB Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version This is a wonderful retired piece by Department 56 from the Snow Village Collection titled "Lionel Electric Train Shop". This item is brand new, never been displayed, comes in the original box, and from a smoke-free home! Winning bidder to pay $7.70 USPS Priority Shipping. Insurance is extra and highly recommended (see below). MAKE SURE YOU CHECK OUT MY OTHER ITEMS BY CLICKING ON THE STOREFRONT LINK AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS PAGE. I will COMBINE SHIPPING CHARGES with multiple purchases, but to make sure I am aware of your multiple purchases..please e-mail me following the auction close in order to get a quote on shipping RIGHT AWAY!!! Payment must be received within 10 days of auction close or item will be relisted and negative feedback may be posted - depending on circumstances. I accept PayPal, Money Orders, personal checks, and Cashier's Checks! PayPal and Money orders ship within 3 business days of payment receipt. Personal checks will require clearance (usually 7 days) before shipping. Shipping DOES NOT INCLUDE INSURANCE. Due to the increase in postal rates insurance will be an additional cost. Priority rates for insurance are $1.10 for up to $50.00 and $2.00 for $50.01 up to $100.00. Buyer assumes liability for lost or damaged items not insured. Please include item description and ebay item number if possible on all correspondence. PLEASE USE THE LINK ON THE WINNING BID NOTIFICATION E-MAIL I SEND TO COMPLETE THE TRANSACTION! Not doing so may delay processing your item. All bids are expected to be honored! Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Money Order, Personal Check. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045790825">
    <Name>Dept 56 Heritage East Willet Pottery NIB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$22.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$22.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>U.S.A.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:02:34</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:02:34</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="tbenterprises" Rating="10"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; font-weight : bold; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#ffffff; } a.textLink { color:#93A836;} HR { color: #ffffff; } Dept 56 Heritage East Willet Pottery NIB Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version This is a wonderful retired piece by Department 56 from the Heritage Village Collection titled "East Willet Pottery". This item is brand new, never been displayed, comes in the original box, and from a smoke-free home! Winning bidder to pay $7.70 USPS Priority Shipping. Insurance is extra and highly recommended (see below). MAKE SURE YOU CHECK OUT MY OTHER ITEMS BY CLICKING ON THE STOREFRONT LINK AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS PAGE. I will COMBINE SHIPPING CHARGES with multiple purchases, but to make sure I am aware of your multiple purchases..please e-mail me following the auction close in order to get a quote on shipping RIGHT AWAY!!! Payment must be received within 10 days of auction close or item will be relisted and negative feedback may be posted - depending on circumstances. I accept PayPal, Money Orders, personal checks, and Cashier's Checks! PayPal and Money orders ship within 3 business days of payment receipt. Personal checks will require clearance (usually 7 days) before shipping. Shipping DOES NOT INCLUDE INSURANCE. Due to the increase in postal rates insurance will be an additional cost. Priority rates for insurance are $1.10 for up to $50.00 and $2.00 for $50.01 up to $100.00. Buyer assumes liability for lost or damaged items not insured. Please include item description and ebay item number if possible on all correspondence. PLEASE USE THE LINK ON THE WINNING BID NOTIFICATION E-MAIL I SEND TO COMPLETE THE TRANSACTION! Not doing so may delay processing your item. All bids are expected to be honored! Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Money Order, Personal Check. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045792355">
    <Name>Hallmark 1996 FELIZ NAVIDAD Orn MIMB</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$7.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$7.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Pittsburgh - Home of Steelers !</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:04:59</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:04:59</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="libbylibbylibby" Rating="1673"/>
    <Description>if (navigator.appName == 'Microsoft Internet Explorer') { if (navigator.appVersion.substring(0,1) "); } else { document.write(" "); document.write(" "); document.write(" BODY { background: url(http://home.adelphia.net/~libbys/snow.gif) }"); document.write(" "); document.write(" "); } } else { //Default to Netscape settings. document.write(" "); } Hallmark 1996 FELIZ NAVIDAD Orn MIMB Hallmark 1996 FELIZ NAVIDAD Sculpted by linda Sickman This Hallmark Ornament is Mint in mint box, never displayed, and comes from a totally smoke free home. Bid with confidence that you are purchasing from a top seller of Hallmark items. Buyer to pay $4.50 for USPS Priority shipping &amp; handling for ornaments and most other Hallmark items except Kiddie Cars , Insurance is additional based on final value. Shipping Charges are for one item, typically we can ship up to three Hallmark Ornaments based on the total weight at the single item cost. Heavier items when combined will cost a little more. Please see my other Auctions to combine and save $ on shipping costs. Our shipping costs are all based on Priority mail shipping. We do not use shipping costs as a way to make money only to cover the costs of packaging materials and Postage. We do not ship standard mail in the US at reduced rates so please don't ask. Even though our packaging top notch and we have very very few problems or lost mail We assume no liability for items shipped without insurance so if you have any reservations about item damage please ask for insurance. This pricing is for US addresses only. International bidders should contact me before auction ends for a shipping estimate, based on your needs. Payment is expected within 7 days of close of auction. Methods of payment accepted are PayPal, BillPoint Yahoo Paydirect, postal money orders or cashier's checks for immediate shipping upon receipt. Personal checks are also welcome but may delay shipping up to 10 days while check is clearing bank. Returned Checks are subject to a $15.00 handling fee. Please email me if you have any questions or would like additional images.Thank you for Bidding Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="item=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Please check out the other auctions we currently have running on eBay to combine and save on shipping charges. Created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $4.50 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.10 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions We want you to be as satisfied with your Hallmark items as we are in them. We sell only 1st quality items unless otherwise it stated in Auction .Returns on items that are clearly not as described.. No returns without prior notification and approval.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045793153">
    <Name>Good Friends Are For Always 524131 Ornament</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$7.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$7.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Springfield, MO</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:06:34</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:06:34</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="no.1teacher" Rating="37"/>
    <Description>This 1992 figurine ornament has a treble clef mark. It comes with its original box and papers. It is in mint condition. This charming girl is holding her bunny. The girl has pastel purple hat, coat, and pants. The hat has a pink pom pom on the top of it with a rough edge look around the brim. She has blond hair. The bunny has a pink bow between its ears and is in a pink dress. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $4.00 Shipping Insurance per item (optional) $1.10 Sales Tax (none) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions Payment Accepted: Money Order, Cashiers Checks, Billpoint, Paypal. Winning bidder will pay $4.00 for shipping for the 1st piece and $1.00 additional for every extra piece won in the United States. Insurance is an additional $1.10 and is choice of buyer. Without insurance, I do not guarantee the figurine. No returns.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045795074">
    <Name>LUCY AND ME LUCY RIGG BEAR PEACE ON EARTH</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Lucy &amp; Me</Category>
    <Currently>$11.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$8.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>5</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="cutsiepups" Rating="484">
          <Location>CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 14:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$9.10</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="abraceme" Rating="216">
          <Location>East Coast</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 11:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$9.70</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ex0rcist2000" Rating="190">
          <Location>CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 08:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$10.30</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="consider.it" Rating="509">
          <Location>Anacortes, Wa.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 05:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$10.90</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="ianmuir681@aol.com" Rating="97">
          <Location>Caithness, Scotland</Location>
          <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 02:10:31</Time>
        <Amount>$11.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>CH-CH-CHICAGO</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:10:31</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:10:31</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="kag54" Rating="781"/>
    <Description>LUCY AND ME PEACE ON EARTH ENESCO 1992 by Lucy Rigg &amp; Co. Lucy &amp; Me is gone. It is no longer in production. This is a cute piece is a bear dressed as the world, holding a banner that reads" Peace On Earth". Also has a small dove on his head.. Approximately 3 1/4 " in height. You can see by the picture this piece has great coloring. The bottom of the piece has the Lucy and Me markings. Good Luck Bidding. This bear needs a good home! A great addition to the Lucy and Me or bear collector. See my other auctions for Lucy And Me and Lucy Riggs items. BUYER TO PAY $3.50 IN SHIPPING AND DELIVERY, COST ADJUSTED FOR INSURANCE OR SHIPPING OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES. MONEY ORDER OR CASHIERS CHECK ARE PREFERRED METHOD OF PAYMENT. IF PAYING BY PERSONAL CHECK, SHIPMENT WILL BE MADE AFTER CHECK CLEARS. METHOD OF PAYMENT FOR WINNERS OUTSIDE OF UNITED STATES WILL BE DETERMINED AT A LATER DATE. PAYMENT EXPECTED WITHIN 10 BUSINESS DAYS AFTER AUCTION ENDS. Click below to... View my other auctions _ Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045795128">
    <Name>DEPT 56 SV CHOPPING FIREWOOD - MIB - SET/2</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Dept 56</Category>
    <Category>Snow Village</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>New Jersey</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:10:19</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:10:19</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="chardi" Rating="242"/>
    <Description>Snow Village _Chopping Firewood This item is part of the Department 56 Snow Village #54863. This piece was introduced in 1995 and is current. Set of 2. Father chops wood as son stacks into ventilated cords. Materials are ceramic and wood. This item is in mint condition in original sleeve and only removed for inspection. Buyer to pay a fixed shipping/handing and insurance fee of $5.00. Payments should be received within ten days of auction_s close. Item shipped immediately with cashier_s check, Pay Pal or money order, personal checks must clear before item is shipped. Feel free to contact me with any questions. Please view my other auctions. Thank You!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045795866">
    <Name>17 #1 Comics Worth A LOOK! NM-MINT!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Superhero</Category>
    <Currently>$19.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$19.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Mankato</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:12:00</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:12:00</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="lazyacre" Rating="191"/>
    <Description>ones#2 17 #1 Comics Worth A LOOK!! NM-MINT!! This lot consists of ; 17 #1 comics in nm-mint condition except for Rima the Jungle Girl which is in fine condition, the starting bid is less than 1/2 of The Overstreet Price Guide Value. _ These comics have been bagged and boarded since they were first sold, check out the scans and judge for yourself. _ TERMS AND SHIPPING By bidding on this auction, you agree to the following terms: Payment must be received within 10 days. Money orders shipped immediately. Checks need 10 days to clear. You pay shipping only _ no handling charge. All comics sent priority mail with delivery confirmation. Shipping rates are as follows; (5 regular size comics = 1 lb.) 1-5 comics $3.90 6-10 comics $4.35 11-15 comics $5.55 16-20 comics $6.75 21-25 comics $7.95 Thanks for bidding! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045796439">
    <Name>Pampered Cheff meat pounder</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Utensils</Category>
    <Category>Other Utensils</Category>
    <Currently>$2.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$2.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="rickflash" Rating="119">
          <Location>Vic</Location>
          <Country>Canada</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 12:25:14</Time>
        <Amount>$2.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Montclair, NJ</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:13:14</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:13:14</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="gmckelv@aol.com" Rating="91"/>
    <Description>This is a brand new meat pounder to make your meat flat. Works great. I have two of these. I use the other one all the time. It makes your meat (like chicken and steak) more flat and thin. Shipping is 3.95 Paypal or money order Check out my other auction and safe on shipping Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions sales are final.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045796776">
    <Name>1998 HALLMARK 1917 CURTISS JENNY PLANE 2nd</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Hallmark</Category>
    <Category>Series Ornaments</Category>
    <Currently>$11.51</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>5</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="realgrafs" Rating="885">
          <Location>NEW YORK</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 14:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$5.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="littlericky1" Rating="694">
          <Location>C.C.CA.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 11:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$7.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="sacauction" Rating="1113">
          <Location>Sacramento California</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 08:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$8.51</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="wdgould" Rating="1415">
          <Location>Mid Michigan</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 05:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$10.01</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="marvinski" Rating="306">
          <Location>MOTTRAM, CHESHIRE</Location>
          <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 02:14:15</Time>
        <Amount>$11.51</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Englewood, CO</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 17:14:15</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 17:14:15</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="mannor" Rating="63"/>
    <Description>This is #2 in the Sky's the Limit series. The 1917 Curtiss JN-4D _Jenny,_ 1998 Hallmark Ornament. The ornament and box are both mint. This is a non smoking home. The winning bidder will pay $4.00 S&amp;H in the USA. Your package will be shipped by the USPS Priority mail. Insurance is additional, and based on the final value. We assume no liability for the items shipped without insurance. (We ship outside of the USA only if paid via Paypal and bidder pays actual cost of shipping.) Payment expected within 10 days of the close of the auction. Methods of payment accepted are Paypal, money orders, and cashier's checks for immediate shipping upon receipt. Personal checks also welcome, but will delay shipping for 10 working days while check clears my bank. Please explore my other auctions and combine purchases to save on shipping costs. Note that I also have the first and third planes in this series up for auction as well! THANKS for your time.</Description>
  </Item>
 </Items>
