<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE Items SYSTEM "items.dtd">
<Items>
  <Item ItemID="1045769659">
    <Name>SPRINGERLE COOKIE BOARD ** NO RESERVE**</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Other Kitchenware</Category>
    <Currently>$14.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$14.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="torrisattic" Rating="223">
          <Location>Happy Holidays</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:23:53</Time>
        <Amount>$14.50</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Sunny South</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:23:53</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:23:53</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="do-south" Rating="21"/>
    <Description>Wood Springerle cookie borad depicting a FISH, flowers &amp; birds. It will imprint 8 designs in all. It is app. 3" x 8" in size. Nice patina...no cracks. Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions Contact must be made within 3 days of close of auction. Item must be paid for within 10 days by PayPal or Money Order for next day shipping. Personal checks must clear bank prior to shipping. International buyers must pay by PayPal or Postal Money Orders for US dollars. Buyer to pay shipping/handling and insurance if desired. Satisfaction is guaranteed if notified within 3 days of receipt of item.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045770692">
    <Name>Lanam Co. Lid to fit Longaberger Envelope NEW</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$13.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$13.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="dpaustintx" Rating="100">
          <Location>SEE MY OTHER AUCTIONS</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:25:30</Time>
        <Amount>$13.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Ohio - The Buckeye State!</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:25:30</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:25:30</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dog415@msn.com" Rating="178"/>
    <Description>You are bidding on an oak lid made by the Lanam Company to fit the Longaberger Envelope Basket. This lid has never been used or displayed, stored in my smoke free home. It features laser engraving and hand painting and is just what you need to complete your basket. Buyer to pay actual shipping. I will accept money order, paypal or personal check but will hold until check clears. Over the next few days, I will be selling several baskets and lids from my personal collection. Most have never been used or displayed. Be sure to check my other auctions. Feel free to email me with questions. Thanks for lookig!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045771355">
    <Name>Nabisco OREO Cookie Stacked Cookies Jar NR!!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Cookie Jars</Category>
    <Category>Modern (1970-Now)</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Great State of, Kentucky</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:26:02</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:26:02</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="kywildman" Rating="128"/>
    <Description>.titledata { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:17px; color:#ffffff; } .description { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; color:#FFFFFF; } .link { font-family: verdana, sans-serif; font-size:12px; underline; } HR { color: #ffffff; } Nabisco OREO Cookie Stacked Cookies Jar NR!!! Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Click image to view larger version Here is a wonderful Nabisco OREO Cookie Jar. Stands about 12 inches tall and features a stack of very large OREO Cookies with a comical Oreo Cookie with a face as the handle at the top. Part of the Nabisco Classics collection. Has two very small nicks in the back otherwise no cracks or crazing. If you have any questions, please email me before you bid as all sales are final and I want you to be happy with your purchase! Happy bidding! Buyer to pay actual shipping unless otherwise noted in auction description. Payments to be recieved within 10 days of close of auction. We happily take Paypal, Visa, MasterCard, Money Orders Cashier's Checks and Personal Checks, from US buyers only. Internationala Buyers payments accepted via USD Money Order or Cash Only there will be a 10 day delay in shipping your item after receiving payment by personal check. This allows enough time for the check to clear the bank. There will be a $25.00 charge for any check returned unpaid. Payment I accept the following forms of payment: PayPal, Visa/Master Card, Discover, Money Order, Personal Check. Additional Information Low cost image hosting and full service auction management solutions: AuctionWatch</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773325">
    <Name>OVERSTREET COMIC BOOK PRICE GUIDE #8 (1978)!!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Other Modern Age</Category>
    <Currently>$11.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$11.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="grandmap2823" Rating="1084">
          <Location>Paypal Preferred</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 10:29:40</Time>
        <Amount>$11.95</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Prescott, Arizona</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:29:40</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:29:40</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="cparadise" Rating="6506"/>
    <Description>This is The Official Overstreet Comic Book Price Guide #8 (condition VF/nm; softcover), published by Overstreet Publications, 1978!!! Contents include: Grading, Storage, How to Start Collecting, Collecting Back Issues, Buying and Selling, Conventions, History of Fandom, Fanzines, Collecting Strips, Collecting Original Art, price lists, and more!! WE SHIP WORLDWIDE!!! Write to ask for shipping rates outside the USA! (**WINNERS OF MULTIPLE AUCTIONS CAN COMBINE TO SAVE ON SHIPPING**) After you bid on this item, we want to see you bidding on other items from us. However, we realize that with all the auctions we run, it is hard to look through them and find what you might want. To help you out, we have come up with 4 different ways, not generally offered by eBay, to search our auctions . 1) Click here to search our other auctions alphabetically starting from A to Z (numbers come 1st) then the As, Bs, Cs, Ds, Es, etc.! 2) Click here to search our other auctions alphabetically starting from Z to A. In this order Zs, Ys, Xs, Ws, Vs, Us, etc.! 3) Click here to search our other auctions by lowest current price to highest current price, $3.95, $4.95, $5.95, etc.! 4) Click here to search our other auctions by items closing the soonest (this is less organized but you can get last minute deals easier here)! Good Luck Bidding!! Shipping Terms: High bidder pays either $2.50 Book Rate shipping (10-21 days for delivery) or $4.00 Priority shipping (3-5 days for delivery) To cover the cost of our packing materials and employee's wages who pack the orders, all orders are subject to an 80_ handling fee. Insurance is an extra $1.10(per $50 of value) and is required on auctions closing above $25. If you choose no insurance and your package is lost or damaged, no refund is possible. We have been in business for 10 years so bid with confidence. Payment may be made with Pay-Pal (at our address of wantlist@cableone.net), with Money Order, Check, or directly with VISA, MASTERCARD, or DISCOVER. To pay by credit card directly please call us at (928)717-1030 and leave your name, item #, credit card #, expiration date, address, and telephone #. Please speak slow and clear as you have about 2 minutes to record this information. To pay by check or money order please send payment to: Randy Tusha P.O. Box 4224 Prescott, AZ 86302-4224 Payment must be received within 10 days of close of auction. Positive feedback will only be left for those paying promptly, and only after you have received your order and are satisfied. Negative feedback will be left for anyone who doesn't pay! ***SPECIAL NOTE*** WE ARE CLOSED ON WEEKENDS! We contact all winners on Mon-Wed following the auctions. Randy &amp; Michelle Tusha Hours: Monday - Friday 10:00 A.M to 6:00 P.M. Mountain Time (928)717-1030 Besides our normal 300-400 auctions per week: Click here to see our HIGHER DOLLAR items, listed on EBAY! Click here to e-mail us with questions about this or any other item we are listing on eBay!!</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773349">
    <Name>Great 3color DIRIGO acl soda bottle BOAT lake</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bottles: Modern (1900-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Sodas</Category>
    <Currently>$9.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$48.64</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>DEACON JONE'S LOCKER</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:30:55</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:30:55</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="dknjonz" Rating="385"/>
    <Description>Fantastic "near-mint/mint" condition- no chips, cracks, or case wear; super-glossy, three color painted label and smooth, scratch-free glass. Twelve ounce size, from Dirigo Bottling Co., Portland, Maine. 1942. A real beauty! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045773721">
    <Name>ELVIS PRESLEY BLACK AND WHITE.NR</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Art, Animation &amp; Photo Images</Category>
    <Category>Photographic Images</Category>
    <Category>Contemporary (1940-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Celebrity</Category>
    <Category>Other</Category>
    <Currently>$9.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>MISSOURI</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:30:59</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:30:59</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="angel65767" Rating="63"/>
    <Description>IT IS A BLACK AND WHITE PICTURE OF ELVIS PRESLEY,IT IS NOT A CUT OUT EITHER.I,VE HAD IT FOR A LONG WHILE.IT IS ABOUT A 13 BY 10 PICTURE WITH FRAME.BUYER PAYS SHIPING AND HANDLING ALSO INSURANCE.THANK YOU FOR STOPING BY.GOOD LUCK ON BIDDING.NR</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045776745">
    <Name>Vintage Mirro Cookie-Pastry Press W/Recipes</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Housewares &amp; Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Kitchenware</Category>
    <Category>Bakeware</Category>
    <Currently>$26.00</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$113.32</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$8.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>6</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kathyh05" Rating="1050">
          <Location>Calif</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 11:15:38</Time>
        <Amount>$11.82</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="jaci888" Rating="1262">
          <Location>OR</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 05:55:38</Time>
        <Amount>$14.66</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="worldsawayimport@aol.com" Rating="2220">
          <Location>Beautiful Lake Tahoe, CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 00:35:38</Time>
        <Amount>$17.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="blagnothing666" Rating="214">
          <Location>Kingston PA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 19:15:38</Time>
        <Amount>$20.33</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="rose-noire" Rating="341">
          <Location>Northern California</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-12-01 13:55:38</Time>
        <Amount>$23.16</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="judyandjef@aol.com" Rating="1126">
          <Location>Fl.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-13-01 08:35:38</Time>
        <Amount>$26.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Northville, MI 48167</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:35:38</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:35:38</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="meldarr" Rating="3402"/>
    <Description>Vintage Mirro Cookie-Pastry Press W/Recipes This is a vintage Mirro brand cookie-pastry press in the original box with recipes. You are getting the aluminum press, 12 cookie plates and 3 pastry tips, and an instruction/recipe book. This is in very good condition -- looks like it was never used. All the pieces fit down into a styrofoam base and there is a box bottom only -- I think a lid of some type is missing, but the base fits over the styrofoam. If you are planning to make holiday Spritz cookies -- this is just what you need! NO RESERVE! Buyer agrees by bidding to pay $5.20 for shipping in the U.S. Most likely, the shipping quote is priority mail through the USPS, but I also use first class, or media mail if appropriate. Insurance is optional at $1.10 for the first $50. coverage. If you opt to not have insurance it is understood that you are shipping at your own risk. If I have not given a quote above it is because this weighs more than 5 lbs. wrapped and the costs vary depending on where you live -- You can get an exact quote by going to the postal website at www.usps.gov -- my zip code is 48167. I cannot ship UPS. International rates will be higher -- write me for a quote before you bid if you are concerned about the cost. Bid on more than one item to save shipping costs!! ALL THE FINE PRINT: Personal checks, money orders, PayPal, Billpoint or Bidpay are accepted. I make every effort to ship as soon as possible with any type of payment. Since I list a wide variety of collectibles, I can't be an expert on everything. I do try to be as accurate as possible in my item descriptions, but I may inadvertently leave out some information because I'm not that familiar with a particular piece. If you have any questions, please feel free to e-mail me. Thank you for looking!! Michigan residents must pay 6% sales tax or provide me with your tax ID#. Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="iid=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Free counters provided by Honesty.com This listing created by eBay Seller's Assistant Basic. Payment Details U.S. Shipping and Handling $6.30 Shipping Insurance per item - Sales Tax (6.000% if shipped to MI) _ Learn more about checkout Payment Instructions If the shipping amount is listed as $1.10 only, that is just the insurance. It is because this weighs more than 5 lbs. wrapped. I will need to calculate the shipping cost based on your address. Returns allowed if item not as listed.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045780900">
    <Name>FATHOM 0 GREEN PRISM VAR SIGNED LIM 250 RARE</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Pop Culture</Category>
    <Category>Comics</Category>
    <Category>Modern Age (1980-Now)</Category>
    <Category>Other Modern Age</Category>
    <Currently>$22.95</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$22.95</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>AUBURN CA.</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:43:45</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:43:45</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="scout0001" Rating="1127"/>
    <Description>THIS IS THE GREEN PRISIM VARIANT SIGNED BY TURNER AND LIMITED TO 250 COPIES. VERY LIMITED AND VERY RARE. NM CONDITION. BUYER TO PAY $3.50 PRIORITY.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045781414">
    <Name>Longaberger Double Chocolate Cocoa Tin</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$4.99</Currently>
    <Buy_Price>$30.83</Buy_Price>
    <First_Bid>$4.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids/>
    <Location>Lehigh Valley, PA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:45:07</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:45:07</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="bonaire3" Rating="157"/>
    <Description>This Double Chocolate Cocoa Tin is brand new from the Homestead. It contains 2.5 oz of Double Chocolate Cocoa. This item was produced exclusively for the Longaberger Company by McSteven's, Inc. It is labeled collectable mini tin #369. Priority shipping &amp; handling is $3.50. I accpet PayPay, Billpoint, and money orders. Personal checks will be accepted from eBayers with a positive feedback rating of 40+. Payment must be received within 10 days of auction close or auction considered void. See my other auctions and save on shipping. Please e-mail with questions prior to bidding. Thank you.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1045781936">
    <Name>Longaberger/Mary's Moo Moos HOMESTEAD SIGN!</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Longaberger</Category>
    <Category>Other Longaberger Items</Category>
    <Currently>$30.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$29.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>2</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="kidsgalorenmoreaw" Rating="172">
          <Location>Lake Wales, Fl.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 02:21:58</Time>
        <Amount>$30.49</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder UserID="badangel49" Rating="1">
          <Location>La Plata, MD</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-11-01 11:57:58</Time>
        <Amount>$30.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location>Dayton, Ohio</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-08-01 16:45:58</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-15-01 16:45:58</Ends>
    <Seller UserID="terih" Rating="4171"/>
    <Description>Hello! This is a great new Longaberger/Enesco Mary's Moo Moos exclusive item! This is a resin piece with a Mary's Moo Moo standing next to the 'Welcome To The Longaberger Homestead' sign. She is holding the classic Apple basket filled with daisies. This is a very detailed item! Just check out the picture. The back of the sign also shows the back of the cow, sign, and more daisies! Bottom states'"From our hearts to you a little moo and daisies too" The Longaberger Company Exclusive'. This is brand new and includes its original box with registration card. Measures 5 1/2" x 3 1/4". Buyer pays $4.50 shipping. Insurance is additional. Credit cards by Paypal, MO, and personal checks accepted. Please click on my "me" page for all the specifics and fine print. Also check out all of my other auctions. I combine items to save you on shipping. E-mail response expected within 3 days, payment within 14 days. Thanks for looking! Teri Click HERE to see my other auctions! I combine items to save you shipping! Pay me securely with your Visa or MasterCard through PayPal! function dw(nu){document.write(s1+"ppsl"+nu+".gif"+s2+sA[nu]);}f1="document.links";s1="\ ","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\","\"Winning bidder, click here to pay instantly by credit card!\"\");c1=c2=c3=c4=0;for(i=0;i =0){c1++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("BetterSeller")=0){c2++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].search")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleShow")=0){c3++;}else if((eval(f1+"["+i+"].hash")).indexOf("ListItemForSaleAutosShow")=0){c4++;}}if((c1=2)||(c20)||(c30)||(c40)){dw(3);}else{dw(2);}f11="xclick-auction";f13="iid=";f14="";for(i=0;i 0){s11=document.links[i].search;j=s11.indexOf(f13);if(j0){s11=s11.slice((j+(f13.length)));for(k=0;k =0){var p=new Array();p[0]=document.links[i].protocol;p[1]=document.links[i].hostname;p[2]=document.links[i].pathname;for(j=0;j Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
 </Items>
